Chapter 1358: Mission

Book Nine: Races of the Spirit Realm

In an endless crimson forest of twisted trees, there were five young men and women. They were in a hidden part of the forest and were ten meters apart from one another.

One of them was a man about thirty years old. He wore embroidered robes and had snow-white robes with eyes like lightning.

There was a black-robed woman with a slender body, black brows and draped hair. Her face appeared hostile.

The other youth appeared in his late twenties with a blood-red birthmark on his mouth and a handsome appearance. His face wore a faint smile.

The second woman wore white robes and appeared to be eighteen. Her dainty face gave her an innocent appearance.

The last of them was an azure-robed youth in his early twenties with an expressionless face. He was Han Li, who had recently left Deep Heaven City.

The five appeared young, but their cultivation was at Deity Transformation stage and above. Apart from Han Li and the white-robed woman who had mid-stage cultivation, the other three possessed late Deity Transformation-stage cultivation.

However, the black-robed woman happened to be the woman surnamed Xiao from the Black Phoenix Clan, who Han Li first met at the beast wave when his cultivation was lost.

The woman coldly glared at Han Li. Although she said nothing, her eyes were filled with bewilderment.

“I truly didn’t think that you humans would send out three cultivators with two of them at mid-stage. Could it be that your race plans on having this operation fail?” The white-browed man coldly asked. Although his voice wasn’t very loud, everyone could clearly hear it.

When they heard the youth, the blood-marked youth’s brow faintly stirred and his smile faded. Han Li simply blinked and fiddled with a white jade slip in his hand.

As for the young white-robed woman, her black eyes were wandering, but a smile still stuck on her face.

The three didn’t reply.

When the white-browed man saw the three’s reaction, he was enraged and thought to say something when the woman surnamed Xiao suddenly said, “This mission is related to Deep Heaven City and the safety of both our kind. If we do not sincerely cooperate, let alone the mission, we may even fail to reach the mission’s destination. Don’t forget, we’ll have to spend a year travelling. Since your kind sent three Fellow Daoists, you must be unordinary. Since we’ll be spending some time with each other, let’s exchange names. I am Xiao Hong and come from the Black Phoenix Clan. This is Fellow Daoist Li from the Dark Falcon Clan.”

Xiao Hong spoke with a neutral tone.

When the blood-marked youth heard this, he raised his brow and smiled, “I am Long Dong. It seems your extreme flames come from refining your life flames to an astonishing realm.”

“You’re a member of the Long Clan!” Xiao Hong’s expression changed upon hearing him.

“I didn’t think that Fairy would know of my clan.” The blood-marked youth grinned and flashed his teeth.

“I am called Ye Ying.” The white-robed woman said with a chuckle. Her voice sounded like birdsong.

“Han Li!” Han Li shortly uttered his name and said nothing else.”

Xiao Hong looked at Han Li and her voice turned cold, “So it was you. It is no wonder you had those Immortal Vanquishing Beads. You were originally a high-grade cultivator. So you’re cultivating a dual body magic art.”

When they heard this, the other three appeared alarm.

“I do cultivate such a technique. It has been many years since I’ve seen you. How is Dai’er doing?” Han Li indifferently asked.

Xiao Hong paused for a moment and indifferently replied, “It was sensible for Dai’er to follow me at the time. She has cultivated at an immense speed and already possesses a golden core. It is only a matter of time before she overtakes both of us.”

“Is that so. I am glad she’s fine.” Han Li let out a faint sigh.

The white-robed young woman, Ye Ying , glanced at the two and asked with a giggle, “What? Does Sister Xiao recognize Brother Han?”

“Know him? Hehe, we can be considered old acquaintances.” Xiao Hong coldly laughed.

At that moment, the blood-marked youth glanced at the two and his sights briefly paused on Xiao Hong. He then immediately looked away.

His eyes deeply revealed a trace of greed and no one seemed to notice.

After some thought Xiao Hong warned, “Although this isn’t deep in the wilderness, it is already a sign of your strength that you were able to make it here. Our next step won’t be as easy as the way here. If we do not unit together, I fear that it will be difficult to safely pass through the Black Leaves Forest. This path contains an immense amount of danger.”

When they heard the name of the forest, the other four wore changed expressions.

The white-robed woman asked, “This mission is to scout the movements of the tree spirit clan? Will this mission be concluded once we recover the spies that are placed there and gather their information? That doesn’t seem too difficult.”

The blood-marked youth sighed and muttered, “That’s hard to say. It’ll depend a lot on luck. If it goes smoothly, the mission will be simple, but if we encounter trouble and the tree spirits discover us, we’ll all likely die. However, this mission is greatly related to our two races. There is certain to be some danger.”

The white-browed youth frowned and puzzlingly asked, “Since it is so important, why did they send Deity Transformation-grade cultivators? Wouldn’t it be safer to send out Spatial Tempering cultivators?”

The blood-marked youth didn’t immediately reply. Instead, he looked at Xiao Hong with a mysterious smile. “Since he’s asking questions, it seems your esteemed self should be in charge of him.”

The white-robed young woman calmly said, “Since Brother Long is aware of this, it seems you must be in charge of the human side.”

The blood mark on the Long Dong’s mouth stirred and he vaguely answered, “That’s right, I do know a few things.”

When the white-robed woman heard this, she curled her lips and turned to look at Han Li.

Han Li remained expressionless as if he hadn’t heard their conversation. This caused her to look at him with surprise.

Xiao Hong turned to the white-browed youth and explained, “They’ve sent Deity Transformation cultivators like us because the Black Leaves Forest is already covered in the Heavenly Wood Dreamnet. If anybody above Deity Transformation-stage were to enter, it will immediately cause alarm.”

The white-brow youth nodded and suddenly looked at Han Li and Ye Yin with narrow eyes. “So it was like that, but even if Fellow Daoist Long might do, the other two are mid-Deity Transformation cultivators. Aren’t they lacking?”

“Brother Li, please feel at ease, the panel of elders sent both Young Lady Ye and Fellow Daoist Han. They naturally hold you in high esteem as well. They definitely won’t disappoint.” Long Dong chuckled.

The white-brow youth then sinister said, “Since you’re vouching for them, let’s leave that alone then. But if they become a burden, I will not save them.”

The white-browed man’s open disdain, finally caused the white-robed woman’s face to sink. “Your cultivation only exceeds mine by a single grade, yet you speak like you’re a Spatial Tempering cultivator.”

The white-browed youth replied with a cold laugh, “Once you’ve reached our stage, the difference is negligible.”

The white-robed woman felt anger. Just as she was thinking of a reply, Han Li interjected,

“Since Fellow Daoist Long and Fairy Xiao know more about this mission, why not have them give us the details first. When I received this mission, I was only given general details. I didn’t think I’d need to cooperate with others. If I had known that, I would’ve most likely not taken this mission,” Han Li said with an indifferent expression. He truly felt somewhat unhappy.

When he found there would be multiple people on this assignment, he knew it wouldn’t be simple and had doubts about it. But since the mission was important and he was given vague details about, it would forfeit the privilege of accepting a different mission if he backed out and would need to stay in Deep Heaven City for ten years.

As such, with nothing else keeping him, he had no choice but to take the mission as he needed to leave the city within several years.

As a result, he needed to gather at this location in a month’s time. When he saw there were only spirit realm natives instead of other ascended cultivators, he could only wryly laugh.

It appears this assignment’s complexity and danger was far beyond what he anticipated.

Didn’t Zhao Wugui mention that this mission would only be chosen by ascended cultivators. Could it be he took the wrong mission?

But before he set out, he was already given enough Earth Cleansing Pills and promised to finish his mission. This was the same as what Zhao Wugui had told him.

Han Li felt bewildered when he thought of this.

Long Dong smiled and said, “I’ll tell Brother Han and Lady Ye about the mission details on the way. The mission is time sensitive, so we should best set off.”

“Brother Long’s words are reasonable. We are short on time. Let’s head out and then give relevant information on the way.” Xiao Hong agreed.

The other two raised no objections.

Han Li paused and slowly nodded.

“Alright, there will be time to talk as we travel.”

The blood-marked youth amiably proposed, “In that case, for the sake of carefulness, everyone should take my spirit cloud boat. We won’t need to waste any magic power, only use a few spirit stones. The boat is also well hidden. We’ll encounter less troubles on the way.”

Chapter 1359: Undercurrents

A ball of faint white light floated out from the forest. It contained a longboat that stretched over sixty meters wide.

The boat was divided into two stories and seemed to be crafted entirely from fine jade. The boat was engraved with simple cloud designs. Gold and silver talisman characters also floated from its surface, producing an unordinary aura.

The jade boat shuddered. Suddenly, the silver and golden talisman characters exploded, turning into a white cloud that wrapped around the boat. The entire boat appeared like an unremarkable white cloud.

The huge cloud soon circled in the air and silently rushed off.

Although the cloud appeared to be gently flying through the air, it traveled at extreme speed, tearing through three hundred meters in an instant. Its speed was comparable to an ordinary Deity Transformation cultivator.

As Xiao Hong stood on top of the boat, she looked around and praised, “Not bad. Although a spirit boat suitable for travel can’t be considered rare, one this fast is a top-grade good. As expected for the Long Clan, an owner of a human auction house.”

Long Dong politely said, “Hehe, Fairy Xiao praises me too greatly. Your clan is one of the seven great demon clans. You must’ve seen every kind of treasure. My Spirit Cloud Boat’s speed can’t be more than acceptable in your eyes. However, the boat does have quite a space. There are at least a dozen rooms. Apart from one person needing to keep watch on the outside, everyone else can rest in a room. If it goes smoothly, we’ll arrive in half a year. With some cultivation, it’ll pass by quickly.”

Xiao Hong nodded, “That is good. We’ll take ten days turns keeping watch while the others can do as they wish on the boat. Everyone should select their rooms first.”

The others raised no objections and found a satisfactory room on the boat.

Since it was their place to rest and meditate, they placed down other restrictions in the room to protect them from prying eyes.

Then after a short discussion, the watch rotation was decided.

As it so happened, Han Li was the last position in the rotation. That gave him forty days before he had to keep watch.

With all of that arranged, Han Li didn’t chat more with the others and headed into his room instead.

The others had done the same, apart from Long Dong, who held the first watch.

With Long Dong alone on board, his lips twitched and he made his way to the front of the boat. He flipped his hand and produced a green mat.

He then sat down on it cross-legged.

The blood marked youth quietly muttered, “Half a year... I look forward to the day that arrives.” Then, he slowly closed his eyes and wore an odd smile on his face.

In a room ten meters wide, Xiao Hong and the white-browed youth took a seat across from each other.

“What? You’re saying that young girl Ye Ying possesses Heavenly Phoenix Blood and is a disciple of the True Spirit Noble Clan?” The youth said with an astonished face.

Xiao Hong solemnly said, “Why is Fellow Daoist Li so surprised. Your Dark Falcon Clan is also a rare species of bird. You must’ve felt something. As for our Black Phoenix Clan, although we are a side branch of the phoenix clan, the purity of our heavenly phoenix blood is far greater than what that girl possesses. But there is no doubt about the presence of phoenix blood in her body.”

The white-browed sighed and wore an odd expression, “So it was like that! When I first saw that girl, I felt ill at ease, like there was a slight sensation of fear, so I was somewhat at a loss when we entered the forest. So why did Fairy Xiao tell me this?”

“It’s just that if the girl has other true spirit blood on her, it would’ve been fine. But she has the Heavenly Phoenix Blood of the myriad bird king. Brother Li should understand what this means.” Xiao Hong sweetly smiled, but her eyes were ice cold.

The white-browed youth grew silent for a moment before letting out a cold laugh. “Of course I understand. But don’t forget how important the elders told us to treat this mission. If we let personal matters get in the way of the clan’s mission, then our lives are forfeit, regardless if we managed to acquire Heavenly Phoenix Blood.”

Xiao Hong chuckled, “When did I say I wanted to attack her before the mission was over. We’ll have to first make sure that the mission is completed. Then we’ll strike.”

“Strike after the mission is over? Oh, if it doesn’t affect the mission, that’ll be possible. But will the other two help her? Even if we take back the True Phoenix Blood, how will we divide it? The blood can’t be evenly divided.” The white-browed youth blinked and he shook his head.

Xiao Hong gritted her teeth and said, “The Heavenly Phoenix Blood is useful to us both, but its effects are more pronounced on those from the Black Phoenix Clan. How about this? If Brother Li helped me acquire the spirit blood, I am willing to reward him with three black flame pills. As for the other two, I have a plan to deal with them. Furthermore, the Black Leaves Forest wasn’t a safe area to begin with. They might not safely return.”

“Three Black Flame Pills? You aren’t joking?” The white-browed youth said with delight.

Xiao Hong wryly smiled and said, “I have some status in the Black Phoenix Clan. Although the pills are considered priceless, after many years, I’ve managed to accumulate enough ingredients for three. I planned on using them to enter Spatial Tempering stage.”

After a moment of thought, the youth frowned and said, “So it was like that. I’ll lend you a hand after the mission is over. However, the blood won’t be easy to take. Especially true blood from the true spirit noble clans. It will be difficult to acquire after they fused it into their human bodies.”

“Don’t worry, the Black Phoenix Clan have a particular method of extracting true blood. It had been well researched. I have an eighty percent chance at the very least.”

When the white-browed youth heard this, he nodded, “Since you are so confident, then fine.”

...

In the other room, the young white-robed woman Ye Ying clasped her hands with an incantation gesture. She was sitting cross-legged on the bed. There was a meter-wide azure halo slowly floating behind her head.

Upon closer inspection, the halo was perfectly round with foot-tall white flames flickered from its edges. There was also a hollow silhouette meditating at its center.

From its appearance through its radiance, it appeared similar to the woman, but was several times smaller. Its eyes were shut and its hand was held in an incantation gesture.

At an unknown time, the young woman’s mouth began to stir and an indistinct smile appeared on her face. At nearly the same time, the image in the halo wore a similar expression.

...

As Han Li paced in the secluded room, he wore an expressionless face and his eyes flickered as if he were lost in thought.

In the corner of the room, there were two small objects on the jade table.

There was a kitten sized leopard with its four legs lazily stretched out on the table next to the items.

Sitting on the small leopard’s head was a monkey only several inches tall. Black light lit up from its fur and it looked at Han Li with intelligent eyes.

Han Li suddenly stopped pacing and he flipped his hand to produce a white jade slip and a small bottle.

The bottle was simply decorated and had three ancient characters engraved on it. Under closer inspection, the words read Earth Cleansing Pill.

Han Li stroked the bottle with a finger and then sighed. In a flash of light, the bottle disappeared. All that remained was a jade slip.

The jade slip was something that was given to him by several mysterious cultivators before he left Deep Heaven City.

Han Li fiddled with the jade slip for a while before placing it against his forehead.

The jade slip continued a huge map, but it seemed to be mostly incomplete. The map’s lacking areas were shining with faint golden light.

Although he looked through it continuously, Han Li couldn't help but continue as if he was trying to find something inside it.

...

Countless kilometers away from Deep Heaven City, there was a hidden underground room where a monk and a Daoist sat across from each other next to a stone table.

The Daoist appeared over forty years old. He had big eyes, thick eyebrows, and faintly golden skin.

The monk appeared old and had a white beard that was a half-foot long. Wrinkles littered his face and his eyes were thin lines as if he couldn't open them.

“It is about time for them to meet together and head on their way.” The old man said weakly.

“Yes, but there is something that eludes me. Why did Brother Jin Yue suddenly changed from his original plan after he left seclusion? Why did you send those Juniors to a foreign land?

Those people were supposed to be the most outstanding of the newly ascended cultivators. You should clearly understand that the mission to receive intelligence from the foreign land may seem simple, but it is truly dangerous. The demon clans would send equivalent people, but in truth, they seem to have other plans.” The Daoist priest spoke with a puzzled face.

“The various races have become restless. You should know this.” The old monk said.

When the Daoist Priest heard the old monk, his heart trembled and he wore a solemn expression. “Of course. But there is a newly appeared profound heavenly treasure that is listed on the chaotic myriad spirit roll. Furthermore, it is a profound heavenly tr easure that ranks in the top three. The Profound Heavenly Spiritslash Sword !”

Chapter 1365: Instigation

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Long; we all value our lives, so we won't do anything reckless," the white-browed young man chuckled.

"Do any of you have a plan?" Long Dong asked.

"I can conceal myself and launch sneak attacks against both the lizard and the giant down below. That way, they'll think that they've been attacked by the other," the white-browed young man immediately proposed.

"That's quite a simple plan, but we don't know how powerful the spiritual sense of those two beings are. If your concealment technique is seen through, you'll be in immense danger. I don't think that's a very safe course of action," Xiao Hong said with a shake of her head.

"In terms of concealment techniques, I have two Limpidity Talismans that can allow one to escape detection from mid-Spatial Tempering cultivators and below. I'd be willing to contribute them to this cause," Ye Ying offered with a faint smile.

"Limpidity Talismans? That's a type of beveled silver spirit talisman; they should definitely be effective against these two creatures, but just to be safe, I don't think it would be wise for us to attack them in person."

"I have two silver wyrm puppets, each of which possesses Nascent Soul Stage power. We can plaster the talismans onto them and get them to attack in our stead. That would make things a lot safer for us," Long Dong proposed with an ecstatic expression.

"That would be great! Even if the puppets fail to pit them against one another, we can split up into groups of two to lure the creatures away, then leave one of us who's proficient in both movement and concealment techniques to take advantage of that opportunity and secure the spirit fruits. Once the spirit fruits have been obtained, all of use will unleash secret techniques to get away from here. These two may possess Spatial Tempering Stage power, but if we're intent on escaping, they won't be able to stop us. It's just that the one who's assigned the duty of securing the fruits must possess an extremely fast movement technique. Otherwise, the speed at which that mutated lizard can blast out its tongue will pose quite a major threat," Xiao Hong mused.

"Indeed, Fairy Xiao. The one to secure the fruits will be incurring a massive risk," the white-browed young man said with furrowed brows.

"That will indeed be a dangerous undertaking. Which of us would be willing to volunteer for such a task? Furthermore, we have to gather together once again after the fruits have been secured, so that fellow Daoist will have to do something to convince us that they'll rejoin the rest of the group," Ye Ying said in a slow and methodical voice.

Peculiar expressions appeared on everyone's faces upon hearing this.

It was just as she had said; regardless of which one of them secured the Zoysia Dragon Fruits in the end, they would most likely be attacked by both of the Spatial Tempering Stage beings down below at once, thereby plunging them into great danger. On top of that, how could everyone else ensure that that individual wouldn't simply take the fruits and run away on their own?

With these considerations in mind, no one knew how to proceed.

"If all of you think I'm up to the task, I'm willing to volunteer to be the one to secure the fruits," Han Li offered with a smile.

"Fellow Daoist Han, you're only at the mid-Deity Transformation Stage; isn't that too dangerous a task for you?" Long Dong asked.

"Indeed, Brother Han; your cultivation base is slightly lacking." The white-browed young man also shook his head as he appraised Han Li.

"My cultivation base is indeed slightly below par, but I possess a top-grade teleportation treasure that's very close to a spirit treasure. Additionally, the cultivation arts I'm using are quite special, so I have confidence in my ability to ensure self-preservation," Han Li replied with a nonchalant smile.

Long Dong adopted a serious expression as he continued, "Seeing as Brother Han is so confident, we can certainly assign this task to you. However, how are you going to convince us that you won't run away on your own after securing the spirit fruits?"

"I'm afraid I don't have any good ideas in that respect. Of course, if any of you think you'd be more suited for the task, feel free to step forward and replace me; it doesn't really matter to me either way," Han Li said with a hint of a smile on his face.

Everyone else faltered upon hearing this.

Even though all of them wanted to secure the spirit fruits, no one wanted to be the one to incur the wrath of those two Spatial Tempering Stage beings. If any mishaps were to occur, they could end up with severe wounds or even dead.

"If Brother Han is willing to let me place a restriction on your body, then I have no objections," Ye Ying proposed in a straightforward manner.

"My thoughts exactly!" Xiao Hong chimed in.

Long Dong and the white-browed young man glanced at one another, but neither of them said anything. "Of course you can place restrictions on my body, but that's only if I'm also able to place the same restrictions on your bodies," Han Li retorted with a cold smile.

"Hmph, in that case, if you were to encounter some kind of mishap, wouldn't we have to die with you?" the white-browed young man harrumphed coldly.

"Hehe, that's the whole point," Han Li replied in a brusque manner. In reality, even if the other four were to agree to his condition, he most likely wouldn't be willing to accept such an arrangement.

He was still quite traumatized by the aftermath of the restriction that the Ice Phoenix had placed on him, so he certainly wasn't going to let history repeat itself.

Long Dong and the others glanced at one another with wry smiles upon hearing Han Li's words.

"How about this? We can trust you if you can leave behind your bonded treasure, then allow us to plant a tracking mark on you. That way, we won't have to worry about you running away with the spirit fruits," Ye Ying proposed as an alternative.

Han Li finally nodded after a period of contemplation. "I can accept that, but all of us have to be implanted with tracking marks so I can monitor everyone's locations as well. Hehe, perhaps I won't even need to take this risk if Brother Long's puppets can prove to be effective."

Long Dong and the others all looked at one another before finally agreeing to Han Li's proposal. Planting tracking marks on everyone appeared to be the only feasible method here.

Of course, as a mid-Deity Transformation cultivator, Han Li appeared to be the weakest in the group, so no one was actually afraid that he'd be able to take the treasures; all of this was merely being done as a precautionary measure.

After ascertaining some of the finer details, everyone finally settled on a specific course of action.

Han Li opened his mouth to expel four streaks of golden light, each of which was several inches in length. The streaks of light revolved around him before transforming into four shimmering golden swords that fell into the hands of his four companions.

Long Dong and the others immediately unleashed secret techniques or plastered talismans onto these swords to restrict them, then stowed them away into their respective storage treasures.

After that, four balls of light of different colors emerged from their fingertips before disappearing into Han Li's body in a flash.

Han Li had used his spiritual sense in advance to carefully assess these balls of light, only allowing them to enter his body after ascertaining that they were indeed formed by pure spiritual power and weren't harboring any restrictions.

Han Li also returned the favor thereafter, sending four balls of azure light disappearing into everyone else's bodies.

As such, everyone was feeling a lot more reassured.

After going over the plan one final time, all of them dispersed and flew away in different directions.

The azure streak of light that Han Li had transformed into flew for over 500 kilometers before his body was revealed again.

He hovered in mid-air as he briefly surveyed his surroundings. He then closed his eyes and slowly released his spiritual sense.

After ascertaining that there wasn't anything amiss in the nearby area, he opened his eyes again before making a hand seal.

A thunderclap immediately rang out behind him as a pair of azure and white wings surfaced on his back. He then flipped his hand over to produce a purple talisman; it was none other than his High Zenith Invisibility Talisman.

He was trying to secure a treasure right under the noses of two Spatial Tempering Stage beings, so he didn't dare to get complacent at all, which was why he decided to use this talisman right away.

He plastered the talisman onto his own body, following which he disappeared on the spot amid a flash of purple light and silver runes.

Having done all that, he rose into the air and set off to return to his former location.

Even though he wasn't able to fly as quickly as he could before activating the talisman, he was still certainly not flying slowly, and it didn't take him long to return to his original spot.

The giant lizard and the Thousand-Eyed Giant were still caught in a tense confrontation down below.

Everyone else had also disappeared as far as the naked eye was concerned.

Han Li exhaled as he used his spiritual sense to detect the locations indicated by the tracking marks he'd left on his four companions.

Everyone else returned as a result and hovered in mid-air in the nearby area.

There were two in the air above the giant lizard while the other two were situated behind the Thousand-Eyed Giant.

They were also all using some special concealment techniques, and there would've been no way for Han Li to ascertain their locations with his spiritual sense if it weren't for the tracking marks that had been planted. As for the two silver wyrm puppets that Long Dong had been referring to earlier, Han Li was completely unable to sense them.

He didn't know whether this was due to the effect of the Limpidity Talismans or if they hadn't actually been released yet.

Countless thoughts were whizzing through Han Li's mind, but his gaze remained fixed directly down below.

Everything in the surrounding area was abnormally quiet, akin to the calm before the storm. This peculiar and rather strained atmosphere persisted for a long while, yet nothing changed at all.

Han Li remained completely expressionless, but he was starting to get a little impatient. It seemed that the time they had agreed on was about to arrive soon as well.

Right at this moment, the giant lizard seemed to have felt a sense of discomfort with one of its giant paws, causing it to raise it reflexively before immediately bringing it down again.

However, right in the instant when it brought its paw down, silver light suddenly flashed from the soil beneath the paw, following which a silver thread shot forth, hurtling directly toward the Thousand-Eyed Giant.

This created the illusion that the lizard was using its paw to launch a sneak attack.

The giant faltered upon seeing this before letting loose a thunderous roar of rage. Gale-force winds were swept up around its body as it swept a palm through the air, violently vanquishing the oncoming silver thread.

However, almost at the exact same moment, a blurry and indistinct object flashed through the air beneath the giant's hand. Immediately thereafter, a pillar of silver light that was as thick as a bowl shot forth out of thin air, traveling at an incredible speed and reaching the lizard's massive head in an instant.

The lizard's green eyes flashed as a crimson pillar of light erupted from its twin horns.

Following a resounding boom, the two pillars of light clashed, and both disappeared into nothingness.

The lizard then immediately threw back its head and let loose an earth-shattering roar. It tensed its four limbs and its massive body immediately rose up as it opened its cavernous mouth to reveal rows of intimidating fangs.

Chapter 1368: Small Town

Much to everyone's surprise, the final spirit fruit fell into the hands of Ye Ying .

The treasures she offered were more extravagant than everyone else could produce, so they could only reluctantly allow her to take the spirit fruit.

This small section of the Myriad Year Green Spirit Tree was Han Li's compensation of choice.

This piece of wood was as light as air and immune to the effects of water and fire. It was one of the most ideal materials for carving formation spells onto, and as it aged, it would develop a certain degree of immunity toward the power of the five elements.

As such, this type of wood was most often used to refine large treasures like spirit arks, beast carriages, and things of that nature.

After fiddling around with the section of wood for a while, Han Li stowed it away before glancing at his surroundings.

The flying carriage had been supplied, once again, by Long Dong, and even though it wasn't as comfortable nor as stealthy as the spirit ark that had been destroyed earlier, it was able to fly at a greater speed than the ark.

Speaking of which, the spirit ark's concealment ability would've been next to useless in the face of powerful ancient beasts. As such, this faster flying carriage was a superior option anyway.

If they were to encounter some minor hindrances, they could simply accelerate and shake them off.

At this moment, the flying carriage was whizzing through the air as an azure blur, hurtling along at an incredible speed.

Aside from Long Dong, who was piloting the carriage, everyone else was sitting in silence.

Han Li withdrew his gaze before suddenly turning his attention to Ye Ying, upon which his eyes narrowed slightly.

The person in the group whom he was most wary of and found to be the most mysterious was this woman, who appeared to possess the same cultivation base as he did.

This woman appeared to be quite young and spoke in a very simple and straightforward manner, but having completely mastered the Great Development Technique, Han Li's instinctive senses had already been honed to an incredibly sensitive degree, and those senses told him that this woman was the most dangerous one among the four, even more so than Long Dong from the so-called True Spirit Family.

Just as Han Li was contemplating these matters, Ye Ying suddenly opened her eyes and met Han Li's gaze.

Han Li's heart jolted upon seeing this, and before he had a chance to react, Ye Ying pursed her lips with a faint chuckle.

Han Li gave a rather awkward smile before immediately turning away. In doing so, he missed the hint of amusement that flashed through Ye Ying 's eyes in response.

During the following half a month, their journey was remarkably smooth, and they didn't encounter any trouble at all.

Everyone was quite relieved by this peaceful spell, praying that the rest of their journey would be just as smooth and placid.

Several days later, the scenery around them transformed as a vast expanse of desert appeared before them, sending gusts of scorching wind sweeping toward their carriage.

A hint of a surprise appeared on the white-browed young man's face as he mused, "Could it be that we've already reached the Southern Skyline?"

"Indeed, this place is the Great Southern Desert, and it's the simplest path through which one can reach the territory of the Wood Tribe," Long Dong replied in a grave voice.

"I've heard many things about this place. The legends say that it's impossible to go around this desert; is that really true? There are often Wood Tribe and Shadow Tribe beings traveling through this desert; isn't it still a little too dangerous for us to go directly through it?" Xiao Hong asked with a frown on her face.

"Fairy Xiao, the environment here certainly isn't the best, but it's much safer than the other two alternative routes we can take. As for going around the desert, that would be next to impossible. On one side of the desert is the renowned Zenith Beast Mountain Ranges, which is teeming with countless high-grade ancient beasts. Even most of the Spatial Tempering cultivators who venture into those mountain ranges never return. On the other side is the even more treacherous Wyrm Abyss Canyon. There are over 100 vicious wyrms at or above the Spatial Tempering Stage lurking in there, including even several tens of Body Integration Stage Wyrm Monarchs. A few Deity Transformation cultivators like us would simply be offering ourselves up as food if we were to take either of those paths. As for skirting around even further to avoid those areas, that would lengthen our journey to an enormous degree, and it would most likely take us around a year or so to get to our destination. The war is imminent, so there's no way that Deep Heaven City would allow us to delay the completion of our mission for so long," Long Dong explained with a wry smile.

"I see. However, I've heard that this desert seems to be a trial ground for the two tribes," Ye Ying suddenly interjected.

"My seniors also cautioned me about this before my departure." The white-browed young man had also adopted a rather cautious stance.

"In that case, I don't think we should continue traveling on this flying carriage; we'd stick out like a sore thumb. Let's all conceal ourselves before continuing onward. Even if everything goes as smoothly as possible, it'd still take us around a month to pass through this desert," Long Dong suggested after a brief period of contemplation.

Xiao Hong contemplated the notion before exchanging a glance with the white-browed young man, following which she nodded, and agreed, "We'll do as you say."

"I have no objections, either; traveling on the flying carriage really will make us stand out far too much for comfort," Han Li said with a smile.

Ye Ying was the only one who expressed a neutral stance, willing to comply with the most popular course of action.

Thus, after a brief discussion, everyone emerged from the flying carriage before unleashing concealment techniques to obscure themselves. Long Dong stowed the flying carriage away, and everyone ventured carefully into the desert.

Not long after entering the desert, Han Li immediately sensed that this desert was unlike any that he'd ever seen, in that the temperatures here were simply far too high.

Even while flying at low altitudes in the air, he could still feel the bursts of scorching heat emanating from the ground. He felt as if he were flying over a massive volcanic crater rather than a desert.

Han Li looked up at the seven scintillating suns in the sky above, then down at the ground below. He swiped a hand through the air, sending an ice spike hurtling downward.

Prior to even making contact with the ground, the ice spike had already completely melted and evaporated into nothingness.

Han Li heaved a faint sigh upon seeing this.

All of a sudden, white light flashed beside him, and Ye Ying appeared with a dainty smile on her face. "Fellow Daoist Han, I'm not sure if you're aware of this, but the Great Southern Desert once consisted of a vast expanse of volcanic craters."

"Is that so? I didn't know that," Han Li replied in an indifferent voice.

"It was said that a heavenly phoenix, which possessed dual wind and earth-attribute powers, once battled a True Spirit level Fire Crocodile that inhabited the volcanoes down below. Their battle raged for over a month, and during that process, the phoenix used its abilities to conjure up countless sandstorms, burying all of the volcanoes down below and forming this desert," Ye Ying continued.

"I see. No wonder this desert is so peculiar. True Spirit level beings really are capable of unfathomable feats," Han Li murmured, seemingly in response to Ye Ying , but also seemingly to himself.

"Indeed. Human cultivators like us may be able to combat some of these True Spirit level beings once we reach the Grand Ascension Stage, but we're still no match for the truly powerful beings at the True Spirit level, such as true dragons and heavenly phoenixes. I wonder what it would be like for a human to attain True Spirit level power," Ye Ying chuckled before flying onward, leaving Han Li behind.

A hint of surprise appeared on Han Li's face as he looked on at her departing figure, but he quickly recomposed himself and focused on forging ahead in his journey.

Over 10 days later, Han Li and the others were still flying along at low altitudes. Even though they were all Deity Transformation cultivators, flying for so long under such scorching heat was making them rather exhausted.

"Let's find a place to rest after a further half a day of travel," Long Dong suddenly proposed.

"We do indeed need to find a place to rest and recover our magic power," Xiao Hong replied with a nod, and the weariness in her voice was quite apparent.

"Huh? What's that?" A low cry of surprise suddenly sounded.

The one who had spoken was none other than the white-browed young man.

Han Li reflexively cast his gaze toward the direction that the young man's attention was focused. However, he discovered that there was nothing there.

Han Li raised his eyebrows as he swept his immense spiritual sense toward that area, upon which a peculiar look appeared on his face.

At this point, everyone else had also scanned through the area with their spiritual sense, and all of them also adopted peculiar expressions.

"Looks like there's a small town there, which is inhabited by humans. I'm not seeing things, am I?" Han Li mused in a skeptical manner.

After releasing their spiritual sense, everyone discovered that there was a relatively large oasis situated up ahead several tens of kilometers away. Within that oasis was a small town, and it appeared that there were many humans and cultivators living there.

"This place is so secluded and it's so close to foreign races; how could there truly be humans living here? Something seems a little fishy here," Xiao Hong mused.

An indecisive look appeared on Long Dong's face, and he raised his eyebrows, but refrained from immediately offering a response.

"Let me send over an avatar to investigate," the white-browed young man offered.

He then laid a hand on the back of his head, and a silhouette flashed as a small falcon that was around a foot in size emerged. The falcon was entirely black in color, and it circled through the air before flying toward the small town in the distance.

The white-browed young man then closed his eyes to forge a connection with the small falcon with his spiritual sense in case any mishaps arose.

Xiao Hong and Long Dong exchanged a glance with one another, but they seemed to also be of the opinion that this was the best course of action, as evidenced by the fact that both of them refrained from stopping the white-browed young man in what he was doing.

Han Li continued to appraise the small town in the distance with befuddlement in his heart.

Ye Ying was also doing the same with an intrigued look on her face.

The small falcon flew extremely quickly, and it was back within five minutes.

When the falcon disappeared into the back of the white-browed young man's head again, the latter opened his eyes. "There's no mistaking it; there really are humans inhabiting that small town, and there are many high-grade cultivators among them. There are seven or eight Deity Transformation cultivators, but I didn't see any Spatial Tempering cultivators."

Everyone was even more perplexed upon hearing this.

"In any case, it would be best to continue in our journey and avoid any unnecessary trouble," Han Li said in an indifferent voice.

"I don't think that's a good idea. The existence of this small town is really peculiar; perhaps something happened recently in the desert. I think it would be best for us to inquire about the situation before continuing onward in case we inadvertently plunge headfirst into peril," Long Dong said with a shake of his head.

Chapter 1376: The Wood Tribe

From a distance, the hill looked ordinary as if there were no changes to it at all, but it was actually just an illusion.

Han Li was standing on the hill, right in front of the half-charred ancient tree.

When Han Li looked at it, he recalled what Long Dong and Xiao Hong had mentioned.

According to what they said, if it was possible, they could meet a spy planted by the humans and demons and receive information that was difficult to record. But if it was too dangerous, and they personally couldn't make the trip, the spy could be disregarded.

Now that he swept his spiritual sense past the area, it appeared that no one had come.

In this case, the assignment was actually quite simple. So long as he removes the item, the mission will be considered complete for him.

With that decided, Han Li extended his finger and swiped it at the ancient tree.

A crackle sounded and an azure sword streak shot forward, cleaving the tree into two.

It contained a white jade slip there.

Han Li’s face lit up with joy and he reached out for it, summoning it into his hand.

At that moment, a muffled sound traveled through the air. A golden light suddenly pierced through the illusion, directly shooting towards the jade slip.

Han Li’s face slightly changed. Without another thought, azure light flashed from his hand. A hand of azure light appeared in the air and swiped at the golden light.

A sweet giggle sounded from the golden light. It broke through the azure hand like it was an illusion. The jade slip that was flying in Han Li’s direction stopped and a faint white blur appeared to the side. She raised her hand and nimble took the jade slip.

“Fellow Daoist Ye!” Han Li narrowed his eyes, recognizing the true figure wrapped in white light. It was Ye Ying, the young white-robed woman.

“Brother Han. It appears you’ve arrived here smoothly and easily.” The young woman flipped the jade slip in her hand and chuckled.

“What do you mean? Did Fairy Ye encounter trouble on her way here? When I left the Southern Skyline and arrived at the edge of the forest, I waited for you all for a while and I received no messages. What happened to you?” Han Li asked with an odd expression.

“It’s quite simple. Fellow Daoist Long and I encountered a group of wind wyrms in the skyline. We had no choice but to split off. To escape them, we had no choice but to change direction. There were a few other problems along the way. That is why you didn’t see us.” The young woman sweetly smiled with significant grace.

Han Li felt his heart tremble. He faintly made out something from her words.

Just as he was about to ask her something, a green light flashed from the sky and charged towards them. The light faded away to reveal a man and a woman.

They were Long Dong and Xiao Hong.

“It’s you!”

“As expected, you arrived here first!”

The two spoke with a tone of surprise.

When Xiao Hong saw Han Li’s unharmed appearance, she revealed a trace of surprise, but when Long Dong saw the white-robed woman, he revealed joy.

The white-robed woman looked at the two and casually said, “So it was Brother Long and Fellow Daoist Ye. I wasn’t fast, you were just slow.”

“Did Lady Ye already grab ahold of the item?” Long Dong glanced at the young woman’s hand and wore a mysterious smile.

Xiao Hong glanced at the jade slip in the white-robed woman’s hand and her expression faintly changed.

The young woman let out a bright laugh and leisurely said, “That’s right. I have it in my hand. In truth, Fellow Daoist Han came here first, but I was still a step ahead of you two.”

Xiao Hong paused for a second and suddenly asked, “Brother Han, was there only one jade slip here?”

Han Li’s heart stirred, but he nodded with a calm expression.

Xiao Hong fell silent upon hearing Han Li’s answer; Long Dong looked at the white-robed woman silently; and the white-robed woman simply looked down while fiddling with the jade slip in her hand.

For a time, silence filled the air. The heavy atmosphere was an omen for a coming storm.

Xiao Hong’s expression relaxed and she wore a pleasant face. She asked, “Junior Sister Ye, could you let me take a look at the jade slip? The spies we sent to the wood tribe included those from my clan. Perhaps they have some information for my clan.”

The white-robed woman pursed her lips and then sweetly smiled, “I’m afraid I can’t. I’ll be open and say that the spies had people from my Ye Clan as well. Why don’t I take a look at it first and then tell you about it?”

Xiao Hong’s expression vastly changed and her smile froze. Her gaze became sullen.

Long Dong calmly said, “Since you already have it, we shouldn’t stay here for much longer. Let’s hurry away and talk about it when we leave the forest.”

“I agree.” The white-robed woman said.

Xiao Hong’s lip stirred but she raised no objections.

Han Li naturally agreed as well. The young woman smiled and her bright eyes flickered around. Just as she was about to put away the jade slip, a silver streak shot out of the ancient tree behind her. It quickly and silently streaked towards the center of her back.

Although the white-robed woman was faced around, she snorted and her body stirred. Her body grew vague and she disappeared.

A moment later, she appeared over thirty meters away, but there was a silver streak that shot then shot up from the ground.

This time, the young woman’s expression faintly changed.

Her shoulder suddenly blurred and she shot ten meters to the side as if there were a spring underneath her, allowing her to avoid the attack.

But at that moment, the sound of tearing air blew past her.

A near indistinct line of transparent line shot out of a sprace nearby her. The target wasn’t the young woman, but the jade slip in her hand.

Alarmed, the young woman suddenly pulled back her hand, but she was too late.

Bang! The jade slip immediately ruptured, turning into countless shards. In the young woman’s fury, her face warped and she grabbed ahold of the transparent line and fiercely pulled it towards her.

Clang. She dragged out a huge transparent beetle out from the void.

This insect was a meter-long and resembled a huge silkworm, but there were a pair of cicada wings on its back. It fluttered for its life to break free. The end of it that spouted out the thread seemed to be its mouth.

At that moment, the young woman pulled, keeping the insect there.

In the instant the jade slip was destroyed, Han Li and the others were blank in surprise.

At nearly the same time, the remaining ancient trees lit up in green light. Soon after, the ancient tree’s hollow images were dissolved to be replaced with several green silhouettes. It appeared as if they were born from the trees.

A towering silhouette swept their gaze past Han Li and spoke human words in a harsh tone, “Hehe, I didn’t expect that it was hidden there. If you weren’t guiding us, we wouldn’t have found it. Our clan won’t have to worry about later consequences.”

Han Li glanced at the figure’s appearance and his eyes narrowed.

The person resembled a human, but their skin was green and their eyes were purple. Other than that, they appeared human. Two of the slender figures resembled women.

These silhouettes were wood tribe beings.

What was most astonishing to Han Li was the orange belt they wore at their waist around their long robes.

The belt of the towering being was yellow orange with a silver stripe.

According to what he knew of their grades, Han Li felt his heart plummet.

“A silver tier! You’re a silver tier tree spirit!” When they recognized the towering figure’s belt, the young woman’s expression turned unsightly.

“I am the lower silver tier spirit master Mu Rui. Since you’ve arrived here, there is no need to leave. Allow my clan to welcome you!” The towering figure spoke expressionlessly and waved his hand.

The other orange belted tree beings crouched down and placed their hands against the ground.

A layer of green light suddenly shot out from the hill in every direction at inconceivable speeds.

Han Li and the white-robed woman immediately took off from the ground without another thought.

A huge rumbling sound shook the air and the illusion restriction Han Li placed down was effortlessly destroyed.

Once the illusion was dispersed, the hill’s surroundings were made clear.

Wherever the green light passed, green trees would turn into towering furred beasts. They had a variety of weapons on hand. Their fur had many differing colors as well. There were even monstrous winds that blew into the sky.

Upon closer inspection, there were several thousands of beasts that densely surrounded the hill.

Long Dong and Xiao Hong’s face turned bloodlessly pale.

Han Li wryly smiled. Only the white-robed woman sullenly glared at Mu Rui. It was unknown what she was thinking.

Mu Rui wore a stiff expression, but he spoke with a derisive tone, “These are the Tree Ape Beasts that our tribe spent a thousand years researching. If you looked through that jade slip, you should’ve had information about them, but now...”

“Attack!”

An unfamiliar voice suddenly sounded. Before Han Li and the others realized what was happening, the white-robed young woman suddenly opened her mouth and released a crimson blood light. Suddenly, it turned into several threads and directly shot towards the wood spirits excluding the silver-tier wood spirit.

Chapter 1379: Wood Phoenix

The Leopard Kirin Beast shut its green eyes for a while before opening them again. It then let out a soft growl.

Han Li smiled.

Ever since he acquired the small beast, he discovered in addition to its quick speed and durable body, it also had extraordinary tracking abilities.

So long as the beast sensed something, no matter if the target was alive, dead, or behind a myriad of restrictions, it could find the item accurately.

This kind of tracking doesn’t merely use the physical senses; it was an inconceivable ability related to spiritual sense.

At the very least, the beast was able to track Han Li down while he used the High Zenith Invisibility Talisman and stood still.

As for the spell plate and the speck of white light, it was obviously linked to the young white-robed woman. He also had a speck of pure spiritual Qi for the other cultivators as well.

The small beast looked all around and tilted its head as if in thought. Soon, it stirred and shot off into a faint yellow blur.

Han Li didn’t immediately chase after it. Instead, he formed an incantation gesture and suddenly struck an azure light at the ground.

As a result, a faint ring sounded from the ground. A ball of silver flame suddenly burst from the ground. A faint flame raven fluttered around it.

Originally inside Black Leaves Forest, he had concealed a Spirit Engulfing Flame raven in the ground.

For the sake of carefulness, when Han Li escaped, he hadn’t taken back the flame. Fortunately, the flame was already completely refined. Even at the speed he was traveling, he was still able to command it to follow him.

Of course, the flame raven wasn’t a true spirit beast. It needed to use a bit of magic power to maintain its shape. However, it was such a little amount to his current cultivation that he didn’t mind.

When he saw there was no problem with his flame raven, Han Li nodded. Then he pointed and the bird disappeared into the ground.

It was still quite dangerous there. He may as well keep it prepared just in case.

With that done, Han Li summoned light around himself and flew off in an azure streak. With a few blinks, he quickly chased after the Leopard Kirin Beast.

The small beast was heading north. After a long while, it eventually changed direction.

Han Li was startled, but he kept silent and changed direction with it.

Afterwards, the Leopard Kirin Beast changed directions several more times.

This caused Han Li’s face to turn solemn.

This illustrated that the white-robed woman, Ye Ying, was continuously shifting movements, likely because she was still being pursued. She wouldn’t have sharply changed direction so many times if this were not the case.

However, this wouldn’t stop him.

With his current abilities, so long as he wasn’t heavily surrounded or faced an opponent with vastly superior cultivation, he was confident he’d be able to preserve his life.

As he needed this woman to acquire his Earth Cleansing Pills, he couldn't leave her alone.

Expressionless, Han Li closely followed the Leopard Kirin and chased after it like azure lightning.

The chase continued for three entire days, but Han Li had yet to catch sight of her.

But on the morning of the fourth day, he arrived at the edge of vast blue waters with no end in sight. The Leopard Kirin Beast suddenly stopped.

With roused spirits, Han Li arrived at the beast’s side in a flash of azure light.

The beast turned its raggy head and softly whimpered as if it were trying to say something.

If it were anyone else, they wouldn’t be able to understand, but Han Li happily said, “You mean they aren’t far away? We’ve arrived? You can have this. Go ahead and return.”

Han Li flicked his finger and tossed another scarlet medicine pill.

The small beast blurred with delight and caught the medicine pill in midair. It spat out a white speck of light and flew back into Han Li’s sleeve in a chain of afterimages.

Han Li flipped his hand and took out a spell plate, absorbing back the white speck. Then, light flashed from his hand and he summoned a High Zenith Invisibility Talisman.

When Han Li saw its dim light, he frowned and hesitated. He then summoned an identical talisman with a flip of his hand.

However, the purple talisman he produced was brimming with dazzling light.

For his trip into the wilderness, he spent great effort to refine an additional two High Zenith Invisibility Talismans.

He had already spent most of the power of the first talisman. For the sake of carefulness in the face of unknown danger, Han Li had best used the fresh talisman.

After putting away the dim talisman, his new talisman blurred and silver characters flashed. His body disappeared.

Soon after, he formed an incantation gesture and his body blurred. He easily flew in the direction that the Leopard Kirin pointed at.

It was unknown if the water belonged to a huge lake, or if it were the edge of a sea. After he flew for over six hundred kilometers, he didn’t spot any land. He did eventually come across a small unremarkable island.

The island was five kilometers long and was dense with vegetation. It appeared to be entirely uninhabited.

Han Li glanced at the island and then raised his head, looking around. He quietly flew towards the center of the island.

According to what the Leopard Kirin said, it should be the island.

There was a small basin at the heart of the island with a few grey-white stones stacked on top of one another.

A white-robed young woman with a pale complexion sat on a huge stone cross-legged. There was a wood tribe woman respectfully standing at attention in front of her.

When Han Li saw this, he was alarmed and he came to a sudden stop. He examined the unfamiliar woman with narrow eyes.

The woman’s flesh was exactly the same as a common wood spirit, a shallow green. Also, she wore an orange-yellow belt, revealing herself to be a tree spirit at Spatial Tempering stage. But under closer examination, Han Li discovered the woman appeared much different compared to an ordinary wood spirit.

When the tree spirit faced the white-robed woman, she wore a dignified and respectful expression different from the wooden expressions of other wood spirits. Furthermore, Han Li was able to sense a vastly powerful fire spiritual power from the woman’s body, despite not releasing his spiritual sense. Only pure wood spiritual Qi should be present in a wood tribe being.

This person wasn’t a wood spirit!

Han Li quickly came to this conclusion. Afterwards, he looked at the young woman.

He discovered in addition to the young woman’s deathly pale complexion, there was a fist-sized bloodstain on the young woman’s chest. It was as if a blood flower had blossomed, a clear indication of a wound.

When he saw this, Han Li hesitated, considering whether he should reveal himself.

At that moment, the young woman raised her head and smiled at him. “Brother Han, since you’re here, how about you join me and rest?”

Han Li felt deeply shocked when he heard this.

How was it possible for her to see through his invisibility.

The High Zenith Invisibility Talisman might not be effective against Body Integration-stage cultivators, but it could definitely hide him from Spatial Tempering-stage individuals. Could it be the woman was pretending? But the woman smiled in his direction, clearly showing his position.

The only explanation he could think of was that she had a spiritual sense equivalent to a Body Integration cultivator.

Han Li felt bewildered. After some thought, silver talisman characters flickered from his body and his body slowly came into view.

Soon after, he slapped his body and summoned a purple talisman into the air and then his hand.

With a calm appearance, Han Li descended to the ground.“Fellow Daoist Ye, who is this Fellow Daoist? Could you introduce me to her?”

“Sure. This is the spy that the humans and demons placed in the wood tribe, Fellow Daoist Ye Chu. It appears Fellow Daoist had escaped the wood tribe’s pursuit.” The young woman said with a smile. She then examined Han Li with a smile. When she saw that Han Li was in good health, she couldn't help but betray her surprise.

“Ye Chu? Is she a human or a demon?” Han Li glanced at the green-skinned woman and narrowed his eyes.

The woman calmly glanced at Han Li and said, “Your eyes are quite sharp. I am a human, but my body possesses Wood Phoenix Spirit Blood. I can be considered half-demon.” Her voice was somewhat hoarse.

“A Wood Phoenix? Yi! You have Spatial Tempering cultivation!” When he heard her name, he swept his spiritual sense past her and his face changed.

Ye Ying answered with bright eyes, “Older Sister Chu comes from our Ye Clan. She possessed early Spatial Tempering cultivation when she was sent to spy on the wood tribe. After many years had passed, she has completed the cycle of Spatial Tempering and is bordering the Body Integration stage.”

“This is thanks to a few benefits I acquired from the wood tribe, or else I wouldn’t have reached this stage. However, I didn’t expect that the young master would personally come here.” Ye Chu spoke with a modest tone and stood in front of the young woman with a helpless appearance.

Han Li felt a chill facing a person with such fearsome cultivation. With a respectful expression, he said, “So it was like that. If Senior hadn’t come to rescue us, I fear we would’ve been completely wiped out.”

“Let’s get to that later.” Ye Ying’s smile faded and her face turned serious, “Because I was chased too quickly, I have yet to ask what happened. Older Sister Chu, why did we fall into the wood tribe’s trap. Where are the others?”

The green-skinned woman answered, “Apart from me, all the others were killed. About a hundred years before, the wood tribe acquired information on our spies. It was only because of my Wood Phoenix blood that I was able to escape detection. The others were caught and tried to escape, but they were caught one by one.”

Chapter 1380: Mission Complete

The green-skinned woman continued her answer, “As for why you were ambushed, it was because the wood tribe’s higher echelon altered the scope of the Dream Sifting Tree’s detection. I fear they detected you as soon as you entered. Fortunately, the upper echelon of the wood tribe doesn’t view Black Leaves Forest with much importance. It only sent a single lower silver-tier wood spirit to oversee it. Otherwise, it would’ve been difficult for you to escape them.”

The young white-robed woman, Ye Ying, slowly said, “So it was like that! Older Sister Chu, these last thousand years must’ve been hard on you.”

“It’s nothing. These past few years in the wood tribe haven’t been spent in vain. I’ve grasped many of their secrets. I’ve even made connections in the tribe, but I am certain I am now exposed. I cannot continue to stay here.”

Han Li felt his heart stir.

Ye Ying smiled, “Deep Heaven City is possibly on the brink of another war. Even if nothing happens, the clan master plans on calling you back. With your current cultivation, there is no point in continuing to hide here.”

However, her smile seemed to provoke her injuries and she coughed several times, causing her face to turn paler.

“Is the young mistress alright? How about you take another Phoenix Spirit Pill?” Ye Chu proposed with a tense expression.

“No need! There aren’t many left. I’ll leave them for something else.” Ye Ying shook her head.

“What? Is Lady Ye heavily injured?” Han Li blinked.

Ye Ying curled her lip and unhappily said, “That silver-tier tree spirit landed a clean blow. Would you say the injury is grave?”

“If it is an ordinary internal injury, I have several medicine pills for that. Perhaps they’ll be useful.” Han Li said with a calm tone. He then waved his sleeve and summoned several medicine pills in her direction.

Ye Ying raised her brow. She reached out for the air and summoned them into her grasp. She then opened them and took a few whiffs.

Having some medicinal knowledge, she wore an astonished expression and immediately uttered their names, “Wondrous Grass Pill, Hundred Blessings Pill, Returning Spirit Water... Brother Han is quite generous to present these sacred medicines to me. In that case, I won’t hold back.”

With her status, Ye Ying could’ve prepared a few of them, but she felt disbelief that a Deity Transformation cultivator could take out so many of them in a single breath.

The young woman blinked and promptly opened the bottles, swallowing several of the pills, revealing her trust in Han Li.

Han Li felt some admiration for her decisive actions.

Of course, she most likely had some sort of secret technique, so she had no fear there was something wrong with the medicine pills.

After she swallowed the pills, color returned to Ye Ying’s face. Then, she glanced at Han Li and asked, “Ah yes, how did you find me? If I’m not mistaken, your invisibility talisman seems to be a silver rune talisman. Might I know its name? This is the first time I’ve seen such a high-grade silver rune talisman.”

“I have a bit of experience with tracking techniques. As for the talisman, it is called the High Zenith Invisibility Talisman. It is something I unintentionally came across. Its effects are truly marvelous. I was quite astonished when you were able to see through it. May I know how you did it? I fear even a Spatial Tempering cultivator would have trouble seeing through it.” Han Li smiled and returned her question with a question.

“I cultivate a technique that happens to penetrate most concealment techniques. It wasn’t odd that I could see through it. Brother Han need not take it to heart.” Ye Ying pursed her lips into a mysterious smile.

When Han Li heard this, he could only wryly laugh.

Although he knew her answer was false, it was difficult to continue asking her about it.

Ye Ying then said, “There is still another matter! Older Sister Chu, you should be carrying the information on the Wood Tribe. We should take advantage of this moment to send it over to Deep Heaven City in case of any surprises.”

“Yes, Young Mistress.” The green-skinned woman promptly replied.

Han Li wore a calm expression, but he felt slight.

Ye Ying reached for her storage bracelet and took out a sparkling silver square plate. The green-skinned woman then opened her mouth and spat out an emerald jade slip.

Han Li also possessed a plate. It could transport exquisite objects to Deep Heaven City. After a single use, the spell plate would be destroyed.

Since Ye Ying used her own teleportation plate, Han Li didn’t need to do anything else. According to the tool refinement masters of Deep Heaven City, it was something that had been recently developed. Otherwise, if Ye Chu originally brought one, Han Li and the others wouldn’t have needed to make the journey.

Ye Ying waved her hand and struck the spell plate with a white spell seal. Suddenly, it brightly shined white.

She then tossed the spell plate in front of her and it turned into a foot-large spell formation. It spun throughout the air and began to hum.

“Let’s be quick. Although it is only a small-scale spell formation, it can alert the Wood Tribe,” Ye Ying quickly said.

Ye Chu tossed the jade slip without another thought. When it landed inside the light formation, it floated in midair.

Ye Ying then struck the plate with another spell seal.

Silver talisman characters suddenly appeared from the spell formation and it roiled. The jade slip then disappeared with a clear ring.

Soon after, the light formation vanished and the silver plate returned to normal.

However, the plate’s engravings had completely disappeared and the plate was thoroughly cracked.

Han Li felt joy and he flipped his hand to produce an azure jade talisman. He stared at it with complete attention.

It was the Myriad Distance Talisman that Deep Heaven City’s higher echelon had given him before he set off for the mission.

Ye Ying smiled when she saw this and put away the destroyed plate. Then she took out her own Myriad Distance Talisman and attentively looked at it.

Ye Chu remained expressionless and stood still.

For a time, silence filled the air.

When the time it took to finish a cup of tea had passed, Han Li’s and Ye Ying’s Myriad Distance Talismans brightly shined and they released a string of talisman characters.

Han Li’s heart fluttered as he committed each of the characters to memory.

The characters densely covered the entire jade talisman. Then, light withdrew and the jade slip turned dim once more.

At that moment, Han Li smiled.

What Deep Heaven City had sent over was clearly the method to dissolve the restriction on his bottle of Earth Cleansing Pills. It appeared the city had recognized that their mission was completed and that they were granted freedom.

Feeling ecstatic, Han Li turned his sights on Ye Ying.

When the woman stared at her Myriad Distance Talisman, her lips curled, clearly satisfied with the contents of what was displayed.

Han Li’s heart stirred.

The woman didn’t need Earth Cleansing Pills. It was unknown what the city’s higher echelons pledged to her to make her brave this danger.

The young woman finally looked through the contents of the jade talisman and she put it away. She then giggled at Han Li and said, “What? Brother Han should’ve acquired what he wanted as well.”

“That’s right,” Han Li replied with a smile.

The young woman said with a deep tone, “In that case, let’s hurry away. Even if you have other plans, you can’t possibly want to stay in the Wood Tribe’s territory either.”

Han Li stared at the young woman for a long while and slowly nodded.

When she saw Han Li’s answer, she felt happy and gave the green-skinned woman a command.

Ye Chu acknowledged her and released a treasure from her hand.

It was a foot-long yellow wooden bird puppet.

Ye Chu cast a spell seal and the bird rose into the air. Meanwhile, light quickly radiated from it. In the blink of an eye, it turned over forty meters wide.

It appeared vivid and true to life.

Ye Ying and Ye Chu wordlessly jumped on top of it. With some brief surprise, Han Li followed after them.

Ye Chu shouted a command and the bird’s huge wings unfolded, instantly surrounding them in a ball of yellow light as they streaked through the sky.

Ever since Han Li grouped up with the two, none of them had yet to mention their other teammates. It was as if they hadn’t existed.

When the wooden bird flew for half a day, a silver streak shot off from the horizon and flew several circles around the island where the cultivators were. It then flashed, hurrying off in the direction where the wooden bird fled.

A month later, a ball of yellow light swept across the wilderness. It was the wooden bird, carrying Han Li and the other two.

Ever since they set off, Ye Chu had been utilizing the wooden bird with her entire power. They were as fast as lightning and she had no intention of slowing down.

In this case, they were able to arrive at the entrance of the Southern Skyline in such a short amount of time.

Han Li and the two women couldn't help but feel relief.

But at that moment, storms suddenly surged in front of them and thunder roiled. The sky turned incredibly dark as dark clouds roiled around them, covering over half the sky. Faint howls could be heard past the cooming thunder.

The howls weren’t loud, but they were muffled, giving them an imposing presence. The two women’s expressions vastly changed when they heard them.

“This is...” Han Li narrowed his eyes and wore hesitation on his face.

At that moment, several huge silver arcs flashed from the dark cloud and thunder rang from it. Like a huge mountaintop penetrating the clouds, two faintly golden eyes opened from the black sky. It rigidly stared at the wooden bird from a distance.

Under the darkness, Han Li sensed an icy Qi suddenly crawl up his back and instantly envelop his body. For a time, he wasn’t able to move his body in the slightest.

Chapter 1381: True Spirit Body

"That's the head of a dragon! The head of a true dragon; definitely not the head of a mere wyrm!" Han Li was shocked as he looked up at the gargantuan creature in the distant sky.

The massive head in the sky was completely identical to the heads of true dragons he'd seen in tomes. Furthermore, the entire head was a shimmering golden color, as if it had been constructed entirely from gold. There were also a couple of tree-like golden horns on its head, and it was quite an intimidating being to behold.

"But it's not a true dragon? Its aura does indeed possess the might of a true dragon, but the spiritual power within its body is only comparable to a mid-Body Integration demonic cultivator at most. How could a True Spirit level being possess such paltry spiritual power?" Ye Chu exclaimed.

A cold light flashed through Ye Ying 's eyes upon hearing Ye Chu's words, and she murmured to herself, "It's not a True Spirit level being, but it can reveal the body of a true dragon, which means its forcibly activating the blood of a true dragon, thereby allowing it to manifest such a form."

"The blood of a true dragon? Then the Long Family must be involved here." Ye Chu's brows furrowed with a cold expression.

"That is indeed most likely the case. I've always found it strange that the young master of the Long Family was assigned this mission not long after I was assigned the same mission. It looks like he's coming after me," Ye Ying chuckled coldly.

"He's coming after you, Young Mistress? Could it be because of that rumor..." A thought occurred to Ye Chu, and a stunned look appeared on her face.

"What rumor?" After activating his Great Development Technique, Han Li had finally recovered from that indescribable sense of intimidation, and he turned to Ye Ying with a dark expression.

"Hehe, all you have to know is that the young master of the Long Family is behind this, and that he's after the heavenly phoenix spirit blood in my body. However, seeing as they've decided to attack me here, they naturally aren't intending to let me escape alive. Our true spirit families had set up an agreement long ago, strictly prohibiting true spirit families from going after the true spirit bloodlines of other such families. If caught doing so, all of the other true spirit families would join forces to destroy that family. No matter how bold the young master of the Long Family is, there's no way he'd dare to attack me in human territory, which is why he followed me all the way to this place before setting his scheme into motion. However, a Deity Transformation cultivator like him won't be capable of activating true spirit blood alone. It's most likely the case that other Spatial Tempering cultivators from the Long Family have also come to this place," Ye Ying analyzed in a remarkably calm manner.

After hearing this and thinking back to the special attention Long Dong had paid to Ye Ying along this journey, he was mostly convinced that Ye Ying had struck the nail on the head.

"I can understand it if he was going after some type of normal true spirit blood, but for ancient true spirit families like our Ye Family and his Long Family, the spirit blood has already been deeply entrenched in our family bloodlines for countless years, so theoretically, there's no way for it to be taken. The Long Family should also be aware of this." A hint of befuddlement flashed through Ye Chu's grave eyes.

"I'm not sure what's going on, either, but seeing as the Long Family is attacking us right now, I can only assume that they've worked out some type of solution to this predicament. However, even if that's the case, they'll have to be able to defeat my heavenly phoenix body first. I'll require your assistance to activate my spirit blood, Big Sister Chu. Brother Han, I'll have to trouble you to protect me during this process," Ye Ying said with a grave expression.

"Seeing as I can't detach myself from this matter, I'll be sure to assist you to the best of my abilities." A wry smile appeared on Han Li's face as he looked at the approaching dark clouds and that massive dragon head.

All of them remained completely unflustered, as if they weren't wary of that supposed true dragon body at all.

"I'm glad you understand the situation, Brother Han. I'll set up a formation first, then activate my spirit blood to battle this true dragon body. Let's see if the power of our Ye Family's heavenly phoenix is superior or if the true dragon blood of the Long Family is purer," Ye Ying said as her expression eased slightly.

She then swept a hand over her storage bracelet, and a thick stack of formation flags of all different colors appeared. She swept a hand through the air, and several tens of streaks of light shot forth in all directions before disappearing into the nearby ground.

A purple layer of light had appeared out of thin air in the blink of an eye before circling around in the air above.

For the time being, Han Li was unable to identify what kind of abilities this formation possessed.

At this moment, Ye Ying sat down with her legs crossed at the center of the formation in a casual manner. She then opened her mouth to expel five balls of light, all of which were of different colors, and those balls of light began to circle around her body.

Each ball of light was roughly the size of a human fist, and they contained miniature treasures of different forms. Those treasures consisted of a flute, a zither, a lute, a saber, and a ring.

Among them, the lute in the yellow ball of light was none other than the Lute of Wisdom that Han Li had seen once before. He had witnessed the power of this treasure in person, and he knew that this was a rare spirit treasure replica.

As such, those four other treasures were most likely treasures of the same caliber as the Lute of Wisdom. If that was indeed the case, then Ye Ying truly was incredibly wealthy.

Just as these thoughts were racing through Han Li's mind, Ye Ying summoned a pristine white jade vial with a grim expression. She removed the lid of the vial, and an extremely pleasant-sounding phoenix cry erupted from within. Immediately thereafter, a miniature rainbow phoenix that was only around an inch in size emerged from the vial, then attempted to fly away into the distance.

However, Ye Ying opened her mouth to blast forth a burst of five-colored light, which immediately ensnared the phoenix.

The brightness of the five-colored light intensified, and spiritual light flashed all over the rainbow phoenix's body, following which it reverted back to a five-colored spirit pill that was emanating a strong fragrant aroma.

Ye Ying pointed a finger at the pill in an expressionless manner. The five-colored spirit pill immediately flew toward her, and she swallowed it before closing her eyes.

At this moment, Ye Chu appeared beside her in a flash and also sat down onto the ground. She then made a hand seal and opened her mouth at the same time, expelling a yellow pillar of light. The pillar of light was filled with extremely pure wood-attribute spiritual Qi, and it was injected directly into Ye Ying 's body.

Almost at the exact same moment, azure spiritual light began to emanate from Ye Ying 's body, following which an azure halo that was several feet in diameter appeared above her head before slowly rotating on the spot.

Not only was this halo of a remarkably circular shape, there were also white flames flashing along its edge, rising up to around a foot in height. At the very center of the halo was a humanoid projection seated with its legs crossed. It bore a slight resemblance to Ye Ying , but it had been shrunk down several times, and it also had its eyes closed while making a series of hand seals.

The projection within the halo abruptly opened its eyes to reveal five-colored light swirling within its pupils, presenting an extremely peculiar sight to behold.

At this point, the dark clouds in the distance were only several kilometers away from them. Right at this moment, Ye Ying 's skin began to take on a remarkably red hue. A layer of extremely vibrant light surfaced over her face before surging into the halo in a frenzy as wisps of light.

The azure halo in the air above immediately shuddered before instantly being stained red, making it as exuberant as blood.

As soon as the projection in the halo came into contact with this crimson light, it instantly absorbed the light into its body, and five-colored spiritual light began to simultaneously emanate from its body.

Following the vast influx of crimson light, the five-colored spiritual light swelled and began to become more dazzling and piercing to behold.

The entire projection was transformed into a piercing five-colored sun.

All of a sudden, the cry of a phoenix pierced directly into the heavens, and the halo swirled before completely disappearing into the five-colored sun. Immediately thereafter, brilliant five-colored spiritual light began to radiate from the artificial sun, and it transformed into a five-colored rainbow phoenix that was around 10 feet in size. The phoenix let loose a clear cry before spreading its wings and flying directly toward the dark clouds.

Along the way, its body swelled drastically, virtually doubling in size with each and every flap of its wings. Following just a few flaps, the entire rainbow phoenix had swelled to over 1,000 feet in length. An intimidating aura that was not inferior to a giant dragon's also began to emanate from its body.

The giant phoenix appraised the dragon head amid the dark clouds with a frosty light in its silver eyes.

In the instant that the giant rainbow phoenix appeared, the golden dragon head's roar abruptly cut off, and it adopted a solemn expression, as if it were preparing to face a powerful foe. The dark clouds and lightning flashed, following which a golden body that was over 2,000 feet in length was finally revealed.

This true dragon body appeared to be around twice the size of the five-colored rainbow phoenix.

Even though the phoenix was clearly significantly smaller than its enemy, it wasn't fearful in the slightest as it flapped its wings.

Gusts of gale-force winds were swept up as thick pillars of wind rose into the air. Meanwhile, countless specks of white light surfaced close to one of its wings. Following a rapid string of spluttering sounds, the specks of light transformed into balls of white flames that quickly began to swell in size, forming a sea of white flames in the blink of an eye.

As such, a peculiar scene appeared.

With the rainbow phoenix's wings as a boundary, one half of the sky was filled with howling winds and violent azure wind-attribute power, while the other half of the sky was ignited by a sea of tumbling white flames, emanating scorching temperatures that made the air shimmer and warp.

Upon seeing this, the golden dragon's aura also abruptly became more chaotic and violent. Loud thunderclaps erupted from within the dark clouds up above, and countless bolts of lightning came crashing down. These bolts of lightning transformed into silver lightning wyrms, each of which was over 100 feet in length, and countless such lightning wyrms began to gather around the golden dragon.

Just as Han Li was looking on from down below in a flabbergasted manner, the roar of a dragon and the cry of a phoenix rang out in unison. The golden dragon opened its mouth to blast forth a golden pillar of light, and the silver lightning wyrms around it also immediately surged toward the phoenix. Meanwhile, the rainbow phoenix swept both wings forward at once, sending forth an azure typhoon and a white sea of flames in retaliation.

Explosive rumbling booms instantly rocked heaven and earth as the two true spirit bodies finally clashed.

Han Li looked on at the battle unfolding up above with narrowed eyes, but most of his spiritual sense had been released to the area near the formation in case any unforeseen circumstances were to arise.

The silver arcs of lightning, azure gusts of gale-force winds, and white flames intertwined with one another. Amid the clash of the three different types of powers, glimpses of the bodies of the golden dragon and the rainbow phoenix could be gleaned from time to time, and they were engaging in a physical brawl just as normal beasts would.

Of course, their powers and abilities were far beyond those of normal beasts. As the golden dragon swept its claws through the air, it was able to easily tear through space, while the rainbow phoenix was able to make space twist and deform with a flap of its wings.

Resounding booms rang out incessantly between the two creatures, and it was as if the entire sky could be torn apart at any moment.

Han Li was feeling quite astonished as he witnessed this battle.

If these so-called true spirit bodies were already this devastatingly powerful, then just how unfathomably destructive would true dragons and heavenly phoenixes be?

The records on the tomes suggested that true dragons and heavenly phoenixes were beings that defied the natural order, and that they didn't even have to fear the true immortals of the True Immortal Realm. It appeared that those claims could indeed be true.

Chapter 1387: Heavenly Phoenix Feather

"Don't you dare!" The blood dragon immediately let loose a roar of shock and fury as a streak of crimson light shot forth from its body, hurtling directly toward the cauldron.

In this desperate situation, Long Dong's soul released its final bit of true spirit blood as a streak of sword Qi in a final stand.

If this was just a normal attack, then the crimson sword Qi would most likely be able to vanquish it.

However the Heavenvoid Cauldron itself was also a Divine Spirit Treasure, and the azure threads it unleashed were extremely versatile.

Azure light immediately flashed in the air as most of the azure threads disappeared at Han Li's behest. The remaining threads also suddenly transformed into a streak of azure light to combat the oncoming crimson light.

In the next instant, spatial fluctuations erupted in the air around a foot above the crimson dragon, and a plume of azure threads shot forth from within space.

The azure threads dispersed, instantly ensnaring the blood dragon and the blood phoenix within the five-colored flames before drawing them toward the Heavenvoid Cauldron.

All of a sudden, a ball of azure light suddenly emerged from the desperately struggling blood dragon. The ball of light flashed before appearing over 100 feet away, then flashed several times in quick succession to cover a distance of 300 to 400 feet.

A cold light flashed through Han Li's eyes as a burst of black light suddenly shot forth from his Law Destruction Eye.

A dull thump rang out in the air, following which the azure ball of light stumbled out of thin air, and it seemed to have dimmed significantly.

However, before Han Li had a chance to unleash any other attacks, the azure ball of light abruptly flashed through the air, disappearing into the distance in the blink of an eye.

Han Li's brows furrowed as the black light that had just accumulated within his third demonic eye dissipated.

The Law Destruction Eye did indeed possess the ability to puncture space, but he naturally couldn't do anything from such a long distance away.

Meanwhile, the blood dragon and the blood phoenix had already been sealed away into his Heavenvoid Cauldron.

The lid of the cauldron then came crashing down with a resounding boom.

What everyone had failed to notice was that in that instant, two discreet specks of golden light suddenly emerged from one of Han Li's sleeves before disappearing into the cauldron in an extremely stealthy manner.

At this moment, the other four cultivators were situated several thousand feet away from Han Li, and all of them were stunned to see Han Li capturing the true spirit blood while Long Dong fled for his life.

The two Long Family cultivators glanced at one another before immediately fleeing the scene as two streaks of light. Those ghosts and devils they had summoned also fled in hot pursuit.

The direction they were escaping toward was none other than the one that Long Dong had just disappeared in.

Ye Chu and Ye Ying displayed no intention to give chase. Instead, both of them flew toward Han Li.

Moments later, the two of them appeared just over 100 feet away from Han Li. Ye Chu was looking at Han Li and his Weeping Soul Beast with undisguised shock in her eyes.

Meanwhile, Ye Ying wore a smile on her face, but her eyes were fixed on the azure cauldron in front of Han Li.

It was quite clear that the two had become extremely wary of Han Li after he had captured the true spirit bloods.

"Brother Han, thank you for your assistance. If it hadn't been for your efforts, the Long Family would’ve most likely succeeded in their scheme. Rest assured, Brother Han; the conditions I promised you earlier remain unchanged. Your efforts won't be for nothing," Ye Ying said with a seductive smile.

"Indeed. With the power of our Ye Family, there are very few wishes what we won't be able to grant you," Ye Chu also said in a slow voice, but there was a barely-disguised threat in her words.

Han Li's lips twitched, but he didn't say anything as he patted the azure cauldron before him.

A ringing sound erupted as the lid of the cauldron was lifted once again. The blood dragon and the blood phoenix both emerged at the opening of the cauldron with countless azure threads binding their bodies.

Ye Ying and Ye Chu were ecstatic to see the true spirit bloods. A crimson light flashed past Ye Ying 's face, and the indistinct projection of a miniature blood phoenix appeared for a split second.

Han Li smiled as he flicked a finger toward the azure cauldron.

All of the azure threads around the blood phoenix were immediately severed, and it was tossed toward Ye Ying .

Ye Ying was ecstatic to see this, and she let loose a delicate cry as the other miniature blood phoenix flew forth from her body, crashing into the oncoming incomplete blood phoenix.

Brilliant crimson light flashed, and the two of them combined as one without any impediment, forming a crimson ball that was around a foot in size.

The ball was of an extremely vibrant shade of red, as if it had been forged from blood essence. After circling around in the air for a while, it transformed into a blood phoenix that was around a foot in size, flapping its wings as it flew in circles around Ye Ying .

Ye Ying wore a smile on her face as she pointed a slim finger at the blood phoenix.

Following a crisp heavenly cry, the blood phoenix spread its wings and disappeared into Ye Ying 's body as a streak of crimson light.

Immediately thereafter, a layer of crimson light surfaced over Ye Ying 's body. At the same time, the indistinct projection of a blood phoenix appeared behind her. It was initially rather blurry, but it slowly became clearer and gradually stabilized.

After a while, the blood phoenix projection disappeared, and Ye Ying opened her eyes with excitement shining on her face.

"Most of my true phoenix blood has been recovered. There's still a small portion missing, and it’s most likely been forcibly devoured by this true dragon blood, so it won't be easy to separate it. Thankfully, the true dragon blood has also fallen in our hands. Brother Han, toss the true dragon blood over to me as well; blood of this caliber has to be stored carefully as using ordinary containers could quite possibly damage its spiritual nature." Ye Ying smiled as she flipped over her hand to produce a small purplish-golden gourd that was extremely intricate and beautiful.

However, Han Li merely smiled in response, but showed no intention of handing over the true dragon blood.

"Fairy Ye, if I recall correctly, I seem to have only promised to help you recover your true spirit blood. Now that you've already recovered the heavenly phoenix blood, isn't it too greedy of you to ask for this true dragon blood as well?"

"What are you trying to say, Fellow Daoist Han? Could it be that you want to keep this true spirit blood for yourself?" Ye Chu's voice immediately cooled as she shot daggers from her eyes.

"I may be an ascended cultivator, but I know the taboos of the true spirit families; I wouldn't dare to take the true dragon blood for myself. Even if I were to fuse the true spirit blood into my body, I'd end up being hunted by all of the true spirit families," Han Li replied with a smile and a shake of his head.

Seeing as Han Li wasn't intending to take the true dragon blood for himself, Ye Ying 's expression eased as she asked, "Then what do you propose, Brother Han?"

"Hehe, nothing much. This true dragon should be no less valuable than your heavenly phoenix blood; your Ye Family would be intent on getting your hands on it, right? If I were willing to offer up this item, what would you give me in exchange?" Han Li asked.

"Hehe, so you're looking for some benefits, Brother Han. That's no problem at all; state your price, Brother Han," Ye Ying replied with a wide smile.

"An item as precious as true spirit blood can't be exchanged for using mere spirit stones. Having said that, if you have 100 or so top-grade spirit stones, I can certainly consider it," Han Li said in an indifferent voice.

Ye Ying 's expression changed slightly, and she turned to exchange a glance with Ye Chu. After turning back to Han Li, her smile was a little more forced as she said, "Surely you jest, Brother Han; even our Ye Family won't be able to offer up so many top-grade spirit stones at once. If you're only looking for a few, I can try and source them for you."

"If I'm only looking for a few top-grade spirit stones, I wouldn't trouble you two; I'd be able to source them on my own, albeit with a bit of effort," Han Li replied.

"So what do you want? Go ahead and spit it out," Ye Chu urged in a cold voice, seemingly having run out of patience.

"It's quite simple; I want one of the heavenly phoenix feathers in your possession, Senior Ye," Han Li said in a slow voice.

"What heavenly phoenix feather? Have you been swindled by that Black Phoenix Race cultivator?" Ye Chu’s pupils contracted slightly upon hearing this, but her expression remained calm.

"Do you think I'd believe that, Senior Ye? If you insist on denial, I wouldn't mind using a soul search technique on Fellow Daoist Xiao. I only want a single feather. One heavenly phoenix feather in exchange for true dragon blood is a huge bargain for the two of you." Han Li's expression remained calm and collected.

Ye Chu's brows furrowed tightly upon hearing this, and she cast her gaze toward Ye Ying .

Ye Ying pursed her lips a few times before asking, "What do you need this heavenly phoenix feather for? This item is also very useful to our Ye Family, so would you be able to accept anything else instead? How about the two Zoysia Dragon Fruits I obtained earlier?"

"I have a treasure that needs to be refined again, and that process just so happens to require a heavenly phoenix feather. As for Zoysia Dragon Fruits, those are quite tempting as well, but in comparison, they obviously pale next to a heavenly phoenix feather," Han Li replied calmly.

"So you're only after the heavenly phoenix feather, Brother Han? Is there no room for negotiation?" Ye Ying stared at the blood dragon atop the azure cauldron with an indecisive look on her face.

"Hehe, if you're in possession of Immortal Gaze Pills or Nineheart Spirit Zoysias, I wouldn't mind taking them as well," Han Li chuckled.

"Hmph, if I had such things, why would I even need the true dragon blood? I could just take those to ascend to the Spatial Tempering and Body Integration Stages. Alright, you have yourself a deal; I'll exchange for the true dragon blood with a heavenly phoenix feather," Ye Ying gritted her teeth and agreed in the end.

Ye Chu's expression changed slightly upon hearing this, and she opened her mouth to say something, but swallowed her words in the end. Han Li's eyes immediately lit up.

"Haha, that's a very wise decision, Fellow Daoist Ye. If you'd allow me to examine the phoenix feather in order to verify its authenticity first, I'll immediately hand over the true dragon blood. You wouldn't be worried that I'll take the treasure and leave, right?" Han Li said with a smile.

Ye Ying sighed and turned to Ye Chu as she instructed, "Big Sister Chu, give him a phoenix feather."

"Yes, Young Mistress." Ye Chu hesitated momentarily, but did as she was told in the end. She swept a hand over her storage bracelet to produce a fiery red jade box.

Not only was this jade box of a vibrant crimson color, its surface was engraved with fiery patterns. Upon being produced, it began to emanate a scorching aura, and the surrounding temperatures were instantly raised significantly.

"Flame Jade!" Han Li was quite taken aback at the sight of this jade box.

Chapter 1394: Scheming for True Toads

About two weeks later, a clear and long shriek sounded from the outside. Although it wasn't loud, it roused Han Li and the others that were resting.

Han Li’s brow moved and he opened his eyes.

He blinked and tilted his head in thought. Then he stood up and walked out of the ice building.

There was a spacious area in front of the ice building, but at an unknown time, it turned into an icy hall that was three hundred meters long. It was supported by many huge pillars of ice. Although they were exceptionally crude, it sparkled under the sunlight and gave it an imposing presence.

Inside the hall, there was a ten-meter-tall platform where a man and a woman stood.

The man had a head of silver hair and a handsome young face. As for the woman, she wore her hair in a coil and had a well-rounded body, adding to her exceptional beauty. Despite her bare, frail and flawless limbs, she didn’t seem to mind the cold.

The two were at the Spatial Tempering stage. The man in particular was at mid-stage.

The long whistle came from the silver-haired man.

Five people were standing below the platform. Fairy Ying and Old Man Liu stood among them. When the whistle sounded, Han Li and the others came out from their buildings.

In the blink of an eye, over twenty cultivators appeared on the mountain.

The cultivators were all at the Deity Transformation stage at the very least. They walked to the hall with various expressions.

Han Li wore a calm expression as he followed them inside.

When the group entered, many people immediately said, “We pay our respects to Senior Zhu and Senior Qing!”

“These two Seniors have also come! It is good to see you again!”

Han Li soon found an empty spot and stood there unmoving.

The two that originally visited and invited him were the pair of famous golden guards, the woman and man on stage.

Although he only spoke to them once, he had heard much about them. If they weren’t also ascended cultivators, Han Li didn’t know if he would've agreed to this meeting, no matter what rewards were promised.

Senior Zhu’s long whistle had come to a stop and he smiled in response to everyone’s greeting. Then he loudly said, “It appears everyone has come. Please have a seat. Let’s have a proper discussion on how we’ll clean up the nest of Blue-eyed True Toads.”

When he finished speaking, the woman at his side immediately released a spell seal on the floor.

Suddenly, the ice hall lit up with white light and rows of exquisite jade chairs appeared as a result of simple spell formations.

When the cultivators saw this, they took a seat. The two Spatial Tempering cultivators on stage also sat down.

The silver-haired man swept his gaze to both sides and smiled, “It appears that the number of cultivators that arrived was what we expected. When we invited you, we assumed forty percent would be able to make it. As for the others, they couldn't make it for a myriad of reasons.

But even so, we will have to concentrate our efforts in exterminating the Blue-eyed True Toad next. When the time comes, we will all take what we need. You will divide the True Toad Spirit Blood among yourselves while we will take the Thousand Heart Flowers that the beasts are guarding.

It is as we had mentioned before. Are there any objections? Of course, the division of True Toad Spirit Blood will be in accordance to what you contribute. It won’t be evenly split. I hope that you will stifle your thoughts about having a free ride.”

With that said, a huge pressure faintly emitted from his body and his face turned stern.

The other cultivators in the room remained standing and added nothing else.

“Good, since you understand, let’s discuss the operation’s concrete steps. The group of True Toads were discovered by Fairy Ying. Let’s have her explain,” the youth smiled and turned to the veiled woman.

“Senior Zhu, your wish is my command.”

Fairy Ying smiled and she gracefully stood up. She swept her gaze past the other cultivators and said, “I won’t speak of how I discovered the True Toad nest, but I can tell you that there are nearly ten toads. The two fully mature toads are around the level of mid Spatial Tempering. The other toads will be at Nascent Soul strength. The toads have always hidden in the depths of their nest and rarely head out. If we wish to attack their nest, it will become very difficult. After all, it will be difficult for us to fight them in that environment.

With that said, the woman briefly paused and continued, “If it was just that, there would be no need to invite you all here. The crucial point is that there are two types of ferocious beasts living nearby. One of them is the Black Blood Ants with the other being a Shadow Insect Beast.

The two insects might not be anything alone, but they live together in a group over a hundred. If we want to deal with the toads, we’ll need to deal with these insects first.”

“Black Blood Ants?”

“Shadow Insect Beasts.”

...

When they heard the masked woman, most of the cultivators began to whisper. There were even a few that didn’t dare to discuss the topic with their neighbors.

The two insects were actually quite infamous. If the insects were there, they would pose a large threat even against Spatial Tempering cultivators.

After she finished speaking, the veiled woman nodded to the silver-haired youth and sat back down.

Senior Zhu calmly said, “There is no need to be nervous. Since we’ve invited you here, we already have a method to deal with them. We only need you to assist us with vigor!”

An old man with a bamboo hat stood up and bowed, saying, “Senior Zhu! It’s not that we don’t trust you, but the matter appears quite dangerous. Could Senior explain his plan?”

The old man was one of the few late Deity Transformation cultivators.

“So it was Fellow Daoist You. Please sit back down. Even if you didn’t mention it, I still would’ve explained.” Senior Zhu smiled nonchalantly.

The old man didn’t speak any further and sat down with a salute.

“It’s quite simple, the two insects may be troublesome, but we’ve purchased Sandalwood Crane Incense. It has an immensely powerful attractive allure to the Black Blood Ants. So long as we light it from a distance, we can easily attract them to the surface and exterminate them. On the contrary, the Shadow Insects are troublesome to deal with. However, we’ve borrowed a set of Profound Heavenly Lightning Flags. With eight of you using this treasure, we can form a ring of lightning and restrain the insects. Apart from that, we also invited Fellow Daoist Han and Fairy Xiao, who both have techniques that will be effective against the insects. With you two assisting the lightning formation, it should be safe. As for the remaining few, they will join with me and my wife in exterminating the True Toads. How do you feel about this?” Senior Zhu’s voice wasn’t loud, but it was easily heard.

When Han Li heard Senior Zhu mention his own name, his expression stirred and he swept his gaze past the hall, finding that many were looking in his direction.

There was also a woman wearing silver-white robes that appeared in her twenties. She possessed a dainty appearance and looked at Han Li with a warm smile.

Han Li unconsciously returned the smile and curiously thought, ‘Could it be she is Fairy Xiao? She also cultivates an ability that can restrain the Shadow Insects?”

Follow that, other cultivators would occasionally ask a question.

Fairy Zhu answered all of the questions with a friendly tone, satisfying all the cultivators present.

However, Han Li took notice that the beautiful woman at his side rarely said a word from the very start. She merely stood there with a smile.

Han Li found this odd.

He recalled that when they invited him to this meeting, only the handsome youth seemed to speak. She hadn’t spoken at all.

Could it be that the woman is a high-ranking Buddhist and practices that strange technique that requires a vow of silence? Otherwise, if she were deaf or mute, how would she be able to cultivate to this stage?

Han Li inwardly pondered.

After two hours passed, there were no other questions and Senior Zhu began to divide them.

It stood to mention that apart from Han Li and Fairy Xiao, there were actually many cultivators among them that practiced a rare lightning technique, allowing them to use the Profound Heavenly Lightning Flags and form a ring lightning formation.

All of those present were ascended cultivators or the descendants of ascended cultivators. None of them had been born naturalized with this world.

Therefore, although their numbers were many, they didn’t care much about how they were divided.

When they were all given an assignment, Senior Zhu didn’t have an intention of delay and promptly gave a command, ordering the twenty-some people to depart. They all flew west.

After three entire days of flight, the party eventually arrived in front of a huge lake.

With a single glance, they saw a dense and salty mist from the lake, giving it a mysterious presence.

Many of the cultivators couldn't help but frown at the sight.

Normally, most cultivators were unwilling to enter strange areas in the wilderness like this one as it was unknown what lurked in the mist and the lake. If they were ambushed, it would be a brush with death.

Without need for a warning, everyone slowed their speed and stopped in front of the mist.

Chapter 1395: Sandalwood Crane Incense and Black Blood Ants

The silver-haired Spatial Tempering youth, Senior Zhu, loudly announced from the front, “Fellow Daoists, be careful. There is an unknown demon bird in the mist, but fortunately, they aren’t very strong. So long as you are careful of the acid they spit, it shouldn’t be fine. As for the mist itself, let me and my wife deal with it.”

Afterwards, the others waited as the silver-haired youth opened his mouth and spat out a long white jade bottle. It spun in the air and had its mouth pointed at the white mist.

The youth formed a hand gesture with both his hands and muttered an incantation, causing the jade bottle to brightly light up.

A muffled crackle sounded, followed by the bottle releasing an azure wind.

When the wind flew out, it only carried a faint azure light, but after it traveled ten meters, it blew into a raging gale. Then in the blink of an eye, it turned into a violent tornado.

The mist on the surface of the lake violently roiled as it split apart.

A clear path opened in the mist.

“We go!”

With Senior Zhu’s command, he and his wife took the initiative to first fly through the path. The jade bottle he earlier released began to circle above his head and continued to release violent gales.

When the others saw this, they felt a sense of relief and followed after them.

As Senior Zhu had mentioned, after they entered five kilometers in, meter-long white birds with flat beaks and dark-green claws began to appear from the surrounding mist.

The birds were clearly targeting the cultivators. As soon as they emerged from the mist, they opened their mouths and released black ice arrows.

With several shouts, the cultivators released their magic treasures, summoning formations of swords or several ancient shields.

When the black ice arrows struck, they immediately turned into black smoke. It left dense and numerous holes in the treasures where they struck.

The masters of the magic treasure revealed shock when they saw this. One of them immediately shouted, “Quickly kill them. Their acid can corrode our treasures!”

The others felt their hearts tremble when they heard this and immediately displayed their various techniques. Streaks of swift light and waves of mist moved in the direction of the demon birds.

Under the wave of attacks, the demon birds turned into balls of gore and blood, instantly dying in their entirety.

When the others saw this, they felt relief.

The birds had been truly weak.

A quarter-hour later, several strange cries sounded from the mist. Suddenly, another flock of white birds flew out from the mist and pelted the cultivators with black ice arrows.

Startled, the cultivators flusteredly released their treasures and blocked the attacks before exterminating the birds once more.

When the last of the birds turned into a bloody pulp, many bird silhouettes began to appear from the mist.

The cultivators became restless when they saw this and many of them wore expressions of unease.

Han Li frowned and he swept his spiritual sense through the mist. Bird cries began to sound out from the mist surrounding them from every direction, including from above and below them. There were too many to keep track of.

Although Han Li had encountered many dangers, even this caused him to feel a chill on his back.

Senior Zhu’s calm voice sounded from the front, “Everyone, don’t be scared! These birds are only launching probing attacks on us. When they see that a dozen waves of their attacks are ineffective, they will scatter.”

When the others heard this, they began to activate their treasures and slaughtered any of the white birds that came to attack them.

Thirteen waves of the birds attacked them in succession. Eventually, long sharp cries sounded from the flocking birds and they scattered, withdrawing from the mist around them.

When the cultivators saw this, they felt relief and seized the opportunity to head forward.

Half a day later, the mist cleared around them. Their surroundings lit up and they saw a huge mountain at the center of the lake. It was overwhelmingly large and seemed to reach out from the bottom of the lake.

The portion of the mountain they could see was filled with green stone. Apart from the moss that grew on top of them, there were no other plants.

After the group came to a stop, Senior Zhu clicked his tongue and said, “It is here! Hehe, we have to thank Fairy Ying and her comrades in finding this place.”

The veiled woman chuckled and said, “We found this mountain unintentionally as we were pursuing a beast. This was only a fortunate encounter.”

Senior Zhu laughed and spoke with excited eyes, “In truth, if one isn’t lucky, it would be difficult to find this secret land. Nevertheless, we came across a group of True Toads. If it were on the outside, It would’ve been likely found by others. Let us start.”

The other cultivators nodded with a smile.

“The True Toad Nest is located in a natural underground cave at the bottom of the mountain. We’ll act as we originally planned. We’ll first attract the Black Blood Ants and kill them. Everyone, be careful. Although the ants are a grade-eight demon beast, they are innately capable of breaking our defensive shields and light. Furthermore, they are incredibly venomous. If they bite us, immediately swallow an antidote or your life will be forfeit. Alright, everyone prepare yourselves. I will light the Sandalwood Crane Incense.” Following his quick warning, Senior Zhu flipped his hand and suddenly produced a palm-sized incense burner. He struck a half-foot-long stick of green incense.

He flung the incense burner up where it slowly revolved in midair.

Senior Zhu raised his hand and flicked his finger, igniting the incense with a flash of red light. The green incense stick then released a trail of azure stroke.

When Han Li looked at the incense burner, an odd expression appeared on his face.

‘The Sandalwood Crane Incense looked unremarkable and it didn’t have much of a scent either? Was it truly effective against the Black Blood Ants?’ Han Li worriedly mused.

At that moment, the cultivators began to separate and conceal themselves.

Han Li was among them, flying three hundred meters up. Just as he was about to cast a technique, a white streak flickered and a slender silhouette appeared by his side.

Han Li was stunned and looked at the silhouette. She was the dainty woman, Fairy Xiao.

The woman was also surprised Han Li chose the same location. She soon smiled and politely said, “Brother Han, I have a Hundred Bewildering Lights Flag. It is rather marvelous at concealing a location. How about I use it to hide us both?”

“Hehe, in that case, I’ll have to trouble you,” Han Li courteously replied.

“It is only a slight effort. Brother Han is being too formal!” She faintly smiled and raised her hand, producing a small snow-white flag. It then spun a circle above them.

The woman struck the flag with a spell seal and it blurred, suddenly producing a white mist. It brilliantly shined, covering them in a mist in the blink of an eye.

A moment later, the mist vanished alongside Han Li and Lady Xiao.

Han Li stood in his original location and raised his hand. Even with his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, he still wasn’t able to see it.

With a tone of surprise, Han Li praised, “Your treasure is truly marvelous. It is much more powerful than ordinary concealment treasures.

“Fellow Daoist Han must be joking. This Hundred Bewildering Lights Flag may be truly powerful in invisibility, but it isn’t capable of concealment from spiritual sense. It is only useful against creatures with weak spiritual sense like these insect beasts.”

To his surprise, Han Li swept his spiritual sense past the woman and immediately verified her words to be true. He lamented, feeling it was a pity.

As his Brightsight Spirit Eyes couldn't see through the invisibility, it would be a formidable treasure if it could also hide from spiritual sense.

At that moment, the others also hid and withdrew their aura.

A moment later, apart from the small incense burner floating in the air, there was nothing else in sight.

The Sandalwood Crane Incense was truly effective. In only the time it took to finish a meal, buzzing sounds came from the direction of the mountain. At an unknown cave at the center of the mountain, a group of large winged ants flew in their direction.

The ants were each about half a foot long and were fanged. There was also a pair of green wings on their back. It appeared as if they were flying birds. They were truly startling.

It was obvious the ants were heading for the incense burner. Eventually, they made their way from the mountain to the incense and were completely surrounded by the cultivators.

Suddenly, the nearby space around the burner fluctuated. Senior Zhu and the beautiful woman appeared at nearly the same time and he shouted, “Attack!”

Lights lit up in every direction and soon, several tens of treasures appeared, turning into mists of light as they swept at the ant swarm. Large scale attacks such as fireballs and lightning struck as well.

From the fierce barrage, it appeared the cultivators wanted to end the ant swarm in a single strike.

With multiple huge explosions, the ants were submerged in rainbow light. Soon, waves of heat and cold swept out from the center of the barrage, forming an immense storm at the center of the explosions. The pressure of the winds even blew the cultivators a few steps back.

When the light and winds faded, all the ants disappeared, leaving not even a trace of ash behind.

Chapter 1411: Gold Marrow Body Refinement

Under closer examination, he discovered that the little bells were emitting a dense wood spiritual Qi; they were actually small golden flowers that resembled bells.

They appeared realistic as if they were bells forged from pure gold.

“There are truly many Woodbud Flowers, and they seem to be over a thousand years old.” When he saw the flowers, the huge ape hummed and wore an astonished expression.

Han Li chuckled, “Woodbud Flowers? You’ve seen them before. How about the Golden Marrow Crystal Insects and the Golden Corral Sand?”

The small beast’s eyes flickered with joy, but he calmly said, “I fear there isn’t enough, but the hundred of flowers will qualify for an exchange of ten pairs of beetles in accordance with our agreement.”

Han Li smiled and he tossed the jade box in front of him, then floating in the air. Then he flipped his other hand and produced a long jade box.

The lit open to produce a box brimming with Woodbud Flowers.

The scene left many of the demon beasts dumbstruck.

Han Li looked at the demon beasts and leisurely said, “This should be enough. Take out whatever crystal insects and coral sand you’ve brought along.”

Startled, the demon beasts whispered a few words to one another. Eventually, the small beast took out fist-sized crystals, and the other demon beasts took out palm-sized black gourds.

In the blink of an eye, fifteen crystals and three black gourds appeared in the hall.

Han Li’s eyes lit up and he silently reached for them.

Suddenly, one of the crystals floated and jumped into his hand.

Han Li closely examined it.

The crystal was clear and translucent. It was clearly condensed from a pair of pure-white insects, unmoving as if they were fossilized.

His immense spiritual sense instantly turned into countless threads and penetrated its crystal body, affecting the small insect on the top of the crystal.

A layer of milky white light appeared from the surface of the insect. Then, it spat a drop of golden liquid from its mouth which seeped onto its body.

Bright light radiated from the crystal, filling the air with sparkling golden light.

When Han Li saw this, his expression stirred and he exerted strength into his grip on the crystal, forcing an immense pressure on it.

The crystal’s body simply flickered with light, but it wasn’t harmed at all.

Han Li muttered, “It really is a Golden Marrow Crystal Insect!”

“Senior, don’t worry. We may be mighty bold, but we’d never deceive you.” The small bull-headed beast wryly laughed.

“Is that so?” Han Li neutrally replied. Then, he put down the crystal and flicked his hand, summoning a black gourd into his grasp.

He tilted it, pouring a river of purple-gold sand out from it. Soon, a meter-tall pile appeared on the ground.

Han Li pinched a grain of sand from the pile and brought it to his eye.

He stared at it for a long while and poured out the sand from the other two black gourds into one combined pile.

Han Li looked at the sand pile and casually said, “Not bad, this Golden Coral Sand is of the best quality. With the addition of the fifteen pairs of crystal insects, the two boxes of Woodbud Flowers are still more valuable, but I’ll still agree to the trade.”

When the four demon beasts heard this, they nodded with joy.

Han Li tossed the two boxes over, and the small beast and the huge gold-furred ape carefully put it away.

Meanwhile, Han Li swept his sleeve across the ground. In an azure mist, the crystals and the gourds of sand disappeared without a trace.

“I am satisfied with this trade. If you find any Golden Coral Sand or other rare items in the future, I will trade them for items you need. I don’t only have Woodbud Flowers, and I won’t have you take a loss. You may leave.” With no further intention of having the demons stay, Han Li dismissed them.

Under the pressure of Han Li’s immense aura, the demon beasts didn’t dare to say anything further and they respectfully and carefully withdrew from Han Li’s cave residence. They promptly took off in a demonic wind.

The demon beasts flew for over five hundred kilometers in a single stretch before stopping and letting out a long sigh. They then gathered together again.

The huge boar excitedly snorted, “This is great! I didn’t expect that we’d get so many Woodbud Flowers in a single go. Furthermore, they’re all over a thousand years old. If we deliver all of them, the Tian Peng race definitely won’t punish us even if we don’t offer anything else.”

The huge ape frowned and said, “Yes, I didn’t expect this person to truly acquire so many of the flowers. If I remember correctly, Woodbud Flowers didn’t in such numbers on that mountain. Could it be when he scouted the mountain, he found other secret areas? From his tone, it seems he had even more flowers.”

The three-headed python looked around and said, “That is most likely so. Having presented so many Woodbud Flowers at once, it's very possible he has even more. The Tian Peng Race heavily values these flowers. They must be rare. They are most likely a specialty of our Hidden Black Mountains.”

The small beast pondered for a moment and said, “Regardless of how rare the flowers are, it has nothing to do with us. So long as we can endure for a hundred years and remove our slave markings, we’ll be able to leave far away. However, we must supply as many high-grade spirit stones to that Master as we can. Otherwise, if we make a mistake, all these years would’ve been wasted.”

“With the Woodbud Flowers, wasting another hundred years won’t be an issue. But what’s key is that we truly don’t have many spirit stones. Low-grade spirit stones are worthless to us and mid-grade spirit stones are worthless to the Master. As for high-grade spirit stones, they’ve all been exhausted from the mine. Furthermore, that Master also wants us to give him four differently attributed top-grade spirit stones. Let alone the Hidden Black Mountains, top-grade spirit stones spotted all around the island are all water-attributed. It is beyond our ability to exchange them.” The yellow-furred ape hummed.

The huge boar muttered, “In accordance to the Master’s words, the top-grade spirit stones are required to break through a bottleneck. Otherwise, it will be very difficult to achieve.”

The four demons turned silent for a spell.

The huge three-headed python turned around and its center head slowly said, “If it were before, it’d be hard to say, but now that this powerful Senior has come from a different place. Perhaps he has other attributed spirit stones.”

“That is something we’ve all thought off, but how can we use top-grade spirit stones at our cultivation? If we exchange for that item, I fear we will provoke his suspicion. We should think of other methods first. If we have no other options, we will trade with him,” the small beast carefully said.

“That sounds reasonable. After we deal with the Tian Peng Race’s envoy, we’ll consider it further,” the huge ape proposed.

The other beasts eventually agreed one after another, having come up with nothing else.

The four demons then turned into four clouds of demonic Qi and flew off in different directions.

At that moment, Han Li was inside his hidden room and was fiddling with the crystal insects. His eyes wandered as he pondered.

The Golden Marrow Crystal Insects were incredibly famous throughout demons and humans, so he only managed to acquire a pitiful few of them alive.

He also discovered that each and every single pair of them came at immense cost, enough to bankrupt a high-grade cultivator.

As such, when Han Li heard that the grade six and seven demon beasts were able to provide crystal insects to him, he was overwhelmed with joy.

The crystal insects had many uses. Not only could he use it as a primary ingredient to progress his cultivation, but it also had clear results in body refinement.

By applying the golden marrow that the insects spat out onto his body, he could easily cleanse his own marrow and essence, strengthening his body an entire step further. However, with the immense power of his current body, he figured the results would be less than he would expect.

Rather than these two uses, Han Li was more hopeful of the more obscure third use.

That was to use the crystal insect to use it to temper his own Provenance True Devil Art’s projection into having a true body.

With the vast power of this ability, he could fuse it with the Provenance True Devil to produce an extraordinary incarnation ability with the power of flattening mountains and silencing oceans.

Naturally, similar abilities appeared in Buddhist Sects which involved condensing Vajra Arts. It wasn’t a complicated technique and many knew of it, but in addition to requiring supplementary materials that involved the Golden Marrow Crystal Insect, but it required several other legendary spiritual medicines. These spirit medicines were rare to the point they were equivalent to the Golden Marrow Crystal Insects. If he wanted to collect them all, they would be a matter of complete luck, so he couldn't rely on it.

Han Li stared at the crystal in his hand and sank into thought.

He suddenly flicked his wrist and produced another four crystals in front of him.

Condensing the Provenance True Devil Art’s projection would take ten pairs of crystal insects. As for the remaining five pairs, he would bluntly use them to reinforce his body. Furthermore, they would assist him in breaking through his bottleneck at mid-Deity Transformation stage.

With all that smoothly decided, he had plans for the next five years.

Without any hesitation, he took a crystal into his hand and summoned pure azure light around it, then closing his eyes.

Underneath the provocation of spiritual power, the crystal formed from two still insects suddenly began to shake and open their mouths, each producing a golden drop.

The two drops of liquid passed through the crystals and flowed down onto Han Li’s hand where it fused with the azure spiritual Qi.

A moment later, the golden liquid glowed brightly with brilliant gold light.

The light and the azure Qi fused together slowly spread down his arm. In the blink of an eye, it covered his arm in golden light entirely.

Once the golden light faded away, the skin on Han Li’s arm had turned a shimmering gold.

Han Li held his golden arm and muttered to himself.

Golden light faintly pulsed from the arm once more and a layer of shimmering white floated off from it and floated in the air.

Han Li calmly breathed and had a tranquil face. Then he used his spiritual power to continue circulating this wondrous effect.

Chapter 1413: The Chi Rong Race

The small beast raised his frow in fright and he hastily replied, “We don’t dare to do such a thing. Lords, please personally inspect the year of the spirit flowers.”

Meanwhile, the huge gold-furred ape turned his palm and white light flashed in front of him. He summoned two jade boxes full of Woodbud Flowers and offered them to the Tian Peng beings with both arms.

The younger Tian Peng man skeptically received the two jade boxes and opened them.

Suddenly, sparkling golden light lit up in front of him and a medicinal scent filled the air.

The three Tian Peng beings were startled, but they were soon overjoyed.

The Tian Peng woman took one of the flowers and closely examined it. She excitedly said, “They truly are Woodbud Flowers over a thousand years old. Their qualities are first class.”

“That’s right,” the older man’s smile faded and he said, “You rarely hand over such high quality flowers. Tell about the other materials you are lacking.”

The four demon beasts felt relief when they heard this and gave them an explanation.

They then took out their other pieces of tribute and presented them for examination.

The younger man began to check through the tribute, “Hm, the Golden Marrow Crystal Insects and the Golden Coral Sand are somewhat lacking, and there is only half the amount of Azure Light Wood...”

“Good enough,” the older man nodded, “There aren’t many lacking materials. The additional Woodbud Flowers made up for your shortfalls. As a result of this tribute, we will bestow medicine pills for your slave markings. Next time we come, the more Woodbud Flowers, the better.” Then, he shook his sleeve and released four azure jade bottles to each of the four demons.

The four demons received the small bottles and repeatedly uttered their thanks.

Once the three Tian Peng beings put away their tribute, they immediately left the small beast’s cave residence.

The four demons respectfully saw them out the gate. Once they saw the three Tian Peng beings fly off as birds, they returned to the cave residence with relief and proceeded with their discussion.

The demons were completely unaware of the small golden beetle that was crouched in the corner of the room. It was still as death.

Meanwhile, Han Li remained hidden as he followed the three large birds. His eyes wandered without end.

Han Li had seen everything that happened inside the cave residence, including the tribute that was collected. He was certain they were planning their return to a meeting spot for their Tian Peng Race.

What he currently wanted to do was follow the three Tian Peng beings and find a safe route back to the Heavenly Origin Continent.

After all, in such a large sea, who knew what dangers laid hidden. Han Li didn’t wish to run into the domain of an immensely strong existence.

Furthermore, those from the Flying Spirit Tribe appeared similar to humans. If he could find out a place where the Tian Peng Race gathered, he could use his abilities to blend in and exchange information, materials, and medicines with them.

Perhaps this foreign race had many rare treasures like Gold Marrow Crystal Insects.

After all, the Flying Spirit Tribe were different from humans and had items that were priceless to humans but were ordinary to the Flying Spirit Tribe, and vice-versa.

With that in mind, Han Li’s thoughts grew excited and continued to tail the three Tian Peng Beings.

With Han Li’s abilities, the three weren’t able to escape the range of his spiritual sense and he could keep watch on them.

As a result, the three birds and a single cultivator swiftly flew from the side of a peninsula and through the nearby ocean. After flying for two months, Han Li eventually saw a black line on the horizon.

They’ve finally arrived on the shore of the Tian Yuan Continent.

At that moment, the three Tian Peng beings flew onto land.

Close to the shore, there were fields of uneven hills.

Han Li didn’t dare to slow down and lose them. He increased his speed and closed half the distance between them.

But then, something suddenly changed in front of them.

In front of the three Tian Peng beings was a huge two-headed bird and seven other winged foreign beings.

As soon as they appeared, they immediately surrounded the three Tian Peng beings as if they meant them harm.

Han Li was alarmed, but he didn’t stop. Soon, he found himself only half a kilometer away before he ceased flight.

The huge two-headed bird appeared frightening. It was thirty-meters tall, and of its two heads, one was a wyrm’s while the other was a tiger’s, but the rainbow feathers covering its body were gorgeous. As for the eight winged beings, they also appeared quite frightening. Not only were their wings larger than the Tian Peng Beings, but their scarlet wings seemed to be lit on fire.

In the blink of an eye, the three Tian Peng beings returned to their human forms and wore solemn expressions.

The older Tian Peng man harshly shouted at a large man in the group surrounding them, “Tian Ming, what is the meaning of this? This land is in the Tian Peng Race’s control. Why did your Chi Rong Race appear here and block our way? Could it be you don’t fear punishment of the ten laws?”

The large man wore a red robe, was bald, and had a brawny stature.

The large man chuckled, “Hehe, what is there to fear from the ten laws? Obediently take out the items you have. If you pay allegiance to our Chi Rong Race, perhaps we’ll release you.”

The older man’s expression changed, but his expression soon returned to normal as he asked, “What items?”

The large bald man sinisterly said, “Brother Feng Xiao, doesn’t need to hide it. I’m talking about the Woodbud Flowers.”

The older man bluntly denied, “How could we carry something so rare? Tian Ming, could it be your mind is addled?”

The large man wildly laughed, “It doesn’t matter if you admit it. I’ll be searching for you regardless. Ah yes, I forgot to tell you. Your sacred lord carrying Kun Peng true blood was killed after he was surrounded by three Zheng Zheng Beasts that emerged from the depths. The Flying Spirit Tribe removed the Tian Peng Race as a branch.”

The three were astonished by this news.

The younger Tian Peng man doubtfully said, “Nonsense. The Sacred Kun Peng Lord would be able to escape even if he wasn’t a match. How could three Zheng Zheng Beasts stop him?”

The large bald man flapped his fiery wings and maliciously said, “Hehe, if it were only Zheng Zheng Beasts, they wouldn’t be able to block him, but if he was already injured before and his wings were crippled, he wouldn’t be able to escape.

The older Tian Peng Man remained calm and icily replied, “You think we’ll believe you just like that? Enough nonsense, even if Lord Tian Hua perished, don’t think that we’ll hand over our things.”

Light shined from his other two companions in preparation for a fight.

When the large bald man heard this, he snorted and an ominous glint shined from his eye.

The bald man was a mid Deity Transformation cultivator, and his companions were at early Deity Transformation stage. In addition with the huge two-headed bird, their fighting force was several times greater than the three Tian Peng beings. However, if the Tian Peng beings only focused on escaping, he wasn’t confident they could hold them down.

After all, the Chi Rong Race wasn’t renowned for their speed. If they faced similar grade beings, their prey would most likely escape. However, since the bald man already planned this ambush, he already had something in mind.

A sinister expression flashed on his face as the large man waved his hand.

The other Chi Rong beings flipped their hand and produced a short blue cylinder and pointed it behind them.

With several pops, balls of blue flames shot out.

“Not good! They’re Devil Trapping Cylinders! Go, quickly!” When the older Tian Peng man saw this, he cried out and unfolded his wings without another thought. Silver light burst from his body.

The other two quickly followed him, producing rolls of thunder.

However, it was too slow.

The surrounding balls of blue light suddenly erupted, turning in large blue nets that erupted in size.

In the blink of an eye, the nets fused together and sealed off a kilometer of space in a giant cage.

When the cage was complete, the three flashes of lightning were too slow and hadn’t been able to escape.

When the lightning faded, the three Tian Peng beings wore pale complexions.

When the bald man saw that they trapped the three Tian Peng beings, he happily said, “Although it is the lowest-grade Devil Trapping Net, it’s still enough to hold you down. Feng Xiao, do you truly believe you’ll be able to escape the net as we attack you from all sides.

It would be better to obediently surrender. If you don’t reply, don’t blame me for not trying.”

“Combine our strength and quickly break through the Devil Trapping Net!” The older man, Feng Xiao, expressionlessly commanded his two companions. Soon after, he pinched his hands together and raised them. Two dense bolts of lightning shot out and directly struck the huge blue net.

His younger companions immediately opened their mouths and released dense bolts of lightning to add to the attacks.

Suddenly, several eruptions sounded and a net of blue light fused with silver light, turning the Devil Trapping Net into a blur.

When the bald man saw this, he was thrown into a rage and he furiously shouted, “Attack! Don’t hold anything back!”

Soon after, he blurred through the air and turned into a ten-meter-large scarlet bird. He flapped his wings and immersed himself with flames as he dived to the three Tian Peng beings.

The other Chi Rong beings underwent a similar transformation and began their attack as flame birds.

As a result, the three Tian Peng beings weren’t able to continue their attacks on the Devil Trapping Net and they could only transform into large silver birds, spitting lightning as they confronted their enemy.

For a time, flames roiled and lightning wildly flashed. The nearby air was filled with burning heat and smoke.

Only the huge two-headed bird remained unmoving in place.

Han Li let out a soft sigh, not knowing whether to laugh or cry.

At that moment, the Devil Trapping Net surrounded him as well.

Chapter 1417: Spiritseal Tower

The Tian Peng youth Hua Yu waited for Han Li to take in the huge city and said, “Sir, please follow me!”

Han Li nodded and unfolded the wings on his back. Then he followed the youth to the closest pillar.

On the way, the youth took the initiative to explain, “My lord should be careful not to stray far from the heavenly pillars. The gaps in the city barrier only span a hundred fifty kilometers around the pillars. The city’s Tian Peng restrictions are famous among the seventy-two races of the Flying Spirit Tribe. With these restrictions alone, we can withstand enemies that outnumber us several-fold. Since ancient times, the city restrictions have allowed us to escape extermination time and again.”

The youth spoke with a tone of pride.

Although Han Li didn’t examine the city’s restrictions, the fearsome spiritual pressure of the barrier made him feel the youth’s words were true.

After a blue light flashed wildly from Han Li’s eyes, he began to notice a few remarkable areas.

Deep in the glaring white light above them, he could faintly see floating silver and azure threads of light.

They appeared exceptionally thin, but most of the fearsome spiritual power the barrier was emitting seemed to be coming from these threads.

Han Li took several deep looks at them before following the youth past the side of a huge pillar.

A short moment later, the two appeared inside the huge city.

At a glance, the various buildings in the city greatly differed from human buildings.

The city buildings were all in the shape of cylinders with conical roofs. Their heights all varied with the tallest of them reaching over three hundred meters in height while small ones were only ten meters tall. However, the reach of the buildings had several semicircle arced doors and windows.

What particularly surprised Han Li was that nearly half of the buildings were constructed out of mountain cliffs. There were even caves built out of steep mountain walls that resembled a beehive.

The youth respectfully said, “Sir, the honored guest lodges are spread throughout various areas of the city. Would you like to stay at the closest one? It should be empty.”

“It makes no difference. Let’s do as you say,” Han Li answered indifferently.

“Yes,” the youth uttered a word of acknowledgment and led Han Li at a low altitude, allowing him to take on the many sights in the city. They also brushed past many winged men and women.

Two hours later, they arrived at a large group of buildings and landed on a platform nearby.

The platform was connected to a circular three-story building.

When the two dropped down, two young women with white wings rushed out and saluted them.

“So it was Big Brother Hua Yu. Will this lord be staying at the honored guest lodge?”

When Hua Yu recognized the maid, he solemnly said, “Bai Cui, this is Lord Han. He is an honored guest of Spirit Feng Xiao. Attend to him properly.”

A trace of astonishment appeared on her dainty face and she respectfully answered, “A guest of Spirit Feng Xiao? I will definitely treat this lord well!”

Han Li took a glance at the young woman and noticed that her weak aura was Qi Condensation-grade. He simply nodded and walked into the building.

The young woman lowered her head and closely followed after him.

Hua Yu didn’t dare to enter and simply waited outside for the time being.

A moment later, Han Li’s voice sounded from inside, “This place is to my liking. You may leave.”

The youth felt some relief and uttered a word of farewell before flying off.

On the third floor of the building, Han Li was standing behind a semicircle window and narrowed his eyes as he watched the youth slowly depart. The maid named Bai Cui was standing ten meters behind him in a helpless manner.

Without turning his head, Han Li uttered, “How many people are there in the holy city?”

After a pause of surprise, the woman hastily answered, “The holy city is extremely large. Although there haven’t been detailed accounts, there are at least forty million people.”

“Forty million? That few?” Han Li uttered with a tone of doubt.

The woman hastily explained, “Only those that can cultivate to the point they can take spirit form can enter the city. The clansmen that have lesser cultivation and can’t transform don’t have the qualifications to enter. Although we are one of the weaker branches of the Flying Spirit Tribe, we still total over a billion in number.”

“So it was like that!” Han Li said with a tone of realization.

She stole a glance at Han Li and hesitated for a moment before asking, “My lord, is this your first time in the holy city?”

“Are there many honored guests like me that have entered the holy city for the first time?” Han Li indifferently asked.

The woman carefully explained, “My lord must be joking. Very few people check into the honored guest lodge in the first place, and If they aren’t outer tribesmen that checked in for the first time, they are outer tribesmen that have come to the holy city on business.”

“There is nothing to be surprised about. This is my first time returning to the clan. I’ve always cultivated overseas,” Han Li calmly said. He then asked, “Are there any maps of the holy city on sale? If there is, tell me where and I’ll buy one.”

The maid respectfully said, “There is no need for my lord to head outside and buy a map. There is a particular map that is prepared for the honored guests that reside in the lodge. Its detail is far beyond what is sold.”

Han Li felt surprised, but he promptly commanded, “Oh? That is very good. Go ahead and give me one.”

“Yes, my lord.” The maid took two steps back and swiftly wend downstairs.

Han Li stood in his original place by the window and began to ponder about his plans moving forward.

He wanted to infiltrate the Tian Peng Race so that he could acquire the rare materials that the Flying Spirit Tribe had. As for their treasures and tools, Han Li hadn’t given them much thought. Although he only saw a battle involving the Flying Spirit Tribe, they didn’t seem to rely on treasures and tools too much in combat. It was unknown if they were skilled in tool refinement, or if the high-grade existences in the Flying Spirit Tribe didn’t draw assistance on common tools. The grand treasures like the Devil Trapping Net and the Fire Dragon Pearl only seemed to have an auxiliary nature. However, these still didn’t catch much of his interest. So long as he could acquire some useful materials, the trip here would’ve been worth it.

As for the quarrel between the Tian Peng and the other branches of the Flying Spirit Tribe, he had no interest in involving himself.

While Han Li mulled over these thoughts, the maid returned to the third floor with an emerald-green bamboo tube that was only several inches long. Despite its size, a luster glinted from its surface.

Feeling somewhat shocked, Han Li promptly reached out to the tube that was offered to him.

In a gust of wind, a green streak shot out and arrived in his hand.

Afterwards, he waved his arm at her and she promptly descended after a swift salute.

Alone, Han Li fiddled with the bamboo tube in his hand with great interest. He then sank his spiritual sense into it and saw a huge man clearly etched on the interior of the tube.

The tube was mostly similar to a jade slip, but it was still quite peculiar to produce something similar to a jade slip with refined bamboo. It appeared the Flying Spirit Tribe wasn’t lacking in tool refinement and had their own uniqueness.

In any case, Han Li’s spiritual sense quickly focused on the tube’s interior and concentrated on the image of the map.

In the time it took to finish a meal, he let out a sigh and withdrew his spiritual sense from the tube entirely before wearing a pensive expression.

The holy city was a bit smaller than he expected. It was comparable to a human city that housed a hundred million people. In any case, the city was still astonishingly large. It would take most of a day to fly from one end of the city to another.

Han Li wasn’t very interested in buildings apart from the largest trading hall in the city.

The hall was constructed on a huge mountain at the side of the city. The mountain was where people traded items. It was about the same as a human or demon market.

Apart from this building, Han Li was also curious in a place called the Spirit Transmit Hall. It was where the Tian Peng Hall specialized in supplying a few high-grade cultivation arts to their clansmen.

The map also marked a few forbidden areas. Han Li took note of them and had no interest in pursuing them further.

He then closed his eyes and committed various parts of the map to memory. After going through the information once more, he unfolded his wings and wrapped himself in azure light. He then silently flew out the window directly towards the large trade hall.

The Tian Peng Race wasn’t in a stable situation.

He was unwilling to stay in this place for more than half a month. It’d be best if he gathered the materials he needed and left as soon as he could to save himself from being involved in anything troublesome.

However, Han Li didn’t wish to attract too much attention, so he flew at a slower speed that matched other Tian Peng beings in the city.

Because the trading hall was located at the edge of the city, Han Li only traveled halfway in a quarter hour. At that moment, he spotted a huge tower not far from his front.

It was over two kilometers tall and it wasn’t a commonly seen cylinder. It appeared to be in the shape of an octagon with each side appearing flat and smooth apart from a few particular talisman designs on each side.

These designs emitted a faint black Qi that gave Han Li a familiar feeling. The top of the tower had several three-meter-tall crystals that emitted seven-colored light that covered the tower.

The black Qi was trapped in the rainbow light barrier, preventing it from escaping.

Han Li stroked his chin in surprise.

If he remembered correctly, the tower should be a forbidden area in the city. It was the so-called Spiritseal Tower and was given no description.

There wasn’t a single Tian Peng being that dared to fly three hundred meters within range of the tower.

Chapter 1418: The Tian Peng Holy Disciple and Kun Peng True Blood

“Black Infernal Mist”, a familiar thought flashed through Han Li’s mind.

The black mist that the stone tower emitted was the strange mist that enveloped half of the peninsula he stayed at.

However, the mist from the tower was extremely thin as if it were being strictly controlled.

Han Li felt somewhat alarmed, but since this was a restricted area of the Tian Peng Race, he wasn’t about to provoke anything.

As everyone else did, he flew around the tower.

But as Han Li brushed past the tower, he felt an aura from the tower surge, causing his body to quiver as a cold sensation covered his back.

This is...

Han Li stopped and turned to stare at the huge tower.

He simply saw the huge tower continue to emit Black Infernal Mist. At an unknown time, the mist had become denser with the tower’s talisman marks occasionally flickering with rainbow light. It wasn’t able to completely block the black Qi from rushing it.

Fortunately, the rainbow barrier emitted from the top of the tower completely blocked the black Qi from leaving the vicinity of the tower. But a short moment later, the black Qi caused the seven-colored light barrier to tremble violently as if it could collapse at any moment.

When the nearby Tian Peng beings saw this, they were all dumbstruck and stopped in shock. They all stared at the strange occurrence occurring at the spirit tower.

Han Li then sensed his wings tremble and turned burning hot, creating a scalding pain on his back.

Han Li’s expression vastly changed.

At that moment, an incredibly high-pitched shriek whistled from the tower. When the nearby Tian Peng beings heard this, they began to close their eyes and fall from the sky.

Although Han Li wasn’t as negatively affected, he still felt his spiritual sense become dazed as his burning hot wings immediately lost effect, causing his body to sway.

Fortunately, he could still fly without any reliance on the Thunderstorm Wings. His body promptly flashed with azure light and he steadied himself. Then he looked at the huge tower with horror.

A huge explosion boomed and the crystals on the top of the tower brightly shined, causing the rainbow light barrier to shine as well. At that same moment, overlapping cryptic chants sounded out from the tower as if over a hundred people were chanting a similar incantation simultaneously.

The Tian Peng beings that originally fell then glowed with spiritual light, floating up in the air as a layer of seven-colored light surrounded them.

However, the tower released another piercing shriek and the dense black Qi inside began to roil, forming a kilometer tall huge bird phantom. The hollow figure appeared faintly black. It unfolded its wings to cover the top of the half of the tower and let out a long shriek, causing the black mist to surge several times in size. The surrounding rainbow barrier began to violently warp, exerting a huge pressure.

At that moment, the other Tian Peng beings covered in rainbow light began to shake but otherwise appeared fine. In their fear, however, they began to scatter in every direction.

Han Li originally thought to immediately fly away, but as soon as the huge black bird phantom appeared, his wings trembled. Suddenly, a huge azure bird phantom appeared from a tremble of his wings. It raised its head and cawed in response to the black bird.

Meanwhile, the nearby air became tense and he felt his body grow heavy, suddenly incapable of movement.

In his fright, Han Li emitted brilliant golden light from his body, exerting immense power in his limbs in an attempt to break free. But what immediately caused his heart to sink was in spite of his body’s immense force, he felt the air surrounding him had become as dense as metal. He wasn’t able to even move his finger.

Han Li’s thoughts quickly churned. Just as he thought of using a true devil projection to break free, the incantations coming from the tower changed and became far more clear. The incantation also faintly sounded with booming wind and thunder. Soon after, the strange talisman characters began to appear in the air near the tower and began to float in the black bird’s direction.

As this went on, the huge crystals on the top of the tower ruptured.

A ring of seven-colored suns slowly floated into the air, releasing a brilliant light that covered the black bird phantom.

With the brilliant seven-colored light and the talisman characters restricting the black bird phantom, the phantom could only shriek as it helplessly dispersed.

To the side, the huge azure bird phantom also vanished.

Han Li felt relief at having regained control of his body, but he felt quite bewildered.

Apart from the difference in size and color, the shape from the azure bird phantom and the black hollow phantom appeared exactly the same, like a legendary Kun Peng. Could it be a Kun Peng was sealed in the tower?

As Han Li pondered with shock, he immediately thought to flee from the scene. But when he swept his sights around him, he wryly laughed and decided to stay still.

This was because there were a dozen balls of light that had emerged from the huge tower. In a few flashes, they arrived a hundred meters away from him.

At this distance, he could clearly see Tian Peng beings through the remaining lights. If he fled now, he would be marking himself as guilty.

As he pondered, he decided to wait and see what they would say.

He quickly swept his sights past the lights and found two late-Deity Transformation-grade beings inside of them. The others were only early- and mid-stage beings. Feeling a bit of dread, Han Li didn’t dare to provoke them and remained still in the air.

With several gusts of wind, the dozen beings unfolded their wings and arrived before Han Li in the blink of an eye, surrounding and staring at him.

Of the two old men in charge, one of them had a pair of white wings, while the other had wings that were faintly gold.

One of them also had a kindly face while the other appeared stern, but like all the others, they were firmly staring at Han Li with an odd look.

Although Han Li didn’t truly fear the Tian Peng beings, he felt somewhat apprehensive at this current situation. He forced a smile and asked, “May I ask why you’ve surrounded me?”

Greatly against his expectations, the white-winged old man respectfully asked, “Brother, what is your esteemed name? Your face is quite unfamiliar. Are you kin that has recently entered the holy city?”

With a few quick thoughts, Han Li answered, “My surname is Han. I’ve cultivated overseas and have only entered the city today.”

Seeing that the Tian Peng beings didn’t reveal any hostile intentions, he decided to give an answer.

“You’re from overseas? And you only entered the city today?” Han Li’s answer greatly shocked the old men, but they soon exchanged a glance and wore an expression of joy.

The stern old man solemnly said, “Good, very good! Regardless of where Brother Han came from, your Tian Peng Qi is quite abundant to provoke the Kung Peng spirit in the tower. You could receive the title of Holy Disciple and inherit the Kun Peng True Blood.”

“The Tian Peng True Blood!” Han Li was shocked.

If it was before, Han Li wouldn’t have understood what they meant, but with the True Dragon and Heavenly Phoenix True Blood in his bracelet, he realized how rare this item was.

Han Li was startled that such fortune had appeared before him.

But with another thought, Han Li felt lacking in confidence.

He wasn’t truly a Tian Peng being. How could he become their holy disciple? Under closer inspection, his disguise would be revealed. He wouldn’t inherit any true blood, but would be provoking the hatred and ire of countless Tian Peng beings.

Han Li dryly chuckled and shook his head, “You’ve made a mistake. I come from an ordinary background. How would I have the qualifications to inherit the true blood? It wasn’t me who provoked the scene at the tower.”

The gold-winged old man seemed to ignore Han Li’s words and smiled, saying, “There is no need for Brother Han to shirk this away. A true spirit projection had appeared from your body. Those of us from the tower had clearly seen it. We weren’t mistaken. Brother Han must see the elders. Being able to become a holy disciple is a matter of the utmost importance.”

Han Li inwardly cursed and looked around. He saw the Tian Peng beings looking at him with excitement and determination.

“I truly am not any holy disciple. It’s fine if you don’t believe me. However, I have important matters to attend to, so I must bid farewell.” Han Li resolved himself and quickly uttered a few words before vanishing in a blur.

He flapped his wings, wanting to use his abilities to fly a distance away, but at that moment, he heard a woman’s voice.

“Outsider, wait! Do you truly plan to leave? If you do, hand over your wings to us.” The voice wasn’t loud but soft and sweet. When Han Li heard it, he felt as if his spiritual sense shook with astonishing thunder and his face turned unsightly.

As soon as those words were uttered, a nearby space fluctuated and a slender figure silently appeared ten meters above him. It was a white-robed woman with golden wings.

Han Li stared at her and felt his blood run cold.

She had an ordinary appearance, but a glistening light was roaming across her body. From her aura, he felt that her cultivation was unfathomably deep. She was a mid-stage Body Integration-grade presence.

Han Li widely opened his eyes.

“We pay our respects to the grand elder!” The Deity Transformation-grade Tian Peng beings respectfully saluted the young woman as soon as she appeared.

This woman was actually the Tian Peng Race’s grand elder.

Han Li felt his mouth dry up.

The woman calmly commanded, “Let me deal with this person. You should return to the tower and strengthen the seal, pacifying the Holy Kun Peng Spirit in turn.”

“As you command!” As a clear display of their respect, they immediately followed their orders and returned.

The young woman then turned her sights on Han Li.

Chapter 1420: The Trade Hall

The young woman calmly said, “That’s right. Although you do have the qualifications to join our Tian Peng race, you are a human after all. Even if you pass through the trial, it is impossible for you to become our race’s holy master. However, Fellow Daoist Han can provide support to the other two holy disciples as a fellow holy disciple and help them pass the trial. If you agree, I won’t treat you unfairly. Not only can you fuse a bit of Kun Peng True Blood into you, but we’ll thank you in other ways as well.”

Such fortune would cause an ordinary person to rejoice and promptly agree, but Han Li simply blinked and didn’t immediately answer.

The young woman didn’t urge him and simply remained seated as she stared at him.

In the time it took to finish a cup of tea, Han Li eventually said, “For the matter of being a holy disciple, Senior would have an outsider like me enter your race. The trial must be quite dangerous. Could you first give me an explanation?”

“It is true the trial is quite dangerous. The various race’s disciples have a sixty to seventy percent chance of failure and injury. Furthermore, the holy disciple’s cultivation must be at the level of a Flying Spirit General, what is known to you humans as the Deity Transformation-stage. But now, our Holy Master has unexpectedly perished, and our holy disciples are only early Spirit General-stage. They still aren’t prepared.

If they attempt the trial, they will most likely fail. Although I don’t know much about your abilities, since you were able to cross most of the Tian Yuan Continent over here, your strength should be significant. Even with the danger in the trial, it shouldn’t be a problem for you.”

Han Li’s eyes stirred and he solemnly asked, “They are only at the stage of a Spirit General?”

“Don’t worry, I won't trick you.” The young woman smiled.

With a moment of thought, Han Li eventually said, “I’ll need some time to consider it.”

The young woman appeared calm as if having expected this answer. “The matter is extremely important, so consideration is expected. How about this? I’ll give you three days before I expect your answer. During this time, you are free to roam the city and no one will come to bother you. Furthermore, I’m named Jin Yue. Remember that name.”

Han Li uttered a word of thanks and bid farewell without any hesitation.

When Han Li left, he blurred and vanished without a trace. Jin Yue smiled and sipped the teacup that was on the table.

“Grand Elder, did you truly release him?” Grey light flashed from the wall and two Tian Peng beings appeared.

Jin Yue glanced at a tall red-bearded old man and asked, “What? How did you think I’d treat that person?”

The lofty red-bearded old man rubbed his hands and said, “There is no need for us to pass off the foreign being as our holy disciple. Wouldn’t it be better to force him to leave behind the wings and select someone better to inherit the true blood?”

The young woman sneered and bluntly answered, “If it were that easy, why would I go through the trouble of saying that to a foreign being. I would just kill him and take the wings away.”

The petite beautiful woman standing at the old man’s side hastily fixed her jacket and respectfully said, “Then the Grand Elder means...”

Jin Yue pondered for a moment and explained, “I hold the most understanding of humans among the entirety of the Tian Peng. The humans are different from us in which their body’s powers are common and most of their abilities lie in the treasures they’ve refined. Furthermore, they can temper their treasures for long periods and thoroughly refine them with themselves. We can take it away and possess it, but it will be difficult to rid the treasure of the original master’s markings in a short amount of time. Furthermore, the treasure’s might will greatly decrease from when it was used by its original owner. I’ve already inspected the treasure to verify this. With the information I have and the trial of the holy disciple soon being imminent, we don’t have the time to seize his treasure and bestow it to our kin.”

The red-bearded old man shook his head. “So it was like that. But even so, must we hand over the True Ancestor’s Blood to this outsider? This isn’t some small matter.”

A clear glint shined from the young woman’s eyes, “Elder Xu, are you confused? If our race doesn’t pass the trial of the holy disciple, the entire race will be absorbed by the other branches. Giving him some true blood is minor in comparison. Besides, we can consider other options to prevent this from happening.”

The dainty middle-aged woman was startled for a moment and smiled, “Hehe, the Grand Elder’s words are reasonable. After this outsider helps us through this calamity, this Spirit General-grade existence will be completely at our mercy.”

Jin Yue coldly glanced at the beautiful woman and emotionlessly said, “We cannot kill him. Even if he is a foreign being, he’s fused Kun Peng True Blood into his body and can be considered half our kin. Our Tian Peng vows will restrict us. Furthermore, he will be our benefactor if he truly aids us through calamity. If it isn’t necessary, we mustn't harm him, but we’ll be able to restrict him in other ways. From now on, he won’t be able to leave the holy city.”

The red-bearded old man said, “So that’s the case. Should we inform the gatekeepers or send people to follow the outsider in secret to keep him from escaping?”

Jin Yue aloofly said, “There is no need for Elder Xu to worry. I’ve performed a small trick on his wings. If he wants to escape the city, I’ll immediately know about it.”

The beautiful woman’s eyes brightly lit up and she grinned, “It seems we’ve been worrying too much.”

“That isn’t so. Our clan has five grand elders and only three of us are in the present. The matter concerning our clan’s existence is something that we must deliberate. I wouldn’t have secretly called you over here otherwise. Do either of you have any objections?”

“No, the Grand Elder’s method is reliable.” Both the beautiful woman and the old man readily agreed.

The young woman nodded in response.

From the very beginning, none of the three Tian Peng elders had even considered that Han Li would refuse.

This came as no surprise. After all Han Li was only a Deity Transformation-grade outsider. How could he refuse their request?

At that moment, hundreds of kilometers away, Han Li was flying at a low altitude.

Although his expression was ordinary and he appeared at the various buildings below him with interest, he was inwardly pondering about his dilemma.

He had carelessly exposed his identity and found himself in a bad situation.

With his rich experience, he figured that no matter if he completed the young woman’s request, the result definitely wouldn’t be good for him.

A bold refusal definitely wouldn’t be possible.

As for immediately escaping, the thought had already surfaced in his mind several times.

But after he swept his spiritual sense past his wings, he could only wryly laugh.

The Tian Peng Grand Elder had brazenly placed a marking on the wings. Within a certain area, she’d be able to find him without a doubt.

And he wouldn’t be able to erase the mark at his current cultivation. At the very least, he’d need to spend many days. The Grand Elder could find him countless times during the duration.

It appeared his only option would be to negotiate a few conditions to protect himself.

Otherwise, it’d be better to take the risk to flee than to become the holy disciple of foreign race.

As for the conditions, he would properly deliberate them once he understood the general circumstances surrounding the Tian Peng Race.

Fortunately, he’s already encountered danger countless times and managed to keep calm even under such a dilemma.

As Han Li slowly flew, thoughts quickly flickered through his mind.

After some time, Han Li arrived at a lofty bookstore in the holy city.

He spent an entire day looking through a small half of the books there before departing with a tired expression.

When he returned to his residence, Han Li shut himself in the honored guest lodge until the morning of the third day. He departed with his objective being the large trade hall that he wanted to go from the very start.

He hadn’t encountered any trouble along the way.

As Han Li flew, he eventually arrived at the edge of the holy city and stood in front of a strangely constructed building.

The building was constructed next to a three-kilometer-tall mountain cliff, and in the cliff, a huge rectangular plaza was carved out of it. At the end of the plaza, there was a three-hundred-meter-tall arched gate embedded on top of the mountain wall.

To either side of the arch, a dozen armed guards were standing in formation. Between them, countless Tian Peng beings rushed to and fro the gate.

Han Li simply examined them from a distance for a moment. Then, his wings stirred and he flew among them in a ball of azure light.

A guard in front of the gate noticed Han Li. His expression faintly changed before he gave Han Li a deep salute.

Han Li nodded to him and boldly walked through.

He walked through and saw the space before him brightly light up.

There seemed to be an entirely different world past the gate.

At a glance, he saw long passages that seemingly had no end. There were also lines to lofty buildings that appeared to be walls. Under closer examination, the halls seemed to have over ten stores with each story being a hundred meters tall. And every three hundred meters in width, there would be a thirty-meter tall hall entrance.

Countless Tian Peng beings were flying back and forth, up and down. It appeared this was where the Tian Peng Race traded.

Chapter 1423: The Kun Peng Relic and the Tian Peng Vow

"Have you agreed to join our Tian Peng Race?" A young woman asked with a pair of bright shimmering eyes.

"I won't be allowed to leave if I don't agree, right?" Han Li sighed in a resigned manner.

At this moment, he was situated within a pavilion with this young woman, along with an elderly man and another beauty.

These two new early-Body Integration Stage Tian Peng Race elders were currently appraising the Thunderstorm Wings on his back with scorching yearning in their eyes.

"You've made a wise decision, Fellow Daoist Han. As long as our race's holy disciple can pass the trial, we'll be sure to repay you." The young woman's voice was filled with elation, but her calm tone also suggested that she had already predicted Han Li's answer well in advance.

"If the trial really is as you describe, then I really haven't offered much assistance here. However, at the same time, I don't want to be completely at your mercy once I've outlived my usefulness, so I have two conditions. I hope you can accept those two conditions so I can assist your race's holy disciple without any qualms or concerns," Han Li suddenly said.

"Conditions? Go on, then," the elderly man prompted with furrowed brows.

"I want a Kun Peng Relic, as well as the right to record my name on the replica scroll of the Tian Peng Vow," Han Li replied with a faint smile.

"You know of those things?" All three Tian Peng beings' expression changed drastically in unison upon hearing this.

"That's impossible! Our race only has a dozen or so Kun Peng Relics in total, and every one of them was left behind by our race's past grand elders when they passed away; how could we give one to you? As for the Tian Peng Vow, our race only has three replica scrolls, and there's no space on them for you to record your name," the elderly man immediately refused with a dark expression.

"Indeed, those two items are both extremely valuable to our race. Would you be willing to accept any other conditions?" the beautiful woman among the trio asked.

The young woman didn't say anything, but she wore a contemplative look on her face."I'm not asking for the Kun Peng Relic solely for myself. Only after consuming the relic will I be able to grasp the power of the Kun Peng and manifest a Kun Peng body. Only then will I be able to pose as your race's holy disciple and not have my cover blown by other races. With the relic in addition to the Kun Peng feather and Kun Peng true blood that I've fused with my body, I should have the right to record my name on a replica scroll of the Tian Peng vow. That's the only way to show me that your race doesn't harbor any ill will toward me after the event," Han Li said in a calm voice.

"How do you know of these things? Did someone in our race disclose this information to you?" the elderly man asked with a steely expression.

"That shouldn't be the case. Fellow Daoist Han stayed for an entire day within the Omniscient Pavilion in the city, so he most likely gathered this information from the books in there. I almost forgot that all humans can possess eidetic memories once they reach a high enough cultivation base," Jin Yue said in a calm voice.

"Even so, we absolutely cannot accept these conditions." The elderly man shook his head in a stubborn manner.

"Why not? If a holy master doesn't appear among your race during this trial, you'll most likely be removed from the 72 branches of the Flying Spirit Race, and you'll be forcibly conquered by other more powerful branches. Compared to that, I think what I'm asking for is very reasonable, unless the three of you were planning to turn on me after the event from the very beginning," Han Li said in a slow voice.

Both the elderly man and the beautiful woman's expressions darkened upon hearing this.

After a brief silence, Jin Yue suddenly said, "Alright, I accept your conditions."

"You can't..."

"Grand Elder, we should discuss this matter in greater depth!"

Both of the other elders hurriedly tried to dissuade her.

"There's no need for further discussion. It's just as Fellow Daoist Han has said, this crisis could quite possibly spell the downfall of our race. In contrast, his conditions are indeed very reasonable. I'm making an executive decision here; speak no further on this matter," Jin Yue said in a cold voice as she raised a hand toward the two elders.

The two elders glanced at one another hesitantly upon hearing this, but they decided to keep their mouths shut in the end.

"I can accept the conditions you stated, but in order to ensure that you'll do everything in your power to assist our two holy disciples to pass the trial, I'll need you to sign a blood vow. If no holy master emerged from our race following the conclusion of the trial, as the Grand Elder, I can sacrifice some of my lifespan to remove you from the Tian Peng Vow, then kill you on the spot." Jin Yue's gaze suddenly became as sharp as daggers.

Han Li's heart stirred slightly in response, but he merely put on a faint smile, and said, "Rest assured, Senior. If the holy disciples fail to pass the trial due to lack of effort on my part, then I'm willing to accept any punishment you hand down to me."

"Good. Go back and prepare; I'll send someone to get you tomorrow so we can hold your spirit initiation ceremony and officially welcome you into our race," the young woman said in an implacable voice.

Han Li naturally had no objections, and he immediately cupped his fist in a farewell salute to the tree elders before departing.

The elderly man looked on as Han Li exited the room, then took a deep breath and exhaled before turning to Jin Yue with a heavy expression. "Grand Elder, I still oppose this course of action. I can accept giving him the Kun Peng Relic, but if we record his name onto the replica scrolls of the Tian Peng Vow, none of our brethren will be able to do anything to him unless he commits the few extremely severe crimes listed in the vow. Beings from foreign races could easily use this against us and bring calamity to our race."

"I'm naturally aware of this. However, you seem to have forgotten something, Elder Xu. The Tian Peng Vow can only restrict our brethren; have you forgotten about that traitor from 3,000 years ago?" A peculiar look appeared on Jin Yue's face as she spoke.

"Could it be..." The beautiful woman among the trio was beginning to understand where this was going.

Jin Yue gently stroked her hair as she replied, "A few days ago, I met the Flying Spirit Generals that have recently returned to the city with the worshipful offerings, and I learned some things about that human from them. According to them, this human cultivator appears to only possess the cultivation base of a mid-Flying General, but he's actually at least as powerful as an early-Great Spirit General. With him on our side, our holy disciples are virtually guaranteed to pass the trial, so I'm willing to make these concessions. Furthermore, when all is said and done, as long as this human is willing to stay in our holy city and doesn't come into contact with any of his brethren, we don't have to resort to that final step. What we do have to be wary of is those enemies of our race plotting against us during the trial."

"Your wisdom is unmatched, Grand Elder!" The two elders were greatly reassured.

On the other end, Han Li had just arrived back at his residence when he encountered a few visitors.

They were none other than Feng Xiao, Bai Lei, and Bai Ning, who had returned to the city with him.

The three of them greeted Han Li in a very warm and enthusiastic manner and stayed to chat with him for the better part of half a day before departing.

After seeing off this trio of siblings, Han Li's smile faded as he returned to the room with a contemplative look on his face and closed the doors.

Sure enough, eight Tian Peng beings came to find him the next morning, four of which were male while the other four were female. Even though their cultivation bases were only at the Foundation Establishment Stage, they were all very young, so their aptitudes were quite brilliant.

After casting a glance at the eight of them, Han Li didn't say anything as he departed behind them toward a certain location in the holy city.

After flying over more than half of the entire city, Han Li appeared within a strange building situated on a corner of the city almost half a day later.

This building was a massive plaza that kind of resembled an arena. The entire plaza was circular in shape and was surrounded by massive stone walls that were roughly 1,000 feet tall, taking up an area of several kilometers.

Atop those stone walls stood hundreds of stone bird statues, and all of them were flashing with different colors of light. They had clearly had some kind of restriction placed on them, and the light emanating from the statues combined to form a rainbow barrier of light that enshrouded the entire plaza.

At the center of the plaza stood a sacrificial-altar-like tall platform that was entirely constructed from pristine and flawless white jade.

Han Li currently stood atop the jade platform with a dozen or so white-robed Tian Peng beings standing around him in a solemn and intimidating manner. There were both men and women among them, and all of them were at the Spatial Tempering Stage.

Jin Yue and the three Tian Peng Race elders stood right in front of Han Li while a pair of young women who appeared to be servants stood behind them, holding a silver disk each.

"Fellow Daoist Han, all of the preparations have been made. In order to completely activate the power of the Kun Peng Relic and Kun Peng Blood within you prior to the commencement of the trial, the two elders and I will be unleashing our abilities to assist you in refining those two items in a short time. We'll then be bestowing upon you the transformation technique of our Tian Peng Race. I hope you won't disappoint us, Fellow Daoist Han," Jin Yue said as she looked directly into Han Li's eyes.

"Rest assured, Senior. I've already made a promise to all of you, so I'll definitely do everything within my power to assist the holy disciples," Han Li replied in a serious manner.

"Good. Fuse the Kun Peng True Blood into your body first and Elder Xu will activate the power of the spirit blood, then forcibly fuse it with your blood so that they become one and the same. The process will be a little painful, but I'm sure you'll be able to handle it. After that, you can consume the Kun Peng Relic, and I'll personally assist you in refining the relic. You have to take care during this process not to suffer backlash and go into Qi deviation from the power of the relic. After all, you're not a true Tian Peng being, so this procedure may be rather perilous," Jin Yue cautioned.

Han Li naturally nodded in response.

Han Li's willingness to cooperate was very pleasing for Jin Yue, and she also nodded before waving a hand behind her.

One of the female servants immediately made her way over to Jin Yue in a respectful manner before offering the silver disk in her hand to the grand elder.

Jin Yue took an indifferent glance at the silver disk before flicking a slim finger toward the screen of light.

White light flashed erratically before disappearing soundlessly to reveal a small thumb-sized azure vial. The vial was rather antiquated and appeared to be made from neither metal nor jade.

Jin Yue looked at the small vial as faint silver light flashed from her body, and her expression suddenly became extremely solemn and dignified.

Meanwhile, all of the other Tian Peng beings bowed in unison toward the small vial with expressions of awe and veneration on their faces.

Chapter 1426: Xumi Paradise

Aside from the thin shopkeeper and the armor-clad man who had just spoken, there was also a young man with a set of delicate facial features present, and he also wore an expression of displeasure on his face.

Han Li surreptitiously swept his spiritual sense toward them to find that these two were both early-Spatial Tempering cultivators.

"Hmph, I never said that I was only going to bring one person with me to help me tame the spirit beast. If anyone wants to leave, feel free to do so. However, don't even think about my Iceheart Crystal, Purple Light Iron, and Azure Shifting Fruit, then," the shopkeeper rolled his eyes with a cold harrumph.

The young man and the armor-clad man glanced at once another upon hearing this while Han Li stood on the spot with slightly furrowed brows.

"Alright, so be it. However, if one of us manages to help you tame the spirit beast first, then wouldn't that mean the other two will have to walk away emptyhanded?" the young man asked.

"Hehe, don't worry about that; I never intended for the three of you to act independently. Instead, all of you are going to need to unleash your lightning powers at once. Otherwise, according to my prior experience, the lightning powers that any single one you possess won't be anywhere near enough. If you three can help me successfully tame the spirit beast, then I'll give all of you the items I promised," the shopkeeper chuckled coldly.

The young man and the armor-clad man's expressions eased upon hearing this, and neither of them raised any further objections.

The shopkeeper nodded with a pleased expression before turning to Han Li, and a look of surprise appeared on his face.

"Brother Han, it's only been several days since we last met, and you've already progressed from a mid-Spirit General to a late-Spirit General. That's truly incredible. I must offer you my congratulations. With your recent progression, your lightning powers will have become even more powerful, right?"

"Thank you for your kind words, Senior. I was merely lucky to have reached this point. As for my lightning powers, they have indeed been enhanced somewhat," Han Li replied half-truthfully with a faint smile on his face.

The armor-clad man and the young man also turned to Han Li with surprise in their eyes upon hearing this conversation.

"Good. Seeing as none of you have any objections, then come with me. I've hidden the spirit beast away in an obscure location," the shopkeeper said.

"I have no objections there, but before this, shouldn't you show us the items that you promised us?" the young man asked.

The armor-clad man faltered upon hearing this before chiming in in agreement. Han Li didn't say anything, but the expression on his face clearly indicated that he also supported this notion.

The shopkeeper seemed to have anticipated this request, and he said, "No problem. I've already prepared the items in advance, so I'd be happy to show them to you now." The ease with which the shopkeeper accepted this request came as a stark contrast to usual stinginess, and the young man was clearly taken aback, having already prepared a response for a refusal from the shopkeeper.

Three wooden boxes of different sizes were hurled through the air, and it appeared that the shopkeeper really was planning to show them the items he'd promised them.

The young man and the armor-clad man were both ecstatic. They swept their sleeves through the air, sending forth swaths of light that caught the oncoming wooden boxes.

Han Li's heart jolted as he also caught the box flying toward him before removing its lid.

A mesmerizing medicinal aroma wafted toward him, and a green fist-sized fruit sat within the box. There were even a couple of strange red leaves under the fruit, and Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly as he extended a finger toward the fruit.

The other two people also reached for the items in their respective boxes so they could conduct a more thorough examination.

However, right at this moment, the shopkeeper suddenly warned, "I wouldn't do that if I were you. All of the items in the boxes have restrictions set up on them. If any mishaps occur, you won't be able to pay for those things even if you give me everything you own."

All three of them immediately faltered upon hearing this.

The armor-clad man was a little enraged as he grumbled, "What are you trying to do, Brother Yu? How are we supposed to be able to ascertain the authenticity of these items without touching them?"

"With your cultivation bases, you'll have a 70% to 80% chance of verifying these items using your eyes and spiritual sense alone. If you want to completely assess the authenticity of these items, then you'll have to wait until after the event. If the three of you are unable to help me tame the spirit beast, then there won't be any need for you to verify the items. Besides, with my reputation, are you really concerned that I would try to deceive you?" the middle-aged man replied in a nonchalant manner.

The young man stared at the item in the box for a long while before finally making a decision and tossing the box back to the shopkeeper. "Alright, we'll trust you on this one. I'm sure Brother Yu wouldn't risk ruining his own reputation over something like this."

The armor-clad man carefully examined the object in his box with a hesitant look, but still reluctantly handed over the box in the end.

After stowing away the two wooden boxes, a pleased look appeared on the shopkeeper's face before he turned toward Han Li.

At this moment, Han Li was staring at the azure fruit in the box with blue light shimmering deep within his eyes and a contemplative look on his face.

The shopkeeper faltered slightly upon seeing this before asking, "What is it? Are you of the opinion that something is amiss with the Azure Shifting Fruit, Brother Han?"

"Not at all." Han Li shook his head before replacing the lid on the wooden box and tossing it to the shopkeeper as well.

The middle-aged man caught the wooden box before taking another meaningful glance at Han Li, then leading the way out the door.

Han Li's trio naturally followed him out of the shop.

The shopkeeper flew extremely quickly, but Han Li's trio were all powerful cultivators in their own right, and they were able to keep up with ease, flying out of the exchange center before heading directly toward a certain direction in the holy city.

After flying for two hours, they arrived in an extremely secluded corner of the holy city.

There were noticeably far fewer buildings here, and very few people in the area. It was quite a sparsely populated place, and the shopkeeper led them on a descent after arriving at a completely mundane looking short building.

This nondescript building was only just over 300 feet tall, and it was split up into two levels.

As soon as the shopkeeper's feet landed on the ground, the doors of the building were immediately flung open, and two men who appeared to be in their twenties emerged from within. They hurriedly extended respectful bows toward the shopkeeper, and greeted in unison, "Welcome back, Patriarch!"

"The two of you, stand guard out here. No one is allowed to enter this place without my permission," the shopkeeper ordered.

"Yes!" the two men answered without any hesitation before positioning themselves on either side of the building's entrance. Han Li glanced at the two of them and paid them no further heed after discovering that they were merely Core Formation cultivators.

Meanwhile, the shopkeeper had already entered the building, and the young man and armor-clad man followed suit after a brief hesitation while Han Li brought up the rear.

The room wasn't a very spacious one, and all of the decor appeared to be quite plain and mundane. There were three square wooden tables and a dozen or so wooden chairs, and those pieces of furniture took up most of the area in the room.

There were also several antiquated artworks that were yellow with age hanging on the walls of the room. All of these pieces of artwork depicted demons beasts and scenery, and they weren't very noteworthy, either.

"Brother Yu, is that spirit beast really here?" the armor-clad man couldn't help but ask. This room was quite small, and it really didn't appear as if it could house any powerful spirit beasts, so it was no wonder that the man was having some doubts.

"Would I lie to you three? Come with me," the shopkeeper instructed in a brisk tone as he glared at the armor-clad man. He then made his way over to one of the scenery paintings hanging from one of the walls, and he rustled his sleeve to produce a scroll.

The scroll was unfurled to reveal the exact same scene depicted in the artwork on the wall.

Han Li and the armor-clad man both faltered upon seeing this, unable to comprehend what the shopkeeper was doing. However, the young man's expression changed drastically as he caught sight of the two pieces of artwork, and he exclaimed, "That's the Xumi Paradise Scroll! You're in possession of the Pentaluster Race's most prized treasure?"

"The Xumi Scroll? No way! Aren't there only a total of seven of those in the Pentaluster Race? How did you manage to obtain one, Brother Yu?" The armor-clad man was very startled to hear this.

Han Li had no idea what this treasure was, but his heart stirred upon hearing the word "Xumi" as he cast his gaze toward the artwork hanging on the wall.

The slightly yellow artwork depicted a small green mountain, and there was a small cluster of buildings on that mountain, but everything was rather blurry and indistinct.

"Hehe, you sure have a strong discerning eye. This is indeed a Xumi Paradise Scroll. However, it's not one of the seven scrolls that the Pentaluster Race view as their most prized treasure; this is an imperfect Xumi Scroll," the shopkeeper chuckled.

"So it's a replica?" Both the young man and the armor-clad man faltered upon hearing this.

A smug expression appeared on the shopkeeper's face as he replied, "Indeed. There aren't many people even in the Pentaluster Race who are aware of its existence. Back then, the Pentaluster Race used the spirit bones of a Five-Colored Phoenix to refine a total of 10 Xumi Paradise Scrolls, not seven. Unfortunately, three of them were flawed, and their effectiveness was severely hampered as a result. As such, those three scrolls were hidden very early on, and their existence wasn't revealed to the rest of the world. Due to various reasons, those three scrolls somehow ended up outside of the Pentaluster Race and switched hands between several other races. As for how I came about this one, that's not something the three of you need to know."

"Even though it's a flawed scroll, obtaining such a treasure is a vast fortune, Brother Yu," the armor-clad man said with an envious expression.

The young man stared at the scroll, and a hint of greed flashed through his eyes.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged, but he was also filled with a sense of yearning.

Xumi treasures were one of the treasures that he wanted to obtain the most after arriving in this Spirit Realm. Unlike the false Xumi space refined using spatial rifts in the human world, this was an independent existence, and was a true spatial treasure that could be carried.

"Alright, let's go. The spirit beast is in the Xumi Paradise." The smile on the shopkeeper's face suddenly faded as he abruptly rustled his sleeve.

An incredible scene then ensued.

Brilliant five-colored light abruptly erupted from the scroll before transforming into a vast expanse of light that disappeared into the artwork on the wall.

The shopkeeper began to chant something while abruptly pointing a finger at the artwork on the wall.

The same five-colored spiritual light also flashed from the scroll before a swath of light emanated from it.

The five-colored light swept up everyone in the room at the shopkeeper's behest. Following a brief hesitation, Han Li relinquished his resistance in the end and allowed the light to enshroud his entire body, but he surreptitiously injected more power into the protective layer of spiritual light around him.

Following another flash of five-colored light, the room was completely devoid of any people.

Chapter 1432: Tian Peng Holy Disciple

After an unknown time had passed, the gentle young man woke up with a splitting headache.

After he opened his eyes, he immediately jumped up out of alarm and noticed Han Li and the black-armored man who earlier regained consciousness.

According to his last memories, the youth couldn't help but shout with fury, “What happened? I last remember that Old Traitor Yu didn’t give us any treasure and instead used the Lightning Drawing Bead on us.”

The large man shook his head, still feeling somewhat muddled. He sat up cross-legged and immediately examined himself with his spiritual sense.

A short moment later, he let out a long sigh, “How lucky. I’ve only lost a bit of vitality. Nothing too bad.”

Han Li lowered his head in silence and his eyes wandered as if he were pondering.

The gentle youth looked at Han Li and the large man and said, “Do you two know what happened afterwards?”

The large man wryly laughed, “Not much. When I was hit by that rainbow lightning, my soul was shaken and I lost consciousness.”

The youth turned to Han Li and said, “Brother Han, I recall that you’ve discovered that traitor’s scheme and didn’t fall into the Lightning Drawing Bead.”

Han Li sighed and said, “As a mere Flying Spirit General, how could I truly escape? Although I dodged the rainbow lightning, the Lightning Beast attacked me and was knocked out like you two.”

“You were attacked by the lightning beast? That’s right, the beast should’ve been possessed by the traitor with the crystal core. He definitely would’ve been able to control its body for a short amount of time.”

The black-armored man said with an odd expression, “The strange part is why would the traitor leave us here when he turned hostile.”

“That is strange! Most likely, the traitor saw that we succeeded and didn’t want to give anything. I found it strange that he would trade such rare items for subjugating a spirit beast. He originally planned on denying us from the start. Fancy that his Myriad Lightning Shop was so famous in the holy city.”

Han Li nodded, “If he only wished to deny us treasure, it isn’t necessary to kill us. However, while we were unconscious, he escaped.”

When the large man heard this, he grew pensive and accepted this idea.

A cold glint flashed from the youth’s eyes and he resentfully said, “We cannot allow that traitor to escape. Let’s go to his residence, even if he managed to get away. We might be able to get some clues.”

The black-armored man hesitated before agreeing, but Han Li shook his head, “My cultivation is too low. It is fortunate that we still have our lives. I don’t want to investigate the matter further so I’ll be bidding you two Seniors farewell.”

The large man and the youth couldn't help but glance at each other in surprise.

The young man gritted his teeth and said, “Brother Han, are you really going to use that done when that traitor played us? Your lightning techniques are quite unordinary, so you should be someone of significant background. Even if the traitor’s cultivation is far beyond ours, his vitality must’ve been greatly damaged when he extracted the soul of the Lightning Beast. If we joined hands, we have nothing to fear. And if that won’t do, we can make a report to the elders. Although he possesses some cultivation, would he dare to resist the clan elders?”

The large black-armored man said, “The clan elders? There is no need to alarm them? Let’s deal with the matter ourselves.”

Han Li calmly shook his head, “Forget about it. I have other important matters in the holy city. I may as well take care of both matters while I’m there. Since this matter can’t be changed, I won’t be paying much attention to it. Seniors, I will bid you farewell.” He then saluted the two and soared to the sky with the wings on his back, taking off in an azure streak.

The young man looked at Han Li flying away with a sullen expression and turned to the large man, “He can’t recognize the kindness of others. So long as we can find that traitor, the two of us will be able to deal with him.”

“Hehe, a mere Flying Spirit General is still something, not much or little.” Feeling somewhat worried, the large black-armored man said, “However, since that Old Traitor Yu dares to turn back on his word, he must have something prepared. Our chances aren’t very high.”

“If we don’t investigate, how do we know if we can’t block him,” the youth shook his head.

The large man hummed several times, “That sounds reasonable. Let’s go.”

Soon after, the two flew in the direction of the shopkeeper’s residence.

At that moment, Han Li was boldly returning to the honored guest lodge and tossed the matter to the back of his mind.

Over the next few days, Han Li sat cross-legged in the building and continuously drank medicine pills to consolidate his late Deity Transformation-stage cultivation. Meanwhile, he spent great efforts to comprehend the Tian Peng’s transformation technique.

From his efforts, he grasped the transformation technique to the point of perfection. He would be able to use it in a real battle.

As time slowly passed by, two months quickly passed.

One day, as Han Li sat cross-legged on his bed with azure waves of light roaming around him, his expression suddenly stirred and his eyes opened.

At nearly the same time, a bright voice leisurely spoke from the outside, “I am Bai Bi. Grand Elder Feng has given me orders to invite you.”

Han Li narrowed his eyes for a moment before wearing a normal expression.

His body moved with an unnatural swiftness as he stood to his feet.

Ever since he cultivated the Tian Peng Transformation Art, he felt his body become far nimbler and his body techniques have seen an improvement as well.

Han Li pushed open his door and walked out, heading directly to the main hall.

When he arrived at the hall, there was a yellow-clothed young man with his hands held behind his back.

The youth didn’t look particularly handsome, but his eyes were clear. When he saw Han Li arrive, he amiably asked, “Are you Senior Han? Under Grand Elder Feng’s orders, I’ve come to remind you to leave.” He spoke with complete and free ease despite only possessing early Deity Transformation cultivation.

Han Li glanced at the youth and smiled, “Bai Bi? It seems your bearing is unordinary. You should be one of the two holy disciples.”

Bai Bi saluted Han Li with a smile and said, “I am ashamed. I have failed the deep favor of the elders as one of the holy disciples. I have come to know a bit about Brother Han’s circumstances from a few of the elders. I must thank Brother Han for his assistance, or else an elder close to me may find their lives in danger.”

“You mean to say...” Han Li wore an expression of surprise.

The youth smiled and said, “My uncle Bai Lei and my Aunt, Bai Ning.”

“You’re Brother Bai Lei’s nephew.” Han Li looked at the shining golden wings on the young man’s back and wore an odd expression on his face.

Sensing Han Li’s doubt, Bai Bi explained with a smile, “There is no need for Brother Han to feel baffled. It was only after I came of age did I arouse the Kun Peng True Bloodline hidden in my body. That is why my wings changed color.”

“So it was like that. Your luck must’ve been quite good,” Han Li chuckled.

Soon after, he followed the Tian Peng holy disciple away from the residence.

Four hours later, Han Li arrived at an imposing hall made of white stone. The hall was serene and had a white stone table and a row of five stone chairs to either side of it.

Apart from Yin Yue, the red-bearded old man, and the beautiful woman, there was also a tall and thin man wearing black robes.

A dark Qi faintly emitted from the man’s body, concealing his face entirely. He also had a pair of black wings that shined with black light.

The stone table had a box as scarlet as fire. Several emerald green tree leaves were intertwined in a pattern on top of it. The green light they emitted made for a stark contrast with the color of the box.

Han Li stood in front of the four with Bai Bi standing off to the side.

The atmosphere in the hall was incredibly heavy, and none of them chose to speak. It was as if no one was there.

As for the black-robed man, he examined Han Li with much interest.

A moment later, footsteps sounded from outside the hall to reveal a silver-robed woman with white wings. She carried a wind into the hall.

Her complexion was like white jade and her eyes were beautiful. There was not a flaw in her appearance.

“Lei Lan, you’re late.” Jin Yue looked at the woman and frowned.

The beauty bowed to Jin Yue and spoke with a hoarse voice, “Grand Elder, I’ve comprehended a few techniques recently and had a sudden understanding, resulting in my tardiness. I hope the elders will forgive me.”

“Since it was related to comprehension, then so be it.” Jin Yue’s expression relaxed.

She uttered a word of thanks and stood to the side.

Jin Yue then stared at the Han Li and the holy disciples and spoke with a pleasant voice, “You should know why we’ve gathered you here. The oncoming trial is related to the life and death of the clan. So one of you two must pass the trail and succeed the position as our race’s holy master. However, we’ve received information that there are branches hostile to us like the Chi Rong. They are unwilling to allow us to escape calamity and have most likely placed people in the trials to act against you. The time you’ve spent as holy disciples is too short. If the other holy disciples violently block you, you won’t return. For this reason, I’ve invited Fellow Daoist Han to our Tian Peng Race. He will temporarily act as the third holy disciple. He will offer you his strength.”

Bai Bi and the newly entered woman raised their head and glanced at Han Li.

The young man had a warm, kind gaze while the woman’s expression was as clear as ice.

Han Li faintly smiled.

Chapter 1433: Branches of the Flying Spirit Tribe

The young woman Jin Yue warned, “Fellow Daoist Han already refined a Kun Peng Feather. Along with the Tian Peng True Blood and the Relic we assisted in merging with him, the other branches can’t say anything about not being one of us. But that stands to mention, we’ll be avoiding speaking of Fellow Daoist Han’s circumstances to the outside to avoid unnecessary complications. We’ll simply say that he was a clan member that was nurtured overseas.”

“We’ll do as you say.” The two holy disciples nodded in agreement.

Jin Yue nodded with satisfaction and turned to Han Li, solemnly saying, “Fellow Daoist Han, I’ve already called for the scroll containing the Tian Peng Vow to be brought out. Furthermore, Elder Shi has also returned. He will participate in dispelling the seal on the scroll. Prepare to sign your name on it.”

Elder Shi seemed to be the black-robed man standing at the side.

“I’ll have to trouble you, Elders.” Han Li agreed without any reservations. His eyes then dropped on the wooden box on the table.

When Jin Yue saw this, she beckoned to the wooden box.

In a brush of wind, the box directly sucked into her grasp and dropped into the young woman’s hand.

In that next moment, the others also focused their attention there.

Jin Yue’s expression remained calm as he brushed her fingers past the green leaves on the box

Suddenly, green light shined brilliantly and she nimbly took the leaves off the box.

Without any of the pressure emitting from the leaves, the crimson box ignited into a ball of scarlet fire.

Jin Yue grabbed the fire and gave it a nonchalant shake.

The flames were immediately extinguished to reveal a half-foot-long scarlet scroll. There were an azure and a red ghost head biting down on either end of it, both appearing true to life.

After uttering a brief incantation, she tossed the scroll in front of her where it suspended itself at a low height.

The young woman then unfolded only one of her wings, which soon glistened with golden light. In a flash, the light wrapped around the box.

With that done, she turned to the black-robed man and said, “Elder Shi, help me dissolve the seal.”

“As the matter concerns the existence of the clan, I will do my utmost,” The black-robed man said with a smile. Then one of his wings released a streak of black light which entered the scroll.

As for the red-bearded old man and the beautiful woman, they performed a similar action.

With the feathers of the four Tian Peng Elders absorbed by the scroll, space began to warp.

Red light flashed from the entire scroll and expanded several times in size. Both of the ghost heads on either end of it simultaneously opened and revealed blood-red eyes. It was then that they released their grip on the scroll and allowed it to unfold.

Red mist flickered from the above of the scroll, condensing into countless roiling talisman characters.

A blue light flickered from Han Li’s eyes allowing him to see the scroll’s contents clearly.

The red light was densely filled with small characters. Most of them appeared to be names.

At the very top of the scroll, ‘Tian Peng Vow’ was written in large golden characters of the Flying Spirit Tribe.

Afterwards, it listed faint silver characters with contents that appeared similar to a few Tian Peng records.

Then, it listed rows of dark azure names.

Han Li carefully swept his spiritual sense through the scroll.

When he made contact with the red list, long clear cries began to sound from it. Soon, the light mist roiled and revealed a mythical bird phantom. As soon as it appeared, it was only a foot tall, but as it brilliantly glowed, it turned the size of a hill, filling most of the hall and completely submerging Han Li and company in it.

Han Li and the holy disciples were alarmed, but Jin Yue and the other elders were completely calm.

“Move back,” Jin Yue raised her hand and waved an azure copper mirror at the bird image.

The phantom suddenly let out a cry and immediately shattered into tiny fragments that were swept into the scroll in an azure wave.

Jin Yue withdrew the mirror and spoke to Han Li with a deep tone, “Use your blood essence to sign the scroll. You must use your true name, or there is no saving you from the vow’s backlash.”

Han Li trembled. A few of his original thoughts had been temporarily placed to the back of his mind.

He took a deep breath and took large steps forward.

He spat out a golden thread. In a golden flash, the thread sliced open a small opening from his finger. Then under the pressure of his spiritual power, he forced a drop of faintly golden blood essence from it.”

“Yi!” Elder Shi wore an odd expression on his face.”

“Has Elder Shi found something amiss?” The red-bearded old man twirled his beard.

The black-robed man hesitated and slowly said, “It’s nothing. Fellow Daoist Han most likely cultivated a peculiar technique or consumed a few rare fruits which resulted in the color of his blood essence.”

The old man looked at Han Li and pensively said, ‘That’s true. Golden blood essence is truly rare. His body has most likely been strengthened to a degree for that to happen!”

The black-robed man smiled and said nothing else.

At that moment, Han Li moved in front of the scroll and quickly wrote his name on an empty spot on the scroll.

When the drop of faint golden blood essence dropped on the scroll, the words absorbed it. In a flash, it turned into dark azure words. They were dull as if they had been written for many years now.

Meanwhile, Han Li faintly sensed that something was gazing at his primal soul, but it immediately disappeared.

Alarmed, it appeared that the Tian Peng Vow seemed to be something of a gateway.

Having thought of this, Han Li felt more at ease.

With a binding like this, the Tian Peng Elders wouldn’t be able to throw him away or their agreement once the matter is settled.

As Han Li pondered to himself, Jin Yue had the other holy disciples put down their names as well.

Once the scroll trembled, it quickly wrapped itself and the two ghost heads stirred, biting down on either hand. When Jin Yue waved at it, the scroll shrunk and quickly flew into her sleeve.

With the scroll retrieved, Jin Yue indifferently said, “Alright, since that matter is done, Elder Xi will explain the matters you must pay attention to during the earth abyss trial. Remember it well. It could save your life.”

“The earth abyss trial is held by the main branch of the Flying Spirit Tribe and is held once every three hundred years...” The red-bearded man began to slowly explain.

Han Li and the two holy disciples carefully listened.

Several days later, several huge snow-white birds flew out of the main gate of the holy city. After they left the restrictions, they soared to the sky.

Han Li was sitting on top of one of the birds.

With each wing flap, the white birds flew forward a hundred meters. With several flaps, they quickly reached the end of the horizon, turning into black dots.

...

On a mountaintop three months later, in a large series of green buildings surrounded by a huge plaza stood over a hundred Flying Spirit Tribe beings. At the center, there was a red crane and a brightly-colored strange bird. They were unleashing attacks as they fought against one another in mid-air.

The red crane’s movements were a marvel. Each claw and peck produced the sound of tearing space, clearly displaying an incredibly sharpness.

The brightly colored bird had four wings and a horn on its head. The colors on its body released a mist of light that seemed to absorb the crane’s attack without a problem.

The red crane was furious at this and suddenly flew a hundred meters backward, spreading its wings in the direction of the bright bird.

Suddenly, tens of long feathers shot out, blurring into gleaming blades as they flew through the air. They all struck the opposing bird’s light mist at nearly the same time.

No matter how wondrous the gorgeous light mist was, it groaned and violently trembled upon receiving the attacks of so many blades and began to forcefully tear.

The crane was overjoyed when it saw this and was about to release more blades when the bright bird suddenly released a sharp cry. A yellow wave rushed forth and the sharp blades were blown askew. They then turned around as if they were completely under the bright bird’s control.

The crane was startled and opened its mouth releasing a white beam of light. It penetrated the bright bird’s wind.

A strange light flashed from the bright bird’s purple eyes and a black horn suddenly shined with red light from the bright bird’s eyes. A red light suddenly shot out from it and struck the oncoming white beam.

The air rumbled and both attacks were nullified.

“Brother Xun, what other abilities do you have? I’ve already fully used all of mine. If you have no others, I am going to attack.” The bright bird spoke with a man’s voice.

A cold snort sounded from the crane, “Your Horned Vulture Tribe only has their many abilities. How could they deal with me?”

“Good, then I’ll let you witness them. This is my newly cultivated ability.” The bright bird strangely said.

The right bird’s four wings flapped, releasing a wave of bright light. The bright bird transformed into a three-meter-tall yellow bell.

“Not good!” Everyone who saw this immediately took several steps back in alarm. Only those with more confidence in their cultivation stood still.

The yellow bell began to shake itself and let out deep rings.

Everyone who heard this felt their minds shaken by the sound.

As for the red crane that directly faced most of the bell’s power, he wordlessly dropped to the floor.

At that same moment, his body flashed white to reveal a white-robed Flying Spirit Tribe man about thirty years old.

Another man flew out of the crowd and caught the man before he landed.

The yellow bell shook and turned into a black-robed young man. He saluted at the ground and calmly said, “You let me win.”

As for the crane that turned back into a man, he looked at the black-robed youth with an unsightly expression as he was carried out by his companion.

Chapter 1434: Jade Emperor Peak

Under close examination, the man that had the form of a red crane appeared very different from an ordinary human. His face was close enough, but his ears were sharp and there was a round red bulge from the top of his head.

As for the black-robed youth, there was a small black horn on his head and his mouth had a pair of sharp fangs several inches long.

As for the surrounding hundred Flying Spirit Tribe beings, most of them appeared different from humans, but they only had a few aspects that were different. But what was most different from all of them was the large variety in the color and length of their wings.

These people were all from the Flying Spirit Tribe.

“The Horned Vulture Race’s Devil Suppressing Bell is truly powerful. I’ve received much experience.” The defeated white-robed man uttered these words resentfully before being half-carried away.

“Are there any others that wish to learn a thing or two?” The black-robed youth said calmly, looking down at the crowd as he uttered a word of challenge.

The crowd became restless, but for a time no one stepped forward.

When the youth saw this, he sneered, but just as he thought to say something, someone spoke from a distance, “Quickly look, holy disciples of the westmost branches, the Pentaluster, Tian Peng, and Chi Rong Races have arrived.”

When the crowd heard this, they began to speak as if it were a race.

Those that were curious turned around, flying a distance away. In the blink of an eye, the crowd shrank by a small half.

When the black-robed youth heard this, his face slightly changed and he silently descended from the sky.

Meanwhile, in an area over fifty kilometers away from the huge mountain, apart from tens of various huge birds, there was also a sixty-meter-long crimson flying scorpion that was flying through to the mountain.

Among the huge birds, there were several with pure-white bodies with various men and women riding them. They were the Tian Peng Race.

Han Li was riding on top of one of the huge birds.

In the Tian Peng’s party, Jin Yue and the mysterious Elder Shi rode alongside the holy disciples.

The red-bearded old man and the beautiful woman remained on guard at the holy city.

At that moment, they were together with two different groups.

One of the groups had purple hair and red skin. As for the other group, they had smaller wings and gorgeous robes.

They were respectively the Chi Rong and the Pentaluster Race. However, the meager five people of the Tian Peng Race were clearly fewer than the other two groups.

The gorgeous young female holy disciple smiled and said, “Elder Jin, it appears that Jade Emperor Peak’s elders knew we were coming and lit up the welcoming fires.”

In a distance away above the huge mountain, there was a large rainbow flame burning, filling the air with a gorgeous glow.

The astonishing scene could be clearly seen by those fifty kilometers away.

“It seems we weren’t the first to arrive. Time truly passes quickly. In the blink of an eye, three hundred years already passed.” Jin Yue turned to an old man with fire-red skin and said, “Brother Zhu, what do you think about this place?”

“What impression is there to be had?” The old man expression asked, “Unless we cultivate a True Spirit Body or to Soaring True Immortal Stage, we’ll just be mounds of earth in tens of thousands of years. The prosperities of the tribe are replaced in turn. Has Elder Jin considered the matter I spoke a few days ago?”

A bright glint flashed from the young woman’s eyes and she indifferently replied, “Our Tian Peng Race has truly become much weaker, but we’ve survived since ancient times. We are the longest living branch of the tribe. We won’t easily discard our legacy and throw ourselves into the embrace of another tribe. I’ve put much thought into Brother Zhu’s proposal to merge, but I can only refuse you.”

Old Man Zhu coldly smiled and said, “Is that so? If I remember correction, from ancient times, your esteemed Elder Shi came from the Black Feather Tribe, a branch that was annexed during your golden age. Now that your own tribe has been weakened, merging with a stronger tribe and handing over the master’s position is a natural position.”

“How can this matter relate to the Black Feather Tribe? At the time, the Black Feather Tribe weren’t only lacking a holy master, but it also faced powerful enemies and took the initiative to merge with our tribe. We hadn’t forced them.” The young woman said with a casual tone.

Old Man Zhu chuckled and said, “Those matters happened so long ago, who truly knows what actually happened. Since you’ve rejected my clan’s kind intentions, we’ll have to see if your clan’s holy disciples can make it through the earth abyss trial. If they fail, don’t blame me if several branches form a council of elders and discuss the proposal to dismantle your clan. Don’t forget that our Chi Rong race isn’t the only one interested in your clan.”

A charming young woman looked over to them with a sweet smile and said, “Brother Zhu, your esteemed clan has become amongst the top three in strength among the seventy-two branches. There is no need to be so overbearing in your pursuit to consume the Tian Peng Race. Could it be you rush to forcefully contend with the Jiu Yue Race?”

“Lady Qui, don’t speak such rubbish. When did anybody from my clan say that?” When the old man heard her, his face greatly changed.

Elder Qui smiled and thought to say more when heavenly music began to play from the direction of the mountain top. The sky’s color then flickered and became more gorgeous.

They hastily shut their mouths and ceased flight as they floated in the air.

In the blink of an eye, the ten variously dressed people, most of aging appearance and venerable bearing, appeared from the slight.”

“We pay our respects to the Elders.” When Jin Yue and the others saw these ten men, they jumped off their birds in alarm and deeply saluted them.

An old woman with a cane with a beaming smile and said, “There is no need to regard us as outsiders. You’ll join our ranks sooner or later. The other elders are awaiting you on Jade Emperor Peak.”

Jin Yue’s heart stirred and she respectfully asked, “What? Could it be that our three branches were the last?”

The old woman chuckled and answered, “This is not the case. The northmost Gui Mian and Du Jiu branches were busy so we’re able to start the earth abyss trial without them. With you three, we may begin.”

“So it was like that,” Jin Yue nodded.

Standing behind them, Han Li felt his heart tremble when he saw the ten that appeared.

The ten were mostly at Body Integration cultivation. As for the old woman, he wasn’t able to see through her cultivation stage. She was most likely the same as Jin Yue, a fearsome existence at Body Integration stage or higher.

This was the so-called joint assembly elders.

It was said that elders were originally from various tribes, but when their lifespans were nearing their end, they could join these elders and renounce their affiliation with their original branch, taking on the responsibilities of the entire Flying Spirit Tribe.

At that moment, Old Man Zhu and the young woman stepped forward and exchanged pleasantries with the old woman. Soon after, the party flew to the mountain under the guidance of the old woman.

A moment later, the party arrived near the huge mountain and the imposing buildings could be faintly seen. Black dots could be seen circling the air above it.

Under closer examination, Han Li discovered that there were hundreds of huge birds flying through the air as well as huge winged insects with malevolent appearances.

When the mountain appeared to only be a kilometer away, a muffled bang sounded. A seven-colored rainbow flew out in a curve from a long distance away towards them.

Soon after, a gorgeous arched bridge appeared above them.

The old woman and the others blurred, taking a step on the bridge and beckoning the others with a smile.

“Let’s go.” Jin Yue commanded. She then stepped off the bird and quickly walked on the bridge.

The other parties did the same.

When Han Li walked on the bridge, he felt that he was stepping on something completely soft like a thick cushion.

Curious, he wanted to take a close look and released his spiritual sense, but he felt the bridge tremble and their surroundings light up, completely enveloping the party. With several shakes, the light brought them to the other end of the bridge.

At that moment, Han Li was unable to examine the marvelous display of the bridge as he found himself in front of over twenty Flying Spirit Tribe beings. They were all staring at him.

Behind them, there appeared to be a jade-green hall wrapped in white fog.

At the very front of this crowd were two people. One of them was a middle-aged man with a large nose and snow-white hair. The other had a wrinkly face and long cheeks, an old man with a black tattoo on his neck.

When the old woman saw them, she smiled and she walked towards them. As for the rest of them, they joined the crowd.

The tattooed old man waved his hand with a smile, “The elders have brought their holy disciples from a distance away. It must’ve been tiring. The holy disciples may rest in the side hall for a spell. The elders may accompany us to the main hall for a chat. The other clan elders are waiting for us there.”

The Chi Rong’s Elder Zhu rushed to speak, smiling as he said, “Elder Ming is too polite. We’ll do as you request.”

Jin Yue and the young woman from the Pentaluster Race raised no objections.

With that, Han Li and the others entered the white fog.

At an unknown time, a slender white-robed woman appeared in front of Han Li and the other holy disciples. She beamed at them and said, “Holy disciple, please follow me. This servant shall arrange your residences.”

Chapter 1438: Earth Abyss Guard

Zhu Yinzi glanced at the azure Peng phantom from a distance as it spread out its wings.

Suddenly, the four tornados ruptured, sending countless azure wind blades in Zhu Yinzi’s direction.

For a time, only glaring azure light and tearing winds could be observed from the light barrier.

When Zhu Yinzi saw the ferocious might of Han Li’s attack, his expression froze.

However, his fame was well earned. He took a deep breath and his wings swelled several times in size before he wildly fanned them.

Red light brilliantly flashed and dense blooms of flame began to spread all around.

With his hands forming an incantation gesture, Zhu Yinzi formed countless scarlet flame arrows and released them.

The barrage’s momentum was no lesser than Han Li’s wind blades.

In an instant, the air was divided into two, with one half filled with azure streaks and faint azure blades, and the other filled with sparkling red light and roiling flames.

A thin line formed where the attacks met. As azure and red light intertwined, countless explosions boomed.

For a time, the two sides found themselves in deadlock.

Han Li remained expressionless, but his incantation gestures changed and the sound of thunder faintly sounded from his sleeve. With two claps, two bowl-thick bolts of golden lightning shot out of his sleeve, fusing in midair to form a dense golden lightning wyrm.

Under Han Li’s mental control, the lightning wyrm waved its head and tail, flashing a hundred meters forward right in front of Zhu Yinzi. As rolls of thunder sounded out from it, it pounced at him.

The lightning wyrm’s incredible speed frightened even Zhu Yinzi.

Without another thought, Zhu Yinzi spat out a scarlet ball gleaming with light.

Boom. The ball and the flood dragon collided, resulting in a blinding light. Soon after, the spiritual Qi roiled and turned into a ten-meter-wide fire tornado that soared to the sky. The tornado was mixed with sparks of golden lightning and thunder repeatedly clapped from it. A burning wind spread out in every direction.

Under the pressure, Zhu Yinzi unconsciously took several steps back and turned to look in Han Li’s direction.

Startled, his face vastly changed.

Han Li was no longer standing in his original place. Rather, he brought Lei Lan near the ground at the edge of the light barrier as if they were about to leave.

In his fury, Zhu Yinzi raised his arm and pointed at him.

With a rustle of wind, red line briefly flickered and shot forward.

However, Han Li was already prepared. With a raised brow, he pointed back.

Red light flashed and a similar red line was launched. It was a fire spirit thread!

A crackle sounded. The two lines flashed in midair, accurately striking one another. As a result, Han Li’s fire thread was repelled with slight damage, while Zhu Yinzi’s line disappeared entirely.

A short moment later, Han Li and Lei Lan flickered, reappearing outside of the arena barrier.

The nearby spectators took several steps back and looked at the two with astonishment.

Seeing he could do nothing to prevent Han Li from leaving, he raised his voice and harshly shouted, “Brother Han, you’ve fled without fighting. Do you not fear tarnishing your clan’s reputation?”

Han Li glanced back at him and indifferently said, “You should understand my thoughts. We can't determine an outcome in a short amount of time. I also carry a heavy responsibility, so we’ll only be able to fight later.”

Soon after, he spread his wings and soared to the distant sky without care.

Lei Lan’s expression wavered and she eventually followed after Han Li.

When Zhu Yinzi saw Han Li bluntly depart, his expression sank.

From the side, Hong Sha hesitantly asked, “Senior Martial Brother Zhu, do you want to pursue them?”

Zhu Yinzi snorted, “How would we? We can’t fight outside the sparring arena. I didn’t think that he would leave so quickly after fighting. Although we’ve only exchanged two blows, we discovered that he’s proficient in wind and lightning, so it wasn’t a wasted effort. Additionally, we’ve noticed his small mountain treasure, which blocked my scarlet flame claw. How troublesome. We’ll have to go back and think of a way to destroy him.”

With a careful heart, the woman only uttered a word of acknowledgment.

Thus, the two descended and gathered with the Chi Rong in the crowd before departing.

The remaining Flying Spirit Tribe members then began to discuss the appearance of Han Li.

...

Jin Yue stared at the pitiful silver-robed Lei Lan and coldly asked, “Did I not instruct you three times over to not travel alone? Why did you go and fight the Chi Rong at the sparring stage?”

At that moment, the Tian Peng Grand Elder was sitting in the first floor hall of their residence with an icy face.

Elder Shi sat at her side. He also appeared displeased.

Lei Lan appeared bloodlessly pale.

Bai Bi and Han Li stood at the side. Bai Bi was silent, restless, and hung his head while Han Li appeared calm.

Not long after Han Li brought back Lei Lan, the two elders immediately discovered what happened and rushed over. They were giving a harsh rebuke to the two holy disciples.

Although the one to blame was Lei Lan, Bai Bi hadn’t done anything to stop her and shared responsibility.

Lei Lan eventually muttered, “Gran Elder, that Chi Rong disciple Hong Sha had a Lightning Star Stone. If I could acquire it, I have at least a thirty percent chance of later entering the Great Spirit General-stage. My judgement wavered...”

Jin Yue resentfully said, “A Lightning Star Stone? It is no wonder you were tempted, but that wasn’t a reason to take such careless actions. Your lives and cultivation are the life and death of the clan. You should understand the weight of your actions. In order to nurture the two of you, our clan had provided you with countless medicines and treasures, allowing you to reach this cultivation stage in a short time, and will continue to do so in the future. If this were not the case, you wouldn’t have reached spirit general stage, no matter your talents.”

Lei Lan didn’t reply and simply wore a face of shame.

As she thought of something to say, Elder Shi smiled and said, “Alright Elder Jin. Although Lei Lan has been rash, Fellow Daoist Han managed to arrive in time and nothing of consequence occurred. Fellow Daoist Han, how do you see the situation?”

“The Chi Rong most likely had doubts about me and wanted to test my skill,” Han Li replied with a smile.

Elder Shi chuckled and said, “I heard that you stood on equal grounds with Zhu Yinzi and even withdrew yourself. A very wise decision.”

“I understand how important this matter is,” Han Li replied.

Jin Yue pondered for a moment and spoke with unquestionable authority, “From this day, none of you three will take a step outside this building. You may only rest and cultivate. For other matters, hand them over to us to deal with.”

“Yes, Grand Elder!” Bai Bi and Lei Lan respectfully answered.

Han Li offered a salute to express his agreement.

To this day, Han Li’s identity in the Tian Peng had been odd. He was a holy disciple in name, but in truth, he was closer to a guest official. And with Tian Peng making demands of him, he could only be polite in return.

Once Jin Yue and Elder Shi left, Han Li and the three entered and remained in secluded cultivation.

Two weeks later, Jin Yue and the other Flying Spirit Tribe elders assembled on top of Jade Emperor Peak, discussing something.

Two months later, several thousand huge birds and flying insects rushed past a desolate yellow plateau.

Mounted on top of the birds and insects were winged beings.

They had set off from Jade Emperor Peak and were on their way to the entrance of the earth abyss.

Han Li and the Tian Peng were saddled on white huge birds at the center of the group.

Although the group was large and they’ve been flying for quite some time, very little was said on the trip.

Han Li also sat cross-legged on his bird and was silently looking around him. The entrance to the earth abyss was much farther from Jade Emperor Peak than he imagined.

Suddenly, there was an uproar from the Flying Spirit Tribe members from the front and a few of them shouted in alarm. The group suddenly flew down.

Han Li’s expression stirred and he immediately sent his spiritual sense to the front.

Five hundred kilometers in front of them, a huge wall had suddenly appeared before them. It was azure-grey and was over a kilometer tall. The wall spread to either side as far as the eye could see.

Every three hundred meter segment on the wall, there stood a pure-white jade pillar.

The pillar was only thirty-meters-tall but its surface gleamed with azure light and was covered in mysterious talisman markings.

To the side of the huge wall, there was a dense gathering of round buildings that were a hundred meters tall. There seemed to be several thousand in number.

Above these buildings flew a myriad of Flying Spirit Tribe beings that were awaiting them.

The holy disciples and the elders gradually drew closer before coming to a stop.

“Greetings, Elders!” An azure-armored middle-aged man flew out towards them and saluted them from a distance.

“So this year, my old pal Jin Feng was on duty. How fortunate. Brother Jin, you should’ve received the information we’ve given you.” From Han Li’s side, several people flew out.

This included an old woman with a cane, a middle-aged man with snow-white hair, and an old man with azure thorns on his face.

They were the most influential of the council of elders and were speaking to the middle-aged man.

Even they appeared very respectful when facing this azure-armored man.

Chapter 1439: The Four Fiend Armor Technique

Han Li glanced at the azure-armored man and felt his heart tremble.

His cultivation was unfathomably deep, no lesser than the three grand elders that have rushed to meet him. It was no wonder they were so polite.

Furthermore, this person’s azure-armor was somewhat particular. Its designs were quite simple and its surface was a dull grey, but it has its talisman characters similar to decorative patterns. But when Han Li brushed his spiritual sense past the armor, it gave him a familiar sensation. He took another glance at it, then suddenly widely opening his eyes as if he saw something inconceivable.

If he was correct, the so-called azure armor should’ve been something condensed from extremely concentrated baleful Qi. This explained why the aura gave him a familiar feeling.

Despite the amount of baleful Qi on his body, he appeared well and was able to use it to create armor.

This ability was truly outrageous.

In his alarm, he looked around and noticed others that were wearing azure armor among the Flying Spirit Tribe.

Each of them wore armor of varying colors.

Blue light flashed from Han Li’s eyes and he narrowed his sight.

Their armor was also formed from baleful Qi. But because of their weaker cultivation or lacking baleful Qi, their armor appeared vague as if they weren’t as condensed.

When Han Li saw the different armors formed by baleful Qi, he was deeply shocked and began to ponder about them.

At that moment, the azure-armored man looked at the crowd behind the three grand elders and wore a smile.

“How could I forget about our tribe’s three hundred year trial. However, the demons in the closest earth abyss are agitated. If you wait another two years, I wouldn’t agree with having the trial.”

The old man chuckled, “That is why we moved the date of the trial earlier when we heard your news. There shouldn’t be a problem starting now, right?”

The azure-armored man indifferently answered, “No. Although the dark Qi is more dangerous than usual, an official eruption will take a year at least. However, the dark demons underground will not stay in the nest levels, so I can’t guarantee that the demons on the first three layers will be spirit general grade. The chances of encountering high-grade earth abyss demons will be much higher, but those at demon king-level won’t likely appear. As the dangerous ones, if you find them to be too harmful, don’t blame me for not warning you.”

“So long as no demon king-grade existences appear, the trial will go on,” the white-haired man said with a firm voice.

The old woman frowned and slowly said, “I have no objections. If we miss this opportunity, we won’t be able to conduct the trial for at least another hundred years. Many of our branches cannot wait that long.”

The tattooed old man muttered to himself for a moment and nodded with a sigh.

The azure-armored man chuckled at their approval and raised his hand to the air.

A fist-sized azure light ball shot out. In a flash, it strangely appeared a kilometer in the air.

Following the explosion of the light ball, a huge world-shaking boom shook the air and a halo of azure light rushed out from the result.

Soon after, a ten-meter-wide azure sun rose to the sky, shining with a blinding light.

The armored Flying Spirit Tribe beings behind the azure-armored man immediately separated into two lines, forming a path in the air.

Their cultivation all differed, but their silent and disciplined movement produced a formless pressure.

When the others saw this, the various elders were better off, showing only a brief change in expression, but Han Li and the other holy disciples became restless with most wearing expressions of astonishment.

The three elders in front then waved their arms behind them before moving forward together.

Suddenly, the entire group went ahead and slowly passed through the armored soldiers in the air.

Mounted on top of a huge bird, he narrowed his eyes as he looked at the armored soldiers to either side.

He found that most of them wore cold, indifferent faces apart from occasionally looking at them with curious eyes. There were also those that were younger and possessed lesser cultivation.

The lowest cultivation among them was at Core Formation level.

And there were many from higher cultivation levels, many of which included those at Great Spirit General-stage.

Han Li felt apprehension.

The earth abyss guards that are stationed here were about the same as the guards of Deep Heaven City.

However, their numbers were far less than the Deep Heaven Guards. But their elites were at a level far beyond those from Deep Heaven City. And considering the people stationed here often fight the demons that emerge from the earth abyss, they have richer combat experience than other Flying Spirit Tribe members.

From the buildings constructed here, it also appears that earth abyss guards live here as well.

As Han Li’s thoughts churned in his mind, the group of holy disciples and elders arrived in front of the span of buildings.

The group of elders separated and started guiding the disciples to nearby residences to rest. The trial would soon begin on the morning of the next day.

The Tian Peng also entered one of the residences.

Jin Yue and Elder Shi guarded the first floor while the holy disciples were each given their own floor so they could rest without disturbance.

Han Li frowned. Although he was happy there was a night of rest, Jin Yue and Elder Shi had ordered them to remain inside and stay on different floors. It would interrupt his earlier plans.

Han Li sat cross-legged on his bed, but he didn’t meditate. Instead, his eyes wandered as his mind began to sink into thought.

Not long after, he seemed to have thought of something and chuckled to himself. He then stood up and went to the first floor.

When he appeared at the bottom of the stairs, he saw Jin Yue and Elder Shi with their eyes closed as they sat down. But immediately after, they open their eyes at the same time and looked over in his direction.

Han Li felt his heart tremble.

“Fellow Daoist Han, why aren’t you getting proper rest? Could it be that you have something urgent to attend to?” Rather than Jin Yue, it was Elder Shi who spoke.

“I have something I wish to do and I want to take a trip outside,” Han Li calmly stated.

“What is it?” Jin Yue said with a trace of dissatisfaction.

With the trial right around the corner, she hoped that Han Li would obediently rest in his room, rather than be distracted by other things.

Han Li smiled and gave an honest answer, “In truth, it isn’t much. I found that the earth abyss guard’s armor was quite peculiar as it was formed from baleful Qi. I was hoping of finding someone that could explain the mysteries behind it.”

Jin Yue paused and then said with an odd expression, “You mean the Four Fiend Armor Technique? The technique requires an immense amount of baleful Qi to use. Otherwise, the technique would be too weak. What do you plan to do with it?”

Elder Shi also felt somewhat surprised.

Han Li smiled and formed an incantation gesture. Golden light shined from his body, emitting an astonishingly deep aura. A dense wave of baleful Qi soon burst out from the depths of his body.

The baleful Qi he refined with the Vajra Arts began to concentrate all over his body.

Both of the elders were astonished by the display of baleful Qi.

“With such dense baleful Qi, it is no wonder you’re interested in the Four Fiend Amor Technique. Hehe, but you don’t need to go outside. The technique isn't kept secret, and I’m proficient in it as well. I can hand over the entire cultivation art to you. With the immense baleful Qi on your body, you may even use the technique tomorrow during the trial.” As Elder Shi heartily laughed, he spoke the words that Han Li already anticipated.

When he saw so many ordinary earth abyss guards comprehend this technique, the Tian Peng elders likely knew this technique as well.

Now, his assumption was proven correct.

Suppressing his joy, Han Li respectfully answered, “Senior Shi, I can’t thank you enough. But are the techniques easy to comprehend? Would I be able to use them after a night?”

Elder Shi waved his hand and casually said, “Hehe, so long as Fellow Daoist Han assists Lei Lan and Bai Bi through the trial, I’m the one who should be thanking you. Don’t worry, the technique isn’t particularly complicated, and with your cultivation, you’ll be able to cultivate several layers in a single night. As for the last few layers, they require immense baleful Qi, so you won’t be able to use them.”

Han Li nodded several times in response.

Jin Yue raised no objections. Instead, she simply closed her eyes again.

Elder Shi took out a finger-sized bamboo tube from his robes and muttered to it for a moment before tossing it over to Han Li, “I’ve put the technique in there. You may return.”

“Many thanks, Senior!” Han Li then took the tube and climbed up the stairs without delay.

He sat cross-legged on his bed and pressed the tube against his forehead and immersed it with his spiritual sense.

Suddenly, an ancient green script flowed through Han Li’s mind, his face becoming entirely still.

Not long after, Han Li put away the tube into his storage pouch and his face relaxed.

The set of techniques was as Elder Shi had described. They were simple and he’d be able to condense a layer of baleful armor.

With that thought, Han Li rested his hands on his knees and began to comprehend the technique.

During this time, a layer of faintly black baleful Qi began to appear from his body.

The baleful Qi roiled and went still for a time. Not long after, his surroundings began to violently stir, creating a faint black wind around him and blurring Han Li’s figure from sight.

Chapter 1444: Demonic Ape

"Yes, Mistress!" The short furry figure shuddered as it ducked its head even lower.

"Go, now. I'll be returning to the third level on my own," the woman instructed before tapping a foot on the massive black flower beneath her.

Black light immediately flashed from the gigantic flower as silver formations of different sizes appeared over its surface. Silver light then flashed and bursts of inky-black mist billowed out from these formations, forming a sea of mist that enshrouded the entire giant flower in the blink of an eye.

A rumbling thunderclap erupted from within the mist, following which the sea of mist was dispelled by gusts of fierce winds amid a few arcs of flashing silver lightning.

The flower and the slender woman abruptly disappeared on the spot, and only the furry figure remained, still half-knelt on the ground.

After around the five minutes, the short humanoid figure finally rose to its feet and slowly raised its head, revealing a set of ape-like facial features and two pairs of ears. Its green eyes were quite small, but they were shimmering with a cold and sinister light.

This was a Resentful Ape Beast with dark yellow fur, and it seemed to have attained intelligence. The demonic ape appraised its surroundings before abruptly opening its mouth to expel a burst of yellow mist that enshrouded the remains of the giant flower.

An incredible turn of events unfolded!

Within this yellow mist, the Giant Spirit Flower quickly disintegrated into a vast expanse of viscous green liquid. The mist then swept up this green liquid and drew it into the demonic ape's stomach.

The ape then closed its eyes while green light appeared within its nostrils and four ears. At the same time, its yellow fur had turned green and was shimmering faintly.

This Resentful Ape Beast stood still on the spot for a long while two of its four ears suddenly twitched slightly.

Not long after this, a ball of red light flashed from the distance.

There was a portly man within the red light who appeared to be in his thirties, and he had a pair of green wings on his back, as well as a pair of sharp horns on his head. A cunning light was shimmering from his beady eyes, and he was a holy disciple from one of the other branches of the Flying Spirit Race.

For some reason, he had chosen the same route as Han Li and the others, and he appeared to be traveling alone. However, this man appeared to be extremely cautious, so it had naturally already noticed the demonic ape up ahead.

Thus, the fatso stopped in mid-air several hundred feet away from the demonic ape before looking down at it with a hint of surprise on his face.

Even though the demonic ape had converted the remains of the Giant Spirit Flower into liquid and consumed it, the fissures on the ground from when the giant black flower had emerged were quite astonishing to behold.

Meanwhile, the demonic ape stood motionlessly on the spot with his eyes tightly shut while green light flashed within his nose and ears. It seemed to have completely detached itself from the outside world.

As such, this scene struck the onlooker with the illusion that the ape had just fought some kind of gargantuan being and had sustained severe injuries in the process. As a result, it was forced to entering a state of recuperation, thereby rendering it completely defenseless.

That was clearly the conclusion that the holy disciple had arrived at, and a hint of excitement appeared on his face at the sight of the demonic ape.

Even though the objective of this trial wasn't to kill demons, being able to slay a high-grade earth abyss demon beast would undoubtedly earn him bountiful rewards such as its demon core, as well as other ingredients and materials that could be procured from its body.

No one would be willing to give up a chunk of delicious meat that was there for the taking.

However, this holy disciple was extremely cautious and didn't spring into action in a reckless manner. Instead, he surveyed the demonic ape in silence from afar.

After a long while, the demonic ape still hadn't moved at all, and he was finally lulled into a sense of security. A sinister smile appeared on his face as he abruptly rubbed his hands together.

A ball of flames erupted from between his palms, and the flames then transformed into a log fiery spear that was around 20 feet in length.

The tip of the spear was extremely sharp, and it was enshrouded in a layer of scorching crimson flames.

The holy disciple then spread its wings and sped toward the demonic ape as a streak of red light.

Even though this holy disciple had a rather portly figure, he was unleashed some kind of secret technique that not only allowed him to fly extremely quickly, it also ensured a soundless flight, thereby resulting in an extremely stealthy approach.

In the blink of an eye, the streak of red light had appeared just over 100 feet away from the demonic ape, yet the demon beast remained standing motionlessly on the spot.

The holy disciple was ecstatic to see this, and he immediately thrust forth his spear without any hesitation.

The spear whistled through the air as a streak of red light before puncturing the demonic ape's body in a flash.

However, an elated expression had only just appeared on his face before it changed drastically.

The body of the demonic ape had vanished right after the fiery spear had punctured it, and it was thus revealed to have only been a projection.

"Crap!"

The holy disciple immediately flapped his wings with alarm to try and flee the scene.

However, it was already too late.

A blurry green figure suddenly appeared in the air above before pouncing onto the man's body in a flash. A dull thump erupted, and a ball of green mist exploded before enshrouding the holy disciple's entire body.

A bloodcurdling howl rang out as the red spiritual light around the man's body vanished like snow melting under the scorching sun, having been completely eroded by the green mist.

The holy disciple only flew for around 100 feet further before plummeting to the ground as a puddle of green liquid.

This holy disciple hadn't even had a chance to unleash any of his abilities before he had been slain.

At this moment, the green mist surged before manifesting into that demonic ape again.

The ape took a cold glance at the liquid on the ground before opening its mouth to consume it. In hindsight, this holy disciple really had perished in extremely unfortunate circumstances.

If everything had taken place above the ground, where he would've had full access to his spiritual sense, there was no way that he would've been deceived so easily by a projection, and he certainly would've sensed the demonic ape's presence before it had gotten so close to him.

The demonic ape smacked its lips before murmuring to itself in a thoughtful manner, "That was a Flying Spirit Tribe being, eh? That makes sense, considering the date of their trial's commencement is about to arrive soon. That means the ones who had destroyed the Giant Spirit Flower were most likely from the Flying Spirit Tribe as well."

With that in mind, the demonic ape sniffed the air before turning its gaze toward the direction that Han Li's trio had departed in.

A sinister smile appeared on its face as it flew through the air as a cloud of green mist, disappearing into the distance in the blink of an eye.

...

"What? You want us to take this?" Lei Lan's brows were tightly furrowed as she appraised the shimmering white jade badge in her had with bewilderment in her eyes.

Bai Bi was also holding an identical object with puzzlement in his eyes.

These two jade badges were both pristine and translucent with silver runes on their surfaces, and it was quite apparent that they were extremely valuable items.

Han Li had suddenly produced them a moment ago and asked the two holy disciples to carry the badges with them.

"Aside from protective properties, the main functions of these badges are aura concealment and location tracking. If some kind of mishap occurs and we end up being separated, we may be able to find one another again using these badges," Han Li explained.

These two badges were treasures known as Limitless Badges, and he'd purchased them in Deep Heaven City for a high price. The current situation was perfect for their usage. At this moment, they had emerged from the desert and were situated on a small mountain.

As a safety precaution, Han Li had produced these two treasures and was asking the two holy disciples to take one each.

"Thank you for your kind offer, Brother Han, but I don't have a habit of carrying other people's treasures," Lei Lan refused with a dark expression.

Bai Bi also shook his head with a faint smile on his face.

Han Li didn't force the issue; he merely stowed the jade badges away with a faint chuckle.

"Seeing as you're unwilling to carry the badges, then so be it. However, seeing as mid-grade demon beasts have appeared even on the first level, it appears our journey won't be devoid of risk as we'd initially thought. I have a flying treasure with concealment abilities. If we continue in our journey using it as a transportation device, it could spare us a lot of trouble," Han Li suggested.

"I'm fine with flying treasures," Lei Lan agreed with a smile on this occasion.

Bai Bi also nodded in response.

Han Li smiled as he swept a hand over his storage bracelet, upon which a yellow flying carriage that was narrow up front and wider at the back appeared before them.

The carriage appeared to have been refined from some kind of spirit wood and seemed to be very light. However, it also appeared to have been very intricately constructed, and many formations seemed to have been set up on it.

The carriage was around 70 to 80 feet in size, so it was more than enough to house the three of them.

This was one of the flying carriages that Han Li had collected prior to departing from Deep Heaven City so he had a variety to choose from depending on the situation.

Lei Lan and Bai Bi glanced at one another before following Han Li onto the carriage.

Han Li patted the flying carriage, casting several incantation seals into it. The carriage immediately tremored before a white barrier of light appeared over it, enshrouding the entire flying carriage within.

As the barrier of light swirled, the entire carriage gradually became transparent until it was virtually invisible.

The carriage then sped into the distance.

"Brother Han, why didn't you use this treasure from the start?" Bai Bi asked with a smile after inspecting the carriage for a while.

"This carriage is very useful, but it has a flaw," Han Li replied in an ambiguous manner.

"And what flaw is that?" Lei Lan was also getting rather curious.

"Hehe, if I want to use this carriage's concealment ability, I have to power it with high-grade wood-attribute spirit stones, and the expenditure is quite high. Furthermore, aside from having decent concealment abilities and speed, this carriage's defensive properties are quite lackluster, so it can easily be destroyed by attacks. As such, I wouldn't normally use it unless it was necessary to do so," Han Li explained.

Bai Bi and Lei Lan nodded in response and didn't make any further inquiries.

Thus, the flying carriage whizzed through the air, disappearing into the distance in the blink of an eye.

Unbeknownst to Han Li's trio, in the extremely far distance behind them, a ball of green mist faltered in mid-air before a low roar of rage erupted from within it. Immediately thereafter, it also accelerated as it hurtled ahead.

Within a canyon that was closes to the gate leading to the first level of the earth abyss, there was a group of seven or eight Flying Spirit Tribe beings advancing in a cautious manner.

The being leading the way had red skin and dark expression on his face. These were none other than Zhu Yinzi and the Chi Rong Race holy disciples.

Chapter 1445: Mysterious Mountain Ranges

The further they advanced in the canyon, the deeper they went into the abyss. The entire space up ahead was completely pitch black without even the slightest hint of light, as if they'd made their way down into an infernal hell.

However, all of the Chi Rong beings' eyes were shimmering with piercing red light, allowing them to see in the darkness, so all of them remained quite calm.

Not long after that, a strange cry erupted from the darkness up ahead, and a vast flock of bird-sized bats with purplish-red eyes pounced toward them while letting loose sharp screeches.

Zhu Yinzi was flying at the forefront of the group, and he merely looked on with expressionlessly at the menacing oncoming bats before abruptly flapping his wings.

Countless feathers shot forth amid a flash of red light before transforming into countless streaks of fire that passed through the flock of bats in the blink of an eye.

A series of loud explosions erupted, and all of the bats plummeted from the sky as fireballs with not a single one surviving that attack.

Thus, the Chi Rong beings continued onward without even being slowed down at all, and quickly disappeared into the darkness.

As long as they kept flying along this canyon, they'd be able to reach the second level of the earth abyss after a day and a night.

...

On a vast stretch of red land, a massive black shadow flashed through the air, seemingly fleeing from something in a panicked manner.

Not long after the black shadow flew past, spiritual light flashed in the distant sky, and a dozen or so streaks of spiritual light of different colors emerged, flying toward the same direction.

All of these beings had different types of wings growing from their backs, but they all had black tattoos on their faces. They were the beings of the Sevenpass Race, the number one branch among the Flying Spirit Race.

The thin female child flying at the forefront of the group was none other than Ao Qing, whom all of the holy disciples were wary of.

Ao Qing looked on at the fleeing black shadow up ahead with a cold smile on her face and pursued it in an unhurried manner.

After a while, a burly man among the Sevenpass Race holy disciples couldn't help but suggest, "Senior Martial Sister Ao, the direction that this Goldentusk Beast is escaping is diverging away from the entrance to the second level that we're heading toward. Wouldn't it be best to kill it now rather than continue to follow it?"

"Where's the hurry? It's very rare to encounter pack-dwelling mid-grade demon beasts like the Goldentusk Beast on just the first level of the earth abyss, so we naturally have to kill all of them at once. Are you doubting my ability to complete the trial just because we have to slightly delay our descent into the next level?" Ao Qing asked in an emotionless voice.

The burly man was given a fright upon hearing this, and he hurriedly explained, "Of course not! I wouldn't dare to think such a thing. I'm just afraid that the Infernal Flame Fruits will be taken by the holy disciples from the other branches."

"If we really do get there too late, then we can just take other people's fruits. If that doesn't work, we can always go to the fourth level of the earth abyss; there'll definitely be a vast quantity of those fruits down there," Ao Qing chuckled coldly in an implacable manner.

The burly man didn't dare to say anything else upon hearing that.

Thus, they continued to pursue the fleeing black shadow in an unhurried manner like a pride of lions toying with their prey.

...

Amid a vast expanse of rugged rocks, three Flying Spirit Race beings with blue feathered wings on their backs and scales all over their faces had surrounded a demon beast of darkness, and had launched a ferocious assault against it. This demonic creature had the head of a deer and the body of a human, and it was around 20 feet tall.

Black Qi was swirling around its body, and it held a massive black trident in its hands, managing to hold its own even in the face of several holy disciples. Furthermore, it seemed to only be growing more powerful as the battle wore on, and it was instead the three holy disciples who were slowly being forced onto the backfoot.

This was only the first level of the earth abyss, so they had no idea how a high-grade demon beast like the Deer-Faced Demon had ended up here.

However, seeing as this carnivorous demon beast was trying to prey on them, they had no choice but to fight for their lives.

Elsewhere, most of the Flying Spirit Race holy disciples on the first level had encountered unexpected troubles. However, there were also some holy disciples who had enjoyed remarkably smooth journeys, and were entering the second level as the Chi Rong beings had.

Meanwhile, in order to avoid the antagonistic Flying Spirit Race branches, Han Li had no choice but to head toward the most secluded entrance, and the flying carriage had flown for over half a day with the trio inside it.

Perhaps it was because this carriage's concealment restriction really was working or because there weren't many demon beasts on this route to begin with. In any case, they encountered no further complications during the rest of their journey, and after flying for two days and two nights, they had passed through two forests and a set of mountain ranges, arriving in a place deep within the first level of the earth abyss.

At this rate, it would only take them another day to arrive at the entrance to the second level.

Lei Lan and Bai Bi were quite elated by their progress.

However, after flying for several tens of thousands of kilometers further, a vast expanse of black mountain ranges suddenly appeared up ahead.

The three of them immediately stopped the carriage in alarm.

"According to the map, there should be a set of plains here; why are there mountain ranges instead?" Bai Bi murmured as he looked at the massive mountains up ahead.

Lei Lan was also rather dumbstruck.

Even from a distance, they could tell that all of the mountains in the mountain ranges were extremely tall. Some of them had extended to the very top of the underground world, leaving only small gaps between mountains through which one could pass, and that presented quite a daunting prospect.

No one knew just how long these mountain ranges extended for, nor whether there were any hazards awaiting them inside.

Han Li's eyes narrowed as suddenly exited the flying carriage, then descended onto the nearby ground to carefully inspect something.

Lei Lan and Bai Bi were rather surprised by what Han Li was doing, but after exchanging a quick glance, they also flew out of the carriage and landed beside Han Li.

"From the signs nearby, it appears that this set of mountain ranges has only appeared here in the past century. It was most likely moved here by someone with unfathomable power," Han Li said in a slow voice.

Lei Lan's face paled upon hearing this, and Bai Bi's expression was also rather disgruntled.

"There's no need to panic. Even the Demon Monarchs in the deepest level of the earth abyss aren't capable of such a monumental feat through their own power. This was most likely done through the assistance of some kind of treasure or formation. The only alternative possibility is that a True Spirit level demon beast has appeared in the deepest level of the abyss," Han Li said with a smile.

"I see." As a holy disciple of the Tian Peng Race, Bai Bi was no ordinary being, and he quickly realized that Han Li was right.

"Even so, the situation here isn't quite right. The desert that we passed through earlier also appeared out of nowhere. Why are the demon beasts of the earth abyss doing this? What could their intentions be?" A concerned look appeared on Lei Lan's face.

"Perhaps this is all due to the beast torrent. Even if that isn't the case and there's another reason behind all this, there's no way that the earth abyss trial would be canceled. Hence, all we can do is get to the third level, then bring back the Infernal Flame Fruit as quickly as possible and report these sightings to the higher-ups in our Tian Peng Race," Han Li said in an unflustered manner. After all, he had many similar past experiences, so this was not something new to him.

"You're right, Brother Han. However, this set of mountain ranges really is quite peculiar. If we fly through the gaps between the mountains, who knows what dangers we could encounter? But if we try to go around it..." Bai Bi said in a hesitant voice.

"We definitely can't go around it," Lei Lan rejected before analyzing, "According to the map, on one side of this land is the earth abyss wind belt, while the Black Abyssal Flying Ants' nests lay on the other side. The earth abyss winds in the wind belt are far more powerful than the gusts we've encountered before, and the glacial power imbued within them can freeze us instantly; it's a renowned restricted area. As for the ant's nests, there are hundreds of thousands of flying ants in there. If we try to force our way through it with our cultivation bases, there's at least a 50% chance that we'd all die in there."

"So that means our only choice is to pass through these mountain ranges," Han Li murmured to himself as he stroked his chin.

"Not necessarily. If we go around in an even larger circle, we can skirt around all of these hazards, but that'll take at least an extra seven or eight days. That delay could prove to be extremely detrimental to our search for the Infernal Flame Fruit." Lei Lan was becoming rather hesitant.

Meanwhile, Han Li was staring at the mountain ranges up ahead in silence.

At this moment, both Bai Bi and Lei Lan also fell silent, entrusting the final decision to Han Li.

After a while, Han Li finally made his decision. "These mountain ranges give me a very eerie feeling; if we really do go through it, I feel like we'll encounter some extreme hazards. Even if we can force our way through the mountain ranges, we'll most likely have expended a large amount of magic power, and that certainly won't hold us in good stead for the rest of the trial. As for entering the second level a few days late, I don't think that's too much of an issue. With these few days of delay, the branches that are targeting us won't be able to predict our route and ambush us. Besides, there are so many trial-takers, and there won't be all that many Infernal Flame Fruits to be found on the second level. I intend to take you two to the third level anyway, so it's better to waste some time rather than face the unknown dangers within those mountain ranges."

He then flew back into the flying carriage. Lei Lan and Bai Bi held a brief discussion through voice transmission upon seeing this before also returning to the carriage.

"Brother Han, I think we should discuss this matter in further depth. Perhaps the mountain ranges aren't as dangerous as we imagine," Bai Bi said as soon as he entered the carriage.

Even though he felt like Han Li's decision made sense, he still couldn't help but feel that wasting so much time was not wise.

"Speak no further; I won't enter these mountain ranges," Han said in an indifferent voice, cutting off what Bai Bi was about to say next.

The carriage then shot forth toward another direction at his behest.

Seeing as Han Li was so determined, Bai Bi heaved a resigned sigh and fell silent. Lei Lan didn't contribute anything further to the conversation, either,

Unbeknownst to two of them, Han Li was not feeling anywhere near as resolute and assured as he appeared.

At this moment, a wisp of his spiritual sense was connected to the Weeping Soul Beast inside his spirit beast bracelet, trying to soothe the beast's violent and uneasy emotions. At the same time, he was wondering what could the cause of its emotional outburst.

Just as he was approaching those mountain ranges earlier, the Weeping Soul Bead within his body suddenly began to heat up. His heart jolted with shock in response, and he hurriedly established a connection with the Weeping Soul Beast in his spirit beast bracelet. As a result, he discovered that the beast was in an extremely abnormal ruffled state, growling incessantly while rushing around in an erratic manner.